<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-10T01:01:21.938Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-10T01:01:21.938Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relationship Hero (YC S17) Is Hiring Sales Associates – Full Time Remote]]></title>
        <id>https://relationshiphero.com/careers?role=salesAssociate</id>
        <link href="https://relationshiphero.com/careers?role=salesAssociate"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T01:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn SQL Queries – Database Query Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>610a44f83306a507d1bfd44e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-queries-database-query-tutorial-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T00:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL stands for Structured Query Language and is a language that you use to manage data in databases. SQL consists of commands and declarative statements that act as instructions to the database so it can perform tasks.  You can use SQL commands to create a table in a database, to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to do wiring in VanillaJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarandeep_singh/how-to-do-wiring-in-vanillajs-36gh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarandeep_singh/how-to-do-wiring-in-vanillajs-36gh"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T23:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After an unbelievable start to my blogging journey, with my first two blogs crossing over 120+ bookmarks combined, here I am with my third blog! This time around we are going to touch on the basics of JavaScript.
"VanillaJS" is a term that developers use to describe regular JavaScript. It means using the inbuilt JavaScript methods and objects without any additional libraries or frameworks.
So why use VanillaJS instead of libraries or frameworks? Well, we gotta admit libraries like ReactJS are just amazing but VanillaJS is faster than any other JavaScript framework because it has fewer overheads. Moreover, Using frameworks or libraries in JS is a little like using Bootstrap or Tailwind in CSS, we might miss out on the fundamentals, it eliminates control over your abilities to solve the prob…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarandeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript If-Else and If-Then – JS Conditional Statements]]></title>
        <id>610657e03306a507d1bfc108</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-if-else-and-if-then-js-conditional-statements/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T23:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There will be times where you will want to write commands that handle different decisions in your code.  For example, if you are coding a bot, you can have it respond with different messages based on a set of commands it receives.  In this article, I will explain what an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug-resistant bacteria found in the guts of lemurs who live around humans]]></title>
        <id>https://today.duke.edu/2021/08/drug-resistant-bacteria-found-guts-lemurs-who-live-around-humans</id>
        <link href="https://today.duke.edu/2021/08/drug-resistant-bacteria-found-guts-lemurs-who-live-around-humans"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T23:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Memory of Abel Wang]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/in-memory-of-abel-wang-fam</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/in-memory-of-abel-wang-fam"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T22:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abel Wang (1972-2021) was Principal Program Manager, Technical Assistant to the CTO of Azure at Microsoft. 
For many years he was a DevOps enthusiast, and in fact he worked as DevOps Lead and Advocate in the Donovan Brown's team until the recent promotion.
You may know him by his nickname AbelSquidHead. He used to be a speaker at many technical events and conferences, and also either a host or guest of countless videos.
Abel was hands down one of the most passionate DevOps practitioners I've ever had the pleasure to listen to. Actually, he was one of the most passionate people in everything he did.
He passed away in July 2021, cancer took him away.
This is my small tribute to him, to one of the best of us all.
In memory of Abel Wang. Rest in Peace. You are and will always be sorely missed.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/Ortp-e5T_8Q]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide 'CoderDave' Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future Is a Landscape]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ecosophia.net/the-future-is-a-landscape/</id>
        <link href="https://www.ecosophia.net/the-future-is-a-landscape/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T22:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metodologías CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marskdev/metodologias-css-2pg2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marskdev/metodologias-css-2pg2"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T22:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metodologías CSS


Una de las cosas difíciles en el desarrollo web y programación en general es el nombramiento de las cosas y el nombramiento en CSS no es diferente.
Cuando trabajas en un proyecto pequeño el nombramiento no es una prioridad pero si es una buena practica, todo cambia cuando se convierte en un proyecto grande, entonces el nombramiento se vuelve primordial, mantener el rastro de todos los selectores se vuelve un caos sin una convención de nombres, usar alguna hará la tarea fácil.
El código se volverá sencillo de leer, mantener y modificar.
Una convención de nombres es un conjunto de reglas para la elección de la secuencia de caracteres que se utilice para identificadores que denoten variables, tipos, funciones y otras entidades en el código fuente y la documentación.
Algunas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcial Ambriz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google Colab with VS Code]]></title>
        <id>610e257e3306a507d1bffc96</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-google-colab-with-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T22:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Colab and VS Code are two popular editor tools that many Python developers use. They're great for developing efficient tech solutions or systems especially in the areas of Machine Learning and Data Science. If you're a Python developer or data scientist, you might already know how to use Google]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stages of Denial]]></title>
        <id>https://beyondloom.com/blog/denial.html</id>
        <link href="https://beyondloom.com/blog/denial.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T22:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understand One-way Data Binding in React the easy way!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/parnikagupta/one-way-data-binding-in-react-30ea</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/parnikagupta/one-way-data-binding-in-react-30ea"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T22:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a popular JavaScript library for many reasons and one of the reasons is “one-way data binding”. If you want to understand React to its core, you should read along.
It’s a one-way road for the data
React apps are made up of carefully organized components. These components receive arguments(props) and return information using the return value of the render function. When data flows from the parent to the child component, it is known as the unidirectional flow of data.
Parent component passes information to child component using props. But it is also possible that a child component might end up requiring to change something in the UI. What to do in that case?
Is it possible to pass data from the child to parent component?
What if clicking a button in the child component changes the t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parnika-Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Lukashenka hackers seize senior Belarusian officials' personal data]]></title>
        <id>https://en.currenttime.tv/a/seeking-change-anti-lukashenka-hackers-seize-senior-belarusian-officials-personal-data-/31392092.html</id>
        <link href="https://en.currenttime.tv/a/seeking-change-anti-lukashenka-hackers-seize-senior-belarusian-officials-personal-data-/31392092.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choice Words about the Upcoming Deprecation of JavaScript Dialogs]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346368</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/choice-words-about-the-upcoming-deprecation-of-javascript-dialogs/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It might be the very first thing a lot of people learn in JavaScript:
alert("Hello, World");
One day at CodePen, we woke up to a ton of customer support tickets about their Pens being broken, which ultimately boiled down to …
The post Choice Words about the Upcoming Deprecation of JavaScript Dialogs appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js with MySQL database.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/popoolatopzy/connecting-node-js-with-mysql-database-36dh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/popoolatopzy/connecting-node-js-with-mysql-database-36dh"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting node.js project with MySQL database is easy, follow the following steps to connect to the the database
By reading this article I believe you have installed nodee Js on your system and familiar with it.
 Step1
Open your code editor.
 Step2
Create a new project
 mkdir project_name
 cd project_name

 Step3
Create project file.
 npm init -y

into the command prompt or terminal.
 Step4
To be able to connect to mysql database you need to install MySQL module into your project.
To do this is very simple, open your CMD or terminal and enter
 npm install mysql

this command will install the module into your project.
 Step5
Now we can open connection From our project code to mysql database

const mysql = require('mysql');

// Creating a mysql connection
const conn = mysql.createConnection({
   host: "localhost",
   user: "db_username",
   password: "db_password",
   database: "db_name"
});

 Step6
Let create a simple database and table
conn.connect((err)=>{
   if (err) throw err;
      console.log("Database connected successful");
   var sql = "CREATE TABLE books (book_name VARCHAR(255), book_description VARCHAR(255))";
   con.query(sql,(err, result)=> {
      if (err) throw err;
         console.log("Table created");
   });
});


You can leave a comment...
Thanks❤️]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>popoola Temitope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure vs Impure Functions in Functional Programming – What&#x27;s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>610d55bf3306a507d1bff496</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pure-function-vs-impure-function/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pure functions and impure functions are two programming terms you will often see in functional programming. Once core difference between these two types of functions is whether or not they have side effects. In this article, you will learn what side effects are and we'll discuss the differences between pure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Yarn 2, Goodbye node_modules]]></title>
        <id>https://freddixx.medium.com/hello-yarn-2-goodbye-node-modules-21d97afc1a75</id>
        <link href="https://freddixx.medium.com/hello-yarn-2-goodbye-node-modules-21d97afc1a75"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Video] Learn how to debug web projects end-to-end in VS Code in 5 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codepo8/video-learn-how-to-debug-web-projects-end-to-end-in-vs-code-in-5-minutes-1kpa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codepo8/video-learn-how-to-debug-web-projects-end-to-end-in-vs-code-in-5-minutes-1kpa"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This weekend I released a video on the YouTube Channel of Visual Studio Code that shows end-to-end web project debugging. 




In five minutes I walk through debugging a web project bit by bit:
I open a project inside VS Code by opening its folder. The demo used is a simple, plain Vanilla JS/CSS/HTML ToDo app you can download/fork on GitHub.
I open a Terminal inside VS Code and start a local server. I use the server that comes with PHP as it already on my computer (for now - MacOS will soon deprecate this option)
Instead of opening the project in the browser, I use the run and debug workflow of VS Code to open a dedicated browser instance to debug this project with. If I have a Chromium based browser on my device and have it set as my default browser, this will be the one VS Code uses. In …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Heilmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning won't solve natural language understanding]]></title>
        <id>https://thegradient.pub/machine-learning-wont-solve-the-natural-language-understanding-challenge/</id>
        <link href="https://thegradient.pub/machine-learning-wont-solve-the-natural-language-understanding-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volley (YC W18) is hiring engineers to build voice games]]></title>
        <id>https://jobs.lever.co/volleythat/5200aeb9-5c55-4490-a92f-1a663d0d8c49</id>
        <link href="https://jobs.lever.co/volleythat/5200aeb9-5c55-4490-a92f-1a663d0d8c49"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Difficult math is about recognizing patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://get21stnight.com/2021/08/09/difficult-math-is-about-recognizing-patterns-lessons-from-jeff-bezos/</id>
        <link href="https://get21stnight.com/2021/08/09/difficult-math-is-about-recognizing-patterns-lessons-from-jeff-bezos/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Move Fast, Break Things & Win: How Facebook Builds Software]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linearb/move-fast-break-things-win-how-facebook-builds-software-2966</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linearb/move-fast-break-things-win-how-facebook-builds-software-2966"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Founder, professional poker player, podcaster and author, Jeff Meyerson, “broke his brain” to bring you the inside-story of Facebook.
Interviewing more than two dozen Facebook engineers, Jeff spent two and a half years writing his new book Move Fast: How Facebook Builds Software. Written from Facebook’s own view of their software strategy and tactics, Move Fast explores the product strategy, cultural principles, and technologies that made Facebook the dominant social networking company.
Jeff joined Dev Interrupted to give us insight into his book and the secrets behind Facebook’s success, the founding story of the Software Daily podcast, the inside scoop on his new company SuperCompute, and how the skills and logic behind poker translate to software engineering.
Listen to the full episode







  
  
  Episode Highlights Include:




The intersection of poker and software engineering


Founding story of the Software Daily podcast


How to think about winning a market


First steps to take when founding a company


Product, culture and engineering — How do they relate?


Is the Facebook the Goldman Sach’s of software?


Why Facebook’s secret sauce is it’s onboarding process, not marketing




If you haven't already heard, Dev Interrupted is partnering with Dzone to host INTERACT: An interactive, community-driven, digital conference on September 30th - by engineering leaders, for engineering leaders. 1 day, 10 speakers, 100s of engineers and engineering leaders, all free.
Register Now






  
  
  Join the Dev Interrupted Server


With over 1500 members, the Dev Interrupted Discord Community is the best place for Engineering Leaders to engage in daily conversation. No sales people allowed. Join the community >>

Originally published at https://devinterrupted.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Bronsdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Torrentinim – low memory-footprint, API-only torrent search engine]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/sergiotapia/torrentinim</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/sergiotapia/torrentinim"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Large, Small, and Dynamic Viewports]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346316</id>
        <link href="https://www.bram.us/2021/07/08/the-large-small-and-dynamic-viewports/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got viewport units (e.g. vw, vh, vmin, vmax), and they are mostly pretty great. It’s cool to always have a unit available that is relative to the entire screen. But when you ask people what …
The post The Large, Small, and Dynamic Viewports appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New carnivorous plant discovered in Pacific Northwest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.npr.org/2021/08/09/1026091196/this-sweet-white-flower-is-actually-a-sneaky-carnivore-scientists-discovered</id>
        <link href="https://www.npr.org/2021/08/09/1026091196/this-sweet-white-flower-is-actually-a-sneaky-carnivore-scientists-discovered"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Beginnings]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jdc1492/new-beginnings-4ooo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jdc1492/new-beginnings-4ooo"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a dev, I find myself constantly thinking about the variety of languages that are out there and if there's one that I would "prefer" over the others. While I can see why that mindset could be a harmful one to a developers.....development, it's still a thought that occasionally crosses my mind. In cases like these it never hurts to feed the curiosity though. 
I recently started a Udemy Python Course. I decided to finally take the chance to see what it was all about. So far I've been able to successfully create a bandname generator. To achieve this, I had to become familiar with the print function, the input function and variable assignment within the language.
Note: I've been working within an environment on Replit.com So for right now the playground is set up for me. As I learn how to ru…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incentives in Computer Science]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cs.columbia.edu/~tr/s20/s20.html</id>
        <link href="http://www.cs.columbia.edu/~tr/s20/s20.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving microservice architecture with GraphQL API gateways]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/logrocket/improving-microservice-architecture-with-graphql-api-gateways-gb6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/logrocket/improving-microservice-architecture-with-graphql-api-gateways-gb6"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Written by Alec Brunelle ✏️
As your organization grows, it's common for multiple API services to be created, each one providing its own feature set. Alongside these services, you’ll want to provide different client apps for your users to use your product. Eventually, your architecture might look like this:








Every client app has different needs



There are many reasons why this happens. Over time, team structure may have directed service creation, and at the time, it was easier to have a single team own a single codebase instead of having a web of teams to service ownership.
Another reason could be that different features in your product had different scaling concerns. For example, your analytics stack may have drastically different needs than your user login stack, and it doesn't m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Angelosanto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amplify Geo + Amplify CDN + Svelte!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/njreid/amplify-geo-amplify-cdn-svelte-5faa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/njreid/amplify-geo-amplify-cdn-svelte-5faa"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to add maps to your Svelte app?
So, we're already seeing some great feedback on our Amplify Geo developer preview release - thanks to everyone who has taken the time to play with it. I thought I'd share some hacky code I threw together to try out using our new CDN-delivered Amplify libraries in an mostly-unbundled Svelte app. 
CDN-powered unbundling can be nice. Until recently, Amplify-powered JS apps have been conventionally bundled at build time. CDN unbundling is particularly handy for Svelte+Rollup, because none of the Amplify libraries need to be parsed each build iteration, meaning lightning-fast refreshes. Also, the resulting bundle is pretty small. My bundle.js for this app  is just 19Kb, unminified.
Grab your favorite Svelte template. I'm a typescript+pug+styl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Native Chaos Engineering with Chaos Mesh]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/cloud-native-chaos-engineering-with-chaos-mesh-3a96</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/cloud-native-chaos-engineering-with-chaos-mesh-3a96"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T19:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Cloud, distributed architectures have grown even more complex and with complexity comes the uncertainty in how the system could fail.
Chaos Engineering aims to test system resiliency by injecting faults to identify weaknesses before they cause massive outages such as improper fallback settings for a service, cascading failures due to a single point of failure, or retry storms due to misconfigured timeouts.
Chaos Engineering started at Netflix back in 2010 when Netflix moved from on-prem servers to AWS infrastructure to test the resiliency of their infrastructure. 
In 2012, Netflix open-sourced ChaosMonkey under Apache 2.0 license as a tool to test the resilience of your application infrastructure. 
CNCF focuses on Cloud Native Chaos Engineering defined as engineering practices focused…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shardul Srivastava</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Flask Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/phylis/my-first-flask-application-2mm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/phylis/my-first-flask-application-2mm"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T19:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION
Have you ever wished you knew how to program, but you have no idea where to start from?.@Lux Tech Academy will guide you on how to Learn Programming, Software Engineering, Data Science, Data Structures, Algorithms and Developer Relations The Right Way.  
For the past three weeks during the Python Bootcamp I have;
Gained basic Python programming concepts. You can check the python basics Here.


Learnt how to develop real-world Python applications.


Learnt how  Python object-oriented programming can be applied to develop software more effectively Here.


Learnt how to develop Python functions, and how to use flow control statements in python. Check it Here.


Been able to apply Python programming techniques in specific fields such as Web Development, Data Science, Machine Learn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PhylisChumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When zero cost abstractions aren't zero cost]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.polybdenum.com/2021/08/09/when-zero-cost-abstractions-aren-t-zero-cost.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.polybdenum.com/2021/08/09/when-zero-cost-abstractions-aren-t-zero-cost.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T19:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildfire restored a Yosemite watershed]]></title>
        <id>https://news.berkeley.edu/2021/08/09/how-wildfire-restored-a-yosemite-watershed/</id>
        <link href="https://news.berkeley.edu/2021/08/09/how-wildfire-restored-a-yosemite-watershed/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T18:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Free, Accessible AI Art Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://colab.research.google.com/drive/1n_xrgKDlGQcCF6O-eL3NOd_x4NSqAUjK</id>
        <link href="https://colab.research.google.com/drive/1n_xrgKDlGQcCF6O-eL3NOd_x4NSqAUjK"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T18:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bring back hydrogen lifting gas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thecgo.org/news/bring-back-hydrogen-lifting-gas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.thecgo.org/news/bring-back-hydrogen-lifting-gas/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T17:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cross Site Scripting? How to Protect against XSS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>5fff3dd898be260817e495cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cross-site-scripting-what-is-xss/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T17:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross Site Scripting is the second most prevalent issue in the Open Source Foundation for Application Security (OWASP) top 10 – it's found in roughly 2/3 of all applications.  While automated tools can find some of these problems, there are also automated tools designed to detect and exploit these vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why does it take so long to get to Mercury?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.esa.int/Science_Exploration/Space_Science/BepiColombo/Why_does_it_take_so_long_to_get_to_Mercury</id>
        <link href="https://www.esa.int/Science_Exploration/Space_Science/BepiColombo/Why_does_it_take_so_long_to_get_to_Mercury"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T17:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundamentals of Incident Management]]></title>
        <id>https://bitfieldconsulting.com/blog/got-game-secrets-of-great-incident-management</id>
        <link href="https://bitfieldconsulting.com/blog/got-game-secrets-of-great-incident-management"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T16:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s Mistake]]></title>
        <id>https://stratechery.com/2021/apples-mistake/</id>
        <link href="https://stratechery.com/2021/apples-mistake/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T15:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML &lt;a&gt; Tag – Anchor Link HREF Example]]></title>
        <id>610d9b6a3306a507d1bff9f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-a-tag-anchor-link-href-example/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T15:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use HTML's <a> tag to link to different parts of a website, to another web page, or to a separate website entirely.  By default, it is underlined and given a bluish color, but you can override these style defaults with CSS (which a lot of people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alter Table in SQL – How to Add a Column or Rename a Column in SQL]]></title>
        <id>610682ee3306a507d1bfc210</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/alter-table-in-sql-how-to-add-a-column-or-rename-a-column-in-sql/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have created your database and your tables, and after all this work, you notice that you need to add or rename a column. Well, you can use the ALTER TABLE statement to do so. Just keep in mind that you need to be really careful when you do this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the CSS Paint API: Image Fragmentation Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345642</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/exploring-the-css-paint-api-image-fragmentation-effect/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T14:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous article, I created a fragmentation effect using CSS mask and custom properties. It was a neat effect but it has one drawback: it uses a lot of CSS code (generated using Sass). This time I am …
The post Exploring the CSS Paint API: Image Fragmentation Effect appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World of CSS Transforms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.joshwcomeau.com/css/transforms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.joshwcomeau.com/css/transforms/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T13:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rocks and Minerals of Minecraft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mindat.org/a/minecraft</id>
        <link href="https://www.mindat.org/a/minecraft"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T13:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Digital Leader Certification Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 6 Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>610aabc23306a507d1bfdc7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-cloud-digital-leader-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T13:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to pass the Google Cloud Digital Leader Certification with this free 6-hour course! This is a significant milestone for free cloud certifications courses, since we now have on freeCodeCamp all the three major cloud service providers (AWS, Azure and GCP). What is the Google Cloud Certified Cloud Digital]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build your own NeXT with a virtual machine]]></title>
        <id>https://learn.adafruit.com/build-your-own-next-with-a-virtual-machine?view=all</id>
        <link href="https://learn.adafruit.com/build-your-own-next-with-a-virtual-machine?view=all"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T12:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A wind-powered vehicle that can travel twice as fast as the wind itself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.businessinsider.com/youtuber-won-10000-bet-with-physicist-over-wind-powered-vehicle-2021-7</id>
        <link href="https://www.businessinsider.com/youtuber-won-10000-bet-with-physicist-over-wind-powered-vehicle-2021-7"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T11:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Watches Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fratellowatches.com/how-watches-work-what-is-an-automatic-watch-and-what-different-types-of-winding-weights-are-there/</id>
        <link href="https://www.fratellowatches.com/how-watches-work-what-is-an-automatic-watch-and-what-different-types-of-winding-weights-are-there/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T11:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/3 From A To Z: Core Concepts (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-core-concepts-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-core-concepts-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What exactly is HTTP/3? Why was it needed so soon after HTTP/2 (which was only finalized in 2015)? How can or should you use it? And especially, how does this improve web performance? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robin Marx)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crystal arrangement results in more power from ferroelectric solar cells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pv-magazine.com/2021/08/04/crystal-arrangement-results-in-1000x-more-power-from-ferroelectric-solar-cells/</id>
        <link href="https://www.pv-magazine.com/2021/08/04/crystal-arrangement-results-in-1000x-more-power-from-ferroelectric-solar-cells/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T10:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elle: A transactional consistency checker for black-box databases]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/jepsen-io/elle</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/jepsen-io/elle"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T08:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What happens if you stick your head in a particle accelerator? (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://aeon.co/ideas/why-we-can-stop-worrying-and-love-the-particle-accelerator</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/ideas/why-we-can-stop-worrying-and-love-the-particle-accelerator"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T06:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ModelingToolkit, Modelica, and Modia: The Composable Modeling Future in Julia]]></title>
        <id>http://www.stochasticlifestyle.com/modelingtoolkit-modelica-and-modia-the-composable-modeling-future-in-julia/</id>
        <link href="http://www.stochasticlifestyle.com/modelingtoolkit-modelica-and-modia-the-composable-modeling-future-in-julia/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-08T20:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Public Library’s Picture Collection Will Be Archived]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/08/03/arts/design/new-york-public-library-picture-collection.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/08/03/arts/design/new-york-public-library-picture-collection.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-08T16:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing object-oriented software vs. what I would do]]></title>
        <id>https://dpc.pw/growing-object-oriented-software-vs-what-i-would-do</id>
        <link href="https://dpc.pw/growing-object-oriented-software-vs-what-i-would-do"/>
        <updated>2021-08-08T09:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Update Statement – Update Query in SQL]]></title>
        <id>61067c973306a507d1bfc1ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-update-statement-update-query-in-sql/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T21:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once you have created a table in a database, it will rarely need to stay the same forever. You will likely need to modify the records in it.  And to help you do that, there is a useful statement, aptly named UPDATE, that you can use to change the records]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Row VS Column in Excel – What is the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>610cebc13306a507d1bfeca9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/row-vs-column-in-excel-what-is-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T21:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Excel displays data in tabular format. This means that information is arranged in a table consisting of rows and columns.  Rows and columns are different properties that together make up a table.  These are the two most important features of Excel that allow users to store and manipulate their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Gobbler]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346259</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-gobbler/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T19:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great little project from Ross Moody: 
SVG Gobbler is a browser extension that finds the vector content on the page you’re viewing and gives you the option to download, optimize, copy, view the code, or export it as an image.
…
The post SVG Gobbler appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Nuxt Features past v2.10]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346290</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/new-nuxt-features-past-v2-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T15:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nuxt offers an incredible developer experience, with a lot of performance and application setup best practices baked in. In recent releases, they’ve been working on taking this developer experience to the next level, with some newer features that speed up …
The post New Nuxt Features past v2.10 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Drasner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Infinite Utility Helpers Using Inline CSS Custom Properties and calc()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345467</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/efficient-infinite-utility-helpers-using-inline-css-custom-properties-and-calc/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T14:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently wrote a very basic Sass loop that outputs several padding and margin utility classes. Nothing fancy, really, just a Sass map with 11 spacing values, looped over to create classes for both padding and margin on each side. …
The post Efficient Infinite Utility Helpers Using Inline CSS Custom Properties and calc() appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gridless.design]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345878</id>
        <link href="https://gridless.design/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T14:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donnie D’Amato built a whole site around the thesis that “digital designers still expect to use the grid while experienced layout engineers have moved beyond it.” The idea isn’t that we should never literally use display: grid; but rather that …
The post gridless.design appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bounce Back Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6708</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/bounce-back-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=bounce-back-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Bounce Back is a book by Susan Kahn, a business coach who will teach you the psychology of resilience from the perspectives of Greek philosophy, Sigmund Freud, and modern neuroscience, so you can recover quickly from professional blunders of all kinds by changing your thinking. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: […]
The post Bounce Back Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Useful VSCode Extensions For Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code can be supercharged wuth hundreds of [VS Code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/). In this article, Leonardo shares four useful extensions that help him in his daily work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Buggy React Code Examples and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345418</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/three-buggy-react-code-examples-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T14:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s usually more than one way to code a thing in React. And while it’s possible to create the same thing different ways, there may be one or two approaches that technically work “better” than others. I actually run into …
The post Three Buggy React Code Examples and How to Fix Them appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hugh Haworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Disabled Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we make disabled buttons more inclusive? When do they work well, and when do they fail on us? And finally, when do we actually need them, and how can we avoid them? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full-Stack Mobile Application With Flutter, Fauna, and GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345552</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-build-a-full-stack-mobile-application-with-flutter-fauna-and-graphql/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Flutter is Google’s UI framework used to create flexible, expressive cross-platform mobile applications. It is one of the fastest-growing frameworks for mobile app development. On the other hand, Fauna is a transactional, developer-friendly serverless …
The post How to Build a Full-Stack Mobile Application With Flutter, Fauna, and GraphQL appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shadid Haque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web Workers In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345866</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T23:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You gotta appreciate the tenacity of Surma. He’s been advocating for Web Workers as a path forward to better-feeling websites for a lot of years now. He’s at it again making sure we all understand the landscape:
[…] regardless 
…
The post The State Of Web Workers In 2021 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using CSS Shapes for Interesting User Controls and Navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345274</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-css-shapes-for-interesting-user-controls-and-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T14:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Straight across or down, that’s the proverbial order for user controls on a screen. Like a list of menu items. But what if we change that to a more fluid layout with bends, curves, and nooks? We can pull it …
The post Using CSS Shapes for Interesting User Controls and Navigation appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Socialism Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6696</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/socialism-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=socialism-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Socialism by Michael Newman outlines the history of the governmental theory that everything should be owned and controlled by the community as a whole, including how this idea has impacted the world in the last 200 years, how its original aims have been lost, and ways we might use it in the future. Read in: […]
The post Socialism Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Children And Iteration Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll discuss and learn about the use case of iterating over React `children` and the ways to do it. In particular, we will deep dive into one of the utility methods, `React.Children.toArray`, that React gives us, which helps to iterate over the children in a way which ensures performance and determinism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arihant Verma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Functions as Proxies]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345744</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/serverless-functions-as-proxies/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T20:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time cloud functions / serverless functions clicked for me was when I saw and tried Auth0’s (now defunct) Webtask. It was a little CodePen-like IDE but you didn’t really see anything aside from code and logs. The …
The post Serverless Functions as Proxies appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic Daily GitHub Backups, Restored in Seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345807</id>
        <link href="https://srv.buysellads.com/ads/long/x/TCZHURZTTTTTTT3IJZ7NTTTTTTTVINFLKTTTTTTTADBXPYTTTTTTTIDNVJR6YWS22M4647ZVKMPW454EQMNWVWPMPABT"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T20:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Any company that uses GitHub for critical applications needs a backup that can be restored quickly when needed. Cyberattacks, human errors, or a forced push are just some of the scenarios that can result …
The post Automatic Daily GitHub Backups, Restored in Seconds appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rewind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How fast can you pipe a large file to a C++ program?]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19429</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/08/03/how-fast-can-you-pipe-a-large-file-to-a-c-program/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T17:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under many operating systems, you can send data from from one process to another using ‘pipes’. The term ‘pipe’ is probably used by analogy with plumbing and we often use the the symbol ‘|‘ to represent a pipe (it looks like a vertical pipe). Thus, for example, you can sort a file and send it … Continue reading How fast can you pipe a large file to a C++ program?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive on Skipping to Content]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345154</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-deep-dive-on-skipping-to-content/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T14:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most people browsing the web on a computer use a mouse, many rely on their keyboard instead. Theoretically, using a web page with the keyboard should not be a problem — press the TAB key to move the keyboard …
The post A Deep Dive on Skipping to Content appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ratcliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Resilient JavaScript UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resilience is intrinsic to the web and therefore us, web developers. This article explores how graceful degradation, defensive coding, observability, and a healthy attitude towards failures better equips us before, during, and after an error occurs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Callum Hart)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Modules (The Native Ones)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345756</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-modules-the-native-ones/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T18:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They are actually called “CSS Module Scripts” and are a native browser feature, as opposed to the popular open-source project that essentially does scoped styles by creating unique class name identifiers in both HTML and CSS. 
Native CSS Modules are …
The post CSS Modules (The Native Ones) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goals! Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6694</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/goals-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=goals-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T12:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Goals! By Brian Tracy shows you how to unleash the power of goal setting to help you get or become whatever you want, identifying ways to set goals that lead you to success by being specific, challenging yourself, thinking positively, preparing, adjusting your timelines on big goals, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite […]
The post Goals! Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Strategy, Regression Testing And Maintenance (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a deep dive into the refactoring process itself, and cover incremental refactoring strategy, visual regression testing, and maintaining the refactored codebase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19419</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/31/science-and-technology-links-july-31st-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T19:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers built a microscope that might be 10 times better than the best available microscopes. Subsidizing college education can lower earnings due to lower job experience: The Post 9/11 GI Bill (PGIB) is among the largest and most generous college subsidies enacted thus far in the U.S. (…) the introduction of the PGIB raised college … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes In August (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2021. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6687</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/now-discover-your-strengths-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=now-discover-your-strengths-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Now, Discover Your Strengths shows you how to find your top five strengths by outlining what strengths are, how you get them, why they’re important to reaching your full potential, and how to discover your own through analyzing the times when your behavior is the most natural or instinctive and why. Read in: 4 […]
The post Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An E-Commerce Site With Angular 11, Commerce Layer And Paypal]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having an e-commerce store is crucial for any store owner as more and more customers are turning to online shopping. In this tutorial, we shall go through how to create an e-commerce site with Angular 11. The site will use the Commerce Layer as a headless e-commerce API and use Paypal to process payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19408</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/29/measuring-memory-usage-virtual-versus-real-memory/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T21:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developers are often concerned with the memory usage of their applications, and rightly so. Software that uses too much memory can fail, or be slow. Memory allocation will not work the same way under all systems. However, at a high level, most modern operating systems have virtual memory and physical memory (RAM). When you write … Continue reading Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Such Thing As A CSS Absolute Unit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are absolute units? What are the differences between relative and absolute units, and how do we create accurate sizes on the web? In this article, Elad Shechter explains why CSS absolute units aren’t so absolute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elad Shechter)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Democracies Die Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6683</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-democracies-die-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-democracies-die-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How Democracies Die explores the foundational ideas of democracy by looking at historical events, especially in Latin America, that show how democracies have failed, whether it can happen again, and how to protect democracy from threats like mutual toleration, inequality, and political parties. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: When Donald […]
The post How Democracies Die Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating An Accessible Dialog From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dialogs are everywhere in modern interface design (for good or for bad), and yet many of them are not accessible to assistive technologies. In this article, we will dig into how to create a short script to create accessible dialogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kitty Giraudel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global vs. Local Styling In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has strong opinions about how to organize JavaScript but not CSS. How can we develop patterns that encourage best CSS practices while also following the framework’s logic? The answer is surprisingly simple — to write well-structured CSS that balances global and local styling concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Dubovoy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kindness Method Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6677</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-kindness-method-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-kindness-method-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T12:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Kindness Method by Shahroo Izadi teaches how self-compassion and understanding make forming habits easier than being hard on yourself, using the personal experiences of the author and what she’s learned as an addiction recovery therapist to show how self-esteem is the true key to behavior change. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post The Kindness Method Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Serverless Functions And The International Space Station]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby recently announced the launch of “functions”. In this article, Paul Scanlon explains how to get the current location of the International Space Station (ISS) as it orbits the Earth in real-time using [Gatsby Functions](https://www.gatsbyjs.com/docs/reference/functions/) and then display it on a 3D interactive globe using [React Three Fibre](https://github.com/pmndrs/react-three-fiber).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soundtracks Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6665</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/soundtracks-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=soundtracks-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T12:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Soundtracks is New York Times bestselling author Jon Acuff’s 2021 book that teaches you how to beat overthinking by challenging whether your thoughts are true, retiring unhelpful and unkind ideas, adopting thought-boosting mantras from others, using symbols to reinforce positive thoughts, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Is there […]
The post Soundtracks Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Attracting Clients To Your Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many web design agencies consider it a badge of honor that they win work exclusively through word-of-mouth recommendations. In this article, Paul Boag explains why that is entirely the wrong attitude and what to do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Time To Your Schedule As A Professional]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you running a business and have too many things going on at once? Meetings, bugs, customer feedback, new clients in addition to your already tight deadlines? Let’s face it, time management is hard, and it becomes even more difficult in the trying times we are in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[75 Hard Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6657</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/75-hard-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=75-hard-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: 75 Hard is a fitness challenge and book that teaches mental toughness by making you commit to five daily critical tasks for 75 days straight, including drinking a gallon of water, reading 10 pages of a non-fiction book, doing two 45-minute workouts, taking a progress picture, and following a diet. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post 75 Hard Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? We’ve collected some useful color tools and resources that we’ve discovered lately — to help you get the most out of your creativity. We’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [accessible front-end components](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/complete-guide-accessible-front-end-components/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fail Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6656</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-fail-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-fail-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T12:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Fail shows the surprising benefits of going through a difficult time through the experiences of the author, Elizabeth Day, including the failures in her life that she’s grateful for and how they’ve helped her grow, uncovering why we shouldn’t be so afraid of failure but instead embrace it. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post How To Fail Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From WordPress To A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at when it makes sense to migrate from a monolithic project to a headless setup and the benefits that come with it. In addition to a step-by-step guide on how to migrate WordPress to Storyblok Headless CMS, the problems that will arise during the process and how to deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Change Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6655</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-change-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-change-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T06:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Change by Katy Milkman identifies the stumbling blocks that are in your way of reaching your goals and improving yourself and the research-backed ways to get over them, including how to beat some of the worst productivity and life problems like procrastination, laziness, and much more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post How To Change Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining End-To-End Quality With Visual Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding visual elements to your tests, you can gain more options to add meaningful ways in maintaining a high level of quality for your app. Colby Fayock explains how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Colby Fayock)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Insights I Gained While Researching Vue.js Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web app accessibility appears difficult because it seems that there is little information on the subject available online. Let’s take a closer look at the accessible use of framework features, concrete Vue.js traits, as well as community initiatives and vetted patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISR vs DPR: Big Words, Quick Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two strategies for incrementally building websites that are growing in popularity: Incremental Static Regeneration and Distributed Persistent Rendering. What’s the difference? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cassidy Williams)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Do That With A JavaScript Data Grid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll get to see some pretty groundbreaking things you can achieve with modern JavaScript grids and discover new ways to augment a data grid to make it engaging, responsive, and accessible. All this will be illustrated using Kendo UI Data Grids and their features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19380</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/14/faster-sorted-array-unions-by-reducing-branches/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing an index, a database or a search engine, you frequently need to compute the union of two sorted sets. When I am not using fancy low-level instructions, I have most commonly computed the union of two sorted sets using the following approach: v1 = first value in input 1 v2 = first value … Continue reading Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Broken Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Too often dealing with filters can be frustrating. Let’s get them right. That means never freeze the UI on a single input, provide text input fallback and never auto-scroll users on a single input. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Dynamic Header With Intersection Observer]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, attaching an event listener to constantly fire a callback on scroll can be performance-intensive. But there is a better way with Intersection Observer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From jQuery To Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’re taking a closer look at different approaches and strategies on how we can migrate a web application that uses jQuery framework, and start using one of the coolest React frameworks in the market: Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Introduction (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS refactoring is not an easy task — it needs to be done in a way that doesn't create problems. First we need to analyze the existing codebase, audit CSS codebase health, discover weaknesses, agree on the approach, and convince management to invest time and resources into the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>