<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-25T15:36:41.256Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-25T15:36:41.256Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.8.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Fig (YC S20) – Autocomplete for the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://fig.io?ref=hn</id>
        <link href="https://fig.io?ref=hn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T15:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty printing JSON.stringify]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/siddharthshyniben/pretty-printing-json-stringify-4pd3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/siddharthshyniben/pretty-printing-json-stringify-4pd3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T15:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of use JSON.stringify a lot to avoid the infamous "[object Object]". But did you know that it had a few more arguments?
JSON.stringify takes a total of 3 arguments. The first one is the data, the second is a replacer function, and the third one is the indentation.
The main topic of this article is the third argument. If you provide a string as the third argument, that string will be used as indentation. Here's an example:
JSON.stringify({a: 'B', c: {d: 'e'}})
// => {"a":"B","c":{"d":"e"}}
JSON.stringify({a: 'B', c: {d: 'e'}}, null, "  ")
// => 
// {
//   "a": "B",
//   "c": {
//     "d": "e"
//   }
// }
JSON.stringify({a: 'B', c: {d: 'e'}}, null, "test")
// =>
// {
// test"a": "B",
// test"c": {
// testtest"d": "e"
// test}
// }

You can also pass in a number instead. If you do so, that many spaces will be inserted as indentation:
JSON.stringify({a: 'B', c: {d: 'e'}}, null, 2)
// => 
// {
//   "a": "B",
//   "c": {
//     "d": "e"
//   }
// }

Hope this helps you while debugging sometime!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddharth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating unique IDs in a Large scale Distributed environment]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/apoorvtyagi/generating-unique-ids-in-a-large-scale-distributed-environment-257d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/apoorvtyagi/generating-unique-ids-in-a-large-scale-distributed-environment-257d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Recently at work, We were looking for a way to generate unique IDs across a distributed system that could also be used as the primary keys in the MySQL tables.
We knew in a single MySQL database we can simply use an auto-increment ID as the primary key, But this won’t work in a sharded MySQL database.
So I looked at various existing solutions for this and finally learned about Twitter Snowflake - a simple 64-bit unique ID generator.
UUIDs are 128-bit hexadecimal numbers that are globally unique. The chances of the same UUID getting generated twice are negligible.
The problem with UUIDs is that they are very big in size and don’t index well. When your dataset increases, the index size increases as well and the query performance degrades.
Another problem with UUIDs is related …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Apoorv Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want to compress your pdf files ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/burakcank/want-to-compress-your-pdf-files-5ff9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/burakcank/want-to-compress-your-pdf-files-5ff9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of scanning images and trying to shrink them under 25 mbs just so you can send them via email ? Look no further, I am here to save you from this trouble. (that kinda rhymed.)
This basic shell script uses ghostscript to compress your scanned pdfs significantly. Just yesterday I scanned 100 pages of documents and it was over 90 mbs. I searched for a way to compress them under 25 mbs and voila. Here I was with only 6 mbs of pdfs. Much wow. Such compression.
Why we need it,
Fast.
Ez.
No need to go online. Especially no need to upload company top-secret documents to any website you see on the Internet.
Possible huge compression without notable loss.
Command usage:
./shrinkpdf.sh in.pdf out.pdf
ghostscript.





If you are in a situation exactly like me where there are 100 pdf files under one folder that you want to compress altogether, a simple for loop will suffice.
import os
import subprocess
import sys

infolder = sys.argv[1]
outfolder = "compressed_" + infolder
os.mkdir(outfolder)

for f in os.listdir(infolder):
    subprocess.run(["./shrinkpdf.sh", os.path.join(infolder, f), os.path.join(outfolder, f)])

Run this python script,
python shrink.py pdfs/
and all of your pdfs will be put under compressed_pdfs/.
http://www.alfredklomp.com/programming/shrinkpdf/
All the relevant details and more, inside. I humbly wanted to let you know such a useful tool exists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Burak Can Kahraman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persisting Typed Objects with DataStore]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yalematta/persisting-typed-objects-with-datastore-apc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yalematta/persisting-typed-objects-with-datastore-apc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post we have explored how to use Preferences DataStore to migrate our SharedPreferences. And in this post we will focus on Proto DataStore.
Proto DataStore different? 🤔


While both Preferences and Proto DataStore allow saving data, they do this in different ways. One important feature is applied only when using Proto DataStore, and it is Type Safety. 
With Proto DataStore we don't have to use keys. Instead we define a schema using Protocol Buffers. And with Protocol Buffers we can persist strongly typed data.
One of the downsides of SharedPreferences and Preferences DataStore is that there is no way to ensure that keys are accessed with the correct type. Using Proto DataStore, we know what types are stored and we will just provide them.
Protocol Buffers were developed by Go…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Layale Matta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340759</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-i-learned-building-a-word-game-app-with-nuxt-on-google-play/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I fell in love with coding the moment I created my first CSS :hover effect. Years later, that initial bite into interactivity on the web led me to a new goal: making a game.
Table of contents
What’s the game 
…
The post What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Hosting for Developer (With Free Trial)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/goonlinetools/best-hosting-for-developer-with-free-trial-di7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/goonlinetools/best-hosting-for-developer-with-free-trial-di7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
If you’re a web developer, you need a web hosting provider that offers the cheapest hosting plan, best hosting features, and as well as excellent support and full backend access.
I recommend 4 web hosting company that can serve you faster and reliably each time so that your website visitors can have a great experience.
Cloudways - 3 Days Free



Cloudways is a managed hosting provider that emphasizes performance and simplicity. From the simple server and application launch to the ongoing server maintenance, Cloudways takes away all the hassles of server management so that you can continue to focus on growing your business.
Linode - 100$ Free Credit



Linode is a cloud hosting provider that focuses on providing Linux powered virtual machines to support a wide range of applications. Given its roots, many experts do not see it as a beginner-friendly.
DigitalOcean - 100$ Free Credit



DigitalOcean is a cloud infrastructure provider that provides cloud computing services to business entities. It is used to scale by deploying DigitalOcean applications that run parallel across multiple cloud servers without compromising performance.
Vultr - 100$ Free Credit



Vultr provides high-performance SSD cloud servers that boast a global footprint. It aims to create the most reliable and efficient service for launching a blazing fast SSD cloud server.
I tried these 4 hosting presonally for my sites and every hosting perform well but cloud hosting provider doesn't provide contact support only for server, no extra support.
If you want good contact support and security in cloud hosting then i recommend Cloudways.
If you manage complete server and server security from your own then you can go with any hosting listed above but i recommend Linode.
I hope you will choose right hosting :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GoOnlineTools</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Build internal apps and dashboards using Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://chartmat.com</id>
        <link href="https://chartmat.com"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 (+/-) Linux skills for landing a Linux job]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/asciiden/top-10-linux-skills-for-landing-a-linux-job-1i5m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/asciiden/top-10-linux-skills-for-landing-a-linux-job-1i5m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hey now, you have probably went through numerous job-hunting websites and you memorized all the buzzwords (Junior Sysadmin; Junior Site Reliability Engineer; NOC Engineer; System support; etc.) that can get you in IT with zero experience, or even zero education. Well, let me tell you - you are on the right track! However, there are some insights that a lot of you don't know as you haven't got a real Linux job. Well now, except you are on the right track, you are on the post, as well!
I am going to note down & explain the top 10 Linux skills (in the opinion of a person who had a Linux job as a first) that you should have before rushing into the interview.
Linux skills? But I know a lot of commands already!
It is not up to the commands you know but the ability to imply them at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denislav Gavrilov 👨‍🚀🤖🤷‍♂️</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Goals for 2021: the Reasons to Learn Java]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexxxismyname/coding-goals-for-2021-the-reasons-to-learn-java-5b0p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexxxismyname/coding-goals-for-2021-the-reasons-to-learn-java-5b0p"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In terms of a pandemic situation, many large companies were forced to take all their processes online. So, they need someone who can build an enterprise-level server-side application, create website content, and keep up maintaining it promptly. In this case, many projects choose Java to build the apps and, consequently, need as many Java programmers as possible to implement that. So, if you still ask yourself “Why should I learn Java”, this is supposed to be an answer.
But, this is not the only reason, and I will explain why becoming a Java developer in 2021 is a fresh start.
Right before considering the other reasons for starting to master Java, it makes sense, to begin with fundamentals and discover what’s so good about becoming a programmer.
Software engineering is a fairly stable indus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The difference between a Cryptocurrency and a Token]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/owans/the-difference-between-a-cryptocurrency-and-a-token-3ee4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/owans/the-difference-between-a-cryptocurrency-and-a-token-3ee4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In broad terms, a digital asset is a non-tangible asset that is created, traded, and stored in a digital format. Using this definition In the context of blockchains, digital assets include cryptocurrency and crypto tokens.
The blockchain terms; token and cryptocurrency are often used interchangeably, as these are both digital assets on blockchains. The biggest difference between a cryptocurrency and a token is that cryptocurrencies are the native asset of a

blockchain like BTC, RBTC, or ETH, whereas tokens are built on an existing blockchain, using smart contracts. Most commonly, these are EIP-20 tokens.
The following chart summarises the similarities between the two:

As we can see, these are largely the same from the perspective of the end user. However, there are large technical differ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owanate Amachree</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Command Line for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harvey/linux-command-line-for-beginners-16n8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harvey/linux-command-line-for-beginners-16n8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux command line is for power users. It is not for the faint of heart or for people who are afraid to take a risk. 
If you are new to Linux and are afraid to take the plunge into using the command line interface, then this tutorial is a good start. 
Linux is an open source operating system that is used on everything from smart phones to main frame computers. 
Linux provides a command line interface (CLI) that provides a quick and powerful way to control and manipulate your computer. Once mastered, the Linux CLI can save you time and provide a powerful tool to aid in your daily tasks.
The command line can be intimidating but learning the basics will give you access to a world of scripts and automation tools that will make your life a lot easier and more productive.
The Basics: You will be using the command line to type various commands and tasks. Commands are what Linux runs. In Linux, the Command Line can be used for various things.

To start, open up a terminal. Now, let's try using some basic Linux commands! 
Most of these commands are applicable for all Linux distributions. Linux is case sensitive (capitalization matters).
Navigation
ls    List directory
cd DIR Change the current directory to the DIR directory
cd ~  Change to home directory
cd /      Change the current directory to the root directory
cd ..     Go one directory lower
pwd   Show name of current working directory 
File Commands
mkdir -p DIR Create directory DIR 
rm FILE Remove FILE
rm -r DIR Remove DIR and its contents recursively
rm -f FILE Force remove FILE 
System Info
date  Print or set the system date and time
cal   Displays a calendar
uptime Tell how long the system has been running
w     Show who is logged on and what they are doing
whoami  Print effective userid]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's probably time to stop recommending Clean Code (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://qntm.org/clean?tw=</id>
        <link href="https://qntm.org/clean?tw="/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.JS - Foal framework - version 2.4 is here]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loicpoullain/node-js-foal-framework-version-2-4-is-here-dhh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loicpoullain/node-js-foal-framework-version-2-4-is-here-dhh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.4 of Foal has been released! Here are the improvements that it brings.
$data references for validation


Version 2.4 allows you to enable the AJV $data option so that you can use the verified data values as validators for other values.
config/default.json
{
  "settings": {
    "ajv": {
      "$data": true
    }
  }
}

Example of auth controller
import { Context, Post, ValidateBody } from '@foal/core';

export class AuthController {
  @Post('/signup')
  @ValidateBody({
    type: 'object',
    properties: {
      username: { type: 'string' },
      password: { type: 'string' },
      // "password" and "confirmPassword" should be identical.
      confirmPassword: {
        const: {
          $data: '1/password',
        },
        type: 'string',
      },
    }
    required: [ 'username', 'password', 'confirmPassword' ],
    additionalProperties: false
  })
  signup(ctx: Context) {
    // Do something.
  }
}


Starting from version 2.4 the Disk.createHttpResponse method accepts an optional parameter to specify the value of the Cache-Control header.
import { Context, dependency, Get } from '@foal/core';
import { Disk } from '@foal/storage';

import { User } from '../entities';

export class ProfileController {
  @dependency
  disk: Disk;

  @Get('/avatar')
  async readProfileImage(ctx: Context<User>) {
    return this.disk.createHttpResponse(ctx.user.avatar, {
      cache: 'no-cache'
    });
  }

See issue #930.
@ZakRabe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Loïc Poullain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm Announces New Mobile Armv9 CPU Microarchitectures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.anandtech.com/show/16693/arm-announces-mobile-armv9-cpu-microarchitectures-cortexx2-cortexa710-cortexa510</id>
        <link href="https://www.anandtech.com/show/16693/arm-announces-mobile-armv9-cpu-microarchitectures-cortexx2-cortexa710-cortexa510"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying monkey patches in Rails]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayushn21/applying-monkey-patches-in-rails-1bj1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayushn21/applying-monkey-patches-in-rails-1bj1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monkey patching is one of Ruby's most powerful features. It allows programmers to add methods to core classes which can result in some very elegant APIs. However it's quite easy to shoot yourself in the foot if you don't know what you're doing.  
This post from Justin Weiss is a brilliant guide on how to monkey patch responsibly. However he doesn't describe how to actually include your monkey patches in a Rails app, so that's what I'm going to describe in this post.  
Following Justin's advice, the implementation of all our monkey patches should go in the lib/core_extensions directory. So we might have some files like this:  
lib/core_extensions/array.rb
module CoreExtensions
  module Array
    def to_set
      Set.new(self)
    end
  end
end

lib/core_extensions/hash.rb
module CoreExtensi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayush Newatia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazing Specific Select File Using HTML CSS & JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikhil27b/amazing-specific-select-file-using-html-css-js-1366</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikhil27b/amazing-specific-select-file-using-html-css-js-1366"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I created a Amazing Specific with HTML & JS. I use JavaScript to select this file name and upload this file you can be use a post method after choose the file using axios or http I hope you like this also comments about your thoughts.
For more content follow me on Instagram  @developer_nikhil27.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Bobade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Button Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.buttoncheatsheet.com/</id>
        <link href="https://www.buttoncheatsheet.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Economist's excess deaths model]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/TheEconomist/covid-19-the-economist-global-excess-deaths-model</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/TheEconomist/covid-19-the-economist-global-excess-deaths-model"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WASM SYNTH, or, how music taught me the beauty of math]]></title>
        <id>https://timdaub.github.io/2020/02/19/wasm-synth/#f1</id>
        <link href="https://timdaub.github.io/2020/02/19/wasm-synth/#f1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jerikan: A configuration management system for network teams]]></title>
        <id>https://vincent.bernat.ch/en/blog/2021-network-jerikan-ansible</id>
        <link href="https://vincent.bernat.ch/en/blog/2021-network-jerikan-ansible"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data portability, the forgotten right of GDPR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alias.dev/report</id>
        <link href="https://www.alias.dev/report"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laws of Fun (2009)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/qZJBighPrnv9bSqTZ/31-laws-of-fun</id>
        <link href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/qZJBighPrnv9bSqTZ/31-laws-of-fun"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:06:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractional (YC W21) is hiring a product engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/fractional/jobs/YftyxZJ-product-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/fractional/jobs/YftyxZJ-product-engineer"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of Power Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6239</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-end-of-power-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-end-of-power-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The End Of Power explains why the old positions of power aren’t as powerful as they used to be due to recent changes in society and technology and how this shift has put more influence in the hands of everyday citizens like you and what it might mean for the future of our governments […]
The post The End Of Power Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immudb 1.0 – open-source, immutable database with SQL and verified timetravel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.codenotary.com/blog/immudb-release-1-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.codenotary.com/blog/immudb-release-1-0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T11:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google now lets you password-protect the page that shows all your searches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2021/5/24/22452122/google-my-activity-page-password-privacy-verification-web-and-app-history</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/5/24/22452122/google-my-activity-page-password-privacy-verification-web-and-app-history"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T11:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German regulator probes Google's market position, data use]]></title>
        <id>https://apnews.com/article/europe-technology-business-d7c3819420c7bb5221e7ed8cb8042520</id>
        <link href="https://apnews.com/article/europe-technology-business-d7c3819420c7bb5221e7ed8cb8042520"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T11:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCHQ’s mass data-sharing violated right to privacy, court rules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2021/may/25/gchqs-mass-data-sharing-violated-right-to-privacy-court-rules</id>
        <link href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2021/may/25/gchqs-mass-data-sharing-violated-right-to-privacy-court-rules"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T10:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The downfall of Malaysia’s biggest sugar daddy platform]]></title>
        <id>https://restofworld.org/2021/inside-the-downfall-of-sugarbook-malaysias-biggest-site-for-sex-work/</id>
        <link href="https://restofworld.org/2021/inside-the-downfall-of-sugarbook-malaysias-biggest-site-for-sex-work/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magit 3.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://emacsair.me/2021/05/25/magit-3.0/</id>
        <link href="https://emacsair.me/2021/05/25/magit-3.0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian seaside residents hit with bygone feudal tax]]></title>
        <id>https://www.smh.com.au/world/europe/it-s-absurd-italian-seaside-residents-hit-with-bygone-feudal-tax-20210525-p57uxi.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.smh.com.au/world/europe/it-s-absurd-italian-seaside-residents-hit-with-bygone-feudal-tax-20210525-p57uxi.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T07:32:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going Unconscious]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nybooks.com/articles/1995/04/20/going-unconscious/</id>
        <link href="https://www.nybooks.com/articles/1995/04/20/going-unconscious/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google is officially releasing Fuchsia OS, starting with a first-gen Nest Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/2021/05/25/google-releases-fuchsia-os-nest-hub/</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2021/05/25/google-releases-fuchsia-os-nest-hub/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T07:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use native context menus on Mac OS]]></title>
        <id>https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=34572</id>
        <link href="https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=34572"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T06:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: How to get started with audio programming?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27273706</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27273706"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T06:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ORBIS: The Stanford Geospatial Network Model of the Roman World]]></title>
        <id>https://orbis.stanford.edu/</id>
        <link href="https://orbis.stanford.edu/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T06:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bird Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://mitpress.mit.edu/blog/hidden-architecture-birds</id>
        <link href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/blog/hidden-architecture-birds"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T04:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drunk as a Lord: the Regency Bottle Men]]></title>
        <id>https://about1816.wordpress.com/2021/05/23/drunk-as-a-lord-the-regency-bottle-men/</id>
        <link href="https://about1816.wordpress.com/2021/05/23/drunk-as-a-lord-the-regency-bottle-men/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T04:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Node Environment Variables with a DotEnv File for Node.js and npm]]></title>
        <id>60abc6d011ffb70827ef630f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-node-environment-variables-with-a-dotenv-file-for-node-js-and-npm/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T00:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Environment variables are variables that are set outside of a program, often through a cloud provider or operating system.  In Node, environment variables are a great way to securely and conveniently configure things that don't change often, like URLs, authentication keys, and passwords. How to Create Environment VariablesEnvironment variables are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchhub: GitHub for Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.researchhub.com/about</id>
        <link href="https://www.researchhub.com/about"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T00:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Calm and Hack The Box – Nibbles]]></title>
        <id>60626dc29618b008528a9589</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keep-calm-and-hack-the-box-nibbles/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T00:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walkthrough for Hack The Box Nibbles machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340808</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-performance/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T22:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making GitHub’s new homepage fast and performant — Tobias Ahlin describes how the scrolling effects are done more performantly thanks to IntersectionObserver and the fact that it avoids the use of methods that trigger reflows, like getBoundingClientRect. Also, 
…
The post Links on Performance appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Small and Sustainable Habits to Get Your First Dev Job]]></title>
        <id>60aaba5911ffb70827ef5ffc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-small-sustainable-habits-to-get-your-first-dev-job/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T21:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving a big goal like transitioning into a new career can be extremely challenging and overwhelming. The amount of information isn't the problem. We have access to more information than we ever have. The problem is knowing how to effectively execute on the information available to us. The more I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Media Queries to Create Responsive Websites]]></title>
        <id>60ac07ec11ffb70827ef66e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-media-queries-to-create-responsive-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T20:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Media Queries allow you to create responsive websites that look good on all screen sizes, from desktop to mobile. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp channel that will teach you how to create CSS Media Queries. After learning the basics, you will learn how to use media]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Generate a Code Coverage Report with CodeCov and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>60aa161211ffb70827ef5f2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-generate-code-coverage-report-with-codecov-and-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software testing is an important part of the software development process. You run tests at different stages of the software development life cycle, and you'll want to make sure that you have good test coverage.  Here are some key reasons for writing software tests:  Testing prevents you from introducing breaking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[proxy-www]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341153</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/justjavac/proxy-www"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like a good trick. What if… a URL was…  a promise… that fetched said URL?
www.codepen.io.then((response) ={
  console.log(response);
});
That’s what @justjavac did with JavaScript Proxys. A clever trick, that. Don’t @ me about the practicality. Trick…
The post proxy-www appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RefinedC: Automating Foundational Verification of C Code with Refined Ownership]]></title>
        <id>https://plv.mpi-sws.org/refinedc/</id>
        <link href="https://plv.mpi-sws.org/refinedc/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T15:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discovering Goroutine Leaks with Semgrep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.trailofbits.com/post/discovering-goroutine-leaks-with-semgrep</id>
        <link href="https://www.trailofbits.com/post/discovering-goroutine-leaks-with-semgrep"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T15:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best No-Code Tools for Developers in 2021]]></title>
        <id>60a5248c906c5207e3a7e54b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-no-code-tools-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T14:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No-code tools let people across the world build different products and applications without writing code.   Before no-code tools, building simple websites or mobile applications took weeks or months and only experienced software developers could do it.  But that's not the case anymore. Now, you can spin up blogs, websites, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Thinking and Incentives: Lessons from Shakespeare]]></title>
        <id>https://fs.blog/2021/05/lessons-shakespeare/</id>
        <link href="https://fs.blog/2021/05/lessons-shakespeare/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T14:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Hanoi Rat Massacre of 1902 Did Not Go as Planned (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.atlasobscura.com/articles/hanoi-rat-massacre-1902.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.atlasobscura.com/articles/hanoi-rat-massacre-1902.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T14:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrangling Control Over PDFs with the Adobe PDF Embed API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340626</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wrangling-control-over-pdfs-with-the-adobe-pdf-embed-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T13:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By our last estimate, there are now more PDFs in the world than atoms in the universe (not verified by outside sources) so chances are, from time to time, you’re going to run into a PDF document or two. Browsers …
The post Wrangling Control Over PDFs with the Adobe PDF Embed API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raymond Camden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spark Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6238</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/spark-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=spark-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Spark teaches you how to become an influential, un-fireable asset to your team at work by taking on the role of a leader regardless of your position, utilizing the power of creative thinking to make better decisions, and learning how to be more self-aware and humble. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the […]
The post Spark Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 22nd 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19268</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/22/science-and-technology-links-may-22nd-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T15:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most computer chips today in flagship phones and computers use a process based on a 5 nm or larger resolution. Finer resolutions usually translate into lower energy usage and lower heat production. Given that many of our systems are limited by heat or power, finer resolutions lead to higher performance. The large Taiwanese chip maker … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 22nd 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340991</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/should-devtools-teach-the-css-cascade/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T23:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Judis, two days before I mouthed off about using (X, X, X, X) for talking about specificity, has a great blog post not only using that format, but advocating that browser DevTools should show us that value by …
The post Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Array Handbook – JS Array Methods Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6098ce302cd0545b5e944d0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, an array is a collection of elements or items. Arrays store data as elements and retrieve them back when you need them.  The array data structure is widely used in all programming languages that support it. In this handbook, I'll teach you all about arrays in JavaScript. You'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte for the Experienced React Dev]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340825</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svelte-for-the-experienced-react-dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is an accelerated introduction to Svelte from the point of view of someone with solid experience with React. I’ll provide a quick introduction, and then shift focus to things like state management and DOM interoperability, among other things. …
The post Svelte for the Experienced React Dev appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340919</id>
        <link href="https://csshell.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collection of common CSS mistakes, and how to fix them
From Stefánia Péter. 
Clever idea for a site! Some of them are little mind-twisters that could bite you, and some of them are honing in on best practices that …
The post CSS Hell appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Counting the number of matching characters in two ASCII strings]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19258</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/21/counting-the-number-of-matching-characters-in-two-ascii-strings/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose that you give me two ASCII strings having the same number of characters. I wish to compute efficiently the number of matching characters (same position, same character). E.g., the strings ‘012c’ and ‘021c’ have two matching characters (‘0’ and ‘c’). The conventional approach in C would look as follow: uint64_t standard_matching_bytes(char * c1, char … Continue reading Counting the number of matching characters in two ASCII strings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gift Of Fear Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6237</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-gift-of-fear-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-gift-of-fear-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T12:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Gift Of Fear is a guide to understanding how your fear and instincts about other people can protect you by showing you how to recognize and understand the warning signs that criminals and violent people exhibit before they strike. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Michael Cantrell is a police […]
The post The Gift Of Fear Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG) From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSON in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/json-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Neal tweeted a heck of a little CSS trick the other day, putting JSON inside CSS and plucking it out with JavaScript. Valid values for custom properties are quite liberal! So this looks for a CSS rule (e.g. a …
The post JSON in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340933</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/learn/css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ooo look at this mighty SEO flex from Google: Learn CSS! Well deserved — this is great content. Twenty-three chapters taking you through all the fundamentals of CSS with extra content, like relevant podcasts, interactive examples, and even quizzes to …
The post Learn CSS! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 11 Tutorial: Code a Project from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>60a6b3ab906c5207e3a7f5fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-11-tutorial-code-a-project-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T19:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is one of the most popular web frameworks. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create an Angular 11 project from scratch. It uses a public API to create a game database website. You will gain a great foundation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Modern C++ by Building an Audio Plugin]]></title>
        <id>60a694ab906c5207e3a7f544</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-modern-cpp-by-building-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of C++ courses teach you how to build toy projects with no real-world application. But it can often be more helpful to write programs people would actually use. We just released a 5-hour C++ course that will teach you how to write modern C++ code by building an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Version Control Using Git]]></title>
        <id>60a4b5c7906c5207e3a7e2bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-version-control-and-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn what version control is and how you can contribute to open-source projects using Git.  We'll get through the fundamentals of Git and I'll give you the knowledge that is indispensable for any web developer. What is Git?Git is a version control software which lets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340715</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/can-we-create-a-resize-hack-with-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow new developments in CSS, you’ve likely heard of the impending arrival of container queries. We’re going to look at the basics here, but if you’d like another look, check out Una’s “Next Gen CSS: @container” article. …
The post Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fit-content and fit-content()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340897</id>
        <link href="https://www.quirksmode.org/blog/archives/2021/04/fitcontent_and.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s some hardcore deep-dive CSS nerdery from PPK. If you can wrap your mind around min-content (the smallest an element can be based on the content it contains) and max-content (the largest the content of an element can push it) …
The post fit-content and fit-content() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Double Helix Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6236</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-double-helix-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-double-helix-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T12:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Double Helix tells the story of the discovery of DNA, which is one of the most significant scientific findings in all of history, by explaining the rivalries, struggles of the prideful scientific community to work together, and other roadblocks that James Watson had on the way to making the breakthrough of a lifetime […]
The post The Double Helix Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340731</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/notion-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Public Beta of the Notion API dropped! Woot! Here’s their guide. I’ve been a Notion user and fan for a long time, for both personal and professional team use. They even sponsored a few videos around here a …
The post Notion API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340692</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-loader-a-different-way-to-work-with-external-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVGs are awesome: they are small, look sharp on any scale, and can be customized without creating a separate file. However, there is something I feel is missing in web standards today: a way to include them as an external …
The post svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Think Again Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6235</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/think-again-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=think-again-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T12:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Think Again will make you more intelligent, persuasive, and self-aware by identifying the power of being humble about what you don’t know, how to recognize blind spots in your thinking before they start causing you problems, and what you can do to become more effective at convincing others of your way of thinking. Read […]
The post Think Again Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinned Audio WordPress Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340613</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pinned-audio-wordpress-theme/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m afraid I have to start this with a whole backstory, as the journey here is the point, not so much the theme.
A fella wrote to me a while back outlining a situation he was in. His company has …
The post Pinned Audio WordPress Theme appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Neon Text With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340420</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-neon-text-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neon text can add a nice, futuristic touch to any website. I’ve always loved the magic of neon signs, and wanted to recreate them using CSS. I thought I’d share some tips on how to do it! In this article, …
The post How to Create Neon Text With CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia O'Dwyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dark Net Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6234</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-dark-net-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-dark-net-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Dark Net dives into the details of the wildest and most dangerous parts of the digital world, including self-harmers, cryptocurrency programmers, computer scientists, hackers, extremists, pornographers, vigilantes, and much more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: The internet has completely revolutionized pretty much everything we do in today’s world. It […]
The post The Dark Net Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Converting binary integers to ASCII characters: Apple M1 vs AMD Zen2]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19250</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/17/converting-binary-integers-to-ascii-characters-apple-m1-vs-amd-zen2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Programmers often need to write integers as characters. Thus given the 32-bit value 1234, you might need a function that writes the characters 1234. We can use the fact that the ASCII numeral characters are in sequence in the ASCII table: ‘0’+0 is ‘0’, ‘0’+1 is ‘1’ and so forth. With this optimization in mind, … Continue reading Converting binary integers to ASCII characters: Apple M1 vs AMD Zen2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forgiving What You Can’t Forget Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6233</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/forgiving-what-you-cant-forget-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=forgiving-what-you-cant-forget-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Forgiving What You Can’t Forget teaches you how to heal from past traumas that still haunt you today by going through the lessons that author Lysa TerKeurst learned from childhood abuse and an unfaithful spouse, which have helped her find peace even in tough situations by forgiving those who have wronged her. Read in: […]
The post Forgiving What You Can’t Forget Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 15th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19244</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/15/science-and-technology-links-may-15th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were rainforests near the south pole 90 million years ago. Though commercial exchanges are typically win-win for both the buyer and the seller, people tend to view the buyer as more likely to be taken advantage of. People with low self-esteem are more likely to blame the political system for their personal problems. Moscona … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 15th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caste Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6232</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/caste-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=caste-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T12:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Caste unveils the hidden cultural and societal rules of our class system, including where it comes from, why it’s so deeply entrenched in society, and how we can dismantle it forever and finally allow all people to have the equality they deserve.  Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Imagine you inherited […]
The post Caste Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2030 Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6231</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/2030-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=2030-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T12:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: 2030 uses the current trajectory of the world, based on sociological, demographic, and technological trends, to outline the changes we can expect to happen in our lives by the beginning of the next decade. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: If you told someone in 2019 about everything that would happen […]
The post 2030 Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of Illness Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6230</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-end-of-illness-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-end-of-illness-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The End Of Illness will change the way that you think of sickness and health by identifying the problems with the current mindset around them and how focusing on the systems within your body instead of disease will help you make better-informed decisions that will keep you on the path of good health. Read […]
The post The End Of Illness Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constructing arrays of Boolean values in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19236</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/05/constructing-arrays-of-boolean-values-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not uncommon that we need to represent an array of Boolean (true or false) values. There are multiple ways to do it. The most natural way could be to construct an array of booleans (the native Java type). It is likely that when stored in an array, Java uses a byte per value. … Continue reading Constructing arrays of Boolean values in Java]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 1st 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19227</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/01/science-and-technology-links-may-1st-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-01T16:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing your own food could lower your carbon footprint by 3-5%. In recent years, we have acquired the ability to measure biological age: your chronological age does not necessarily match your biological since some people age faster. We measure biological aging with gene expression. Researchers found that an eight-week program of diet, exercise, and meditation … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 1st 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ideal divisors: when a division compiles down to just a multiplication]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19218</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/04/28/ideal-divisors-when-a-division-compiles-down-to-just-a-multiplication/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T16:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The division instruction is one of the most expensive instruction in your CPU. Thus optimizing compilers often compile divisions by known constants down to a multiplication followed by a shift. However, in some lucky cases, the compiler does not even need a shift. I call the corresponding divisors ideal. For the math. geeks, they are … Continue reading Ideal divisors: when a division compiles down to just a multiplication]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early — when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>