<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-05T01:38:49.775Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-05T01:38:49.775Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote Controlling a Nintendo Switch for Fun and Profit]]></title>
        <id>https://aricodes.net/posts/remote-controlling-a-nintendo-switch/</id>
        <link href="https://aricodes.net/posts/remote-controlling-a-nintendo-switch/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-05T00:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to lazy-load images? The easiest way to lazy-load images on your website! 🖼]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hasnaindev/how-to-lazy-load-images-the-easiest-way-to-lazy-load-images-on-your-website-249</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hasnaindev/how-to-lazy-load-images-the-easiest-way-to-lazy-load-images-on-your-website-249"/>
        <updated>2021-06-05T00:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lazy-loading is the simple process of loading resources only when they are needed. These resources can be anything, from images to stylesheets, fonts, scripts, iframes etc.
We're going to use the package called, "Lozad." To lazy-load images. Lozad. will only add 1 KB to your production 📦! Check out Bundlephobia  😱 for more info.
We're only going to lazy-load images but Lozad can handle lazy-loading for srcsets, background images, videos and iframes too. So, let's include the package and start hacking! 🪓
npm i lozad

Include Lozad in your entry or main JavaScript file. Alternatively, you could use Lozad CDN if you don't have module bundler set up.
import lozad from 'lozad';

// Make sure to run the library only when all DOM elements are available.
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', () => {
   /**
   * This is all you need to do!
   * Check the link for advanced usages.
   * https://www.npmjs.com/package/lozad
   */
   lozad().observe();
});

By default, Lozad will look for images with class, "lozad," and the attribute of "data-src". When the image is about to enter the viewport, Lozad takes the data-src attribute and assigns it to to the src attribute to load the image.
<img class="lozad" data-src="https://example.com/img.jpg" />

That's it, you've successfully added support for lazy-loading 🎉🧨🎊!
Best practice would be to leave the images that are in the header and lazy-load only the ones that are below the initial viewport.
Use Lozad to lazy-load a background image and video!
Please, share your thoughts and experiences as to how lazy-loading improved your website. PS, are you guys interested in me writing about lazy-loading using vanilla JavaScript? Let me know in the comments, thank you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Hasnain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roadmap to aerospace jobs: How to become an aerospace programmer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/educative/roadmap-to-aerospace-jobs-how-to-become-an-aerospace-programmer-g3i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/educative/roadmap-to-aerospace-jobs-how-to-become-an-aerospace-programmer-g3i"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T23:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working in the aerospace industry is a dream for many engineers. Aerospace is an exciting and innovative field that's making important advances in the designing and building of machines of the future. The field expands beyond just space and rockets. As a programmer in the aerospace industry, you have the opportunity to work on challenging problems that are important to national defense, society, economics, and much more.
Today, we’ll introduce you to the role of aerospace programming and discuss how to get started in the industry.
We’ll cover:
What is an aerospace programmer?


What types of roles are available?


Why work in aerospace?


Aerospace programmer salaries


How to become an aerospace programmer


3 aerospace interview questions to practice






Aerospace is an interdisciplina…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Schaffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TCL-22 Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/the-collab-lab/tcl-22-recap-211m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/the-collab-lab/tcl-22-recap-211m"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T23:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Combining the collective minds of some very talented and enthusiastic individuals with a fascination for avocados and mochi ice cream, TCL-22 set out on a quest to create a fun and engaging shopping list app, aptly titled AvoCart!

Built with React, Material UI, Styled Components, and Firebase, AvoCart was an effective use case for both the team to understand how effective communication can create less friction and allow for more creativity and a greater developer experience in group projects. 
As a user, you will enter items (e.g., “Greek yogurt” or “Paper towels”) into your list. Each time you buy the item, you mark it as purchased in the list. Over time, the app comes to understand the intervals at which you buy different items. If an item is likely to be due to be bought soon, it rises…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Augusto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Journey To Full Stack Web Development From My Side Of The World Teaching Myself.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sopulu_ngene/my-journey-to-full-stack-web-development-from-my-side-of-the-world-teaching-myself-8p9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sopulu_ngene/my-journey-to-full-stack-web-development-from-my-side-of-the-world-teaching-myself-8p9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T23:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a heck of a journey getting into the Web development Industry.
I have been unstable in my learning of Web Development. I started in 2018 but I took off seriously early this year. I have had a bunch of challenges but what some people call luck and I call Divine assistance has been present. From the issue of power supply shortage down to the unavailability of data this has all been a hinderance. My country is still a developing country and its Ecosystem isn't conducive for newbies in Tech or programming. Majority of the people trying to get into the tech industry In Nigeria are either hindered by the high cost of computers and other gadgets, Data unavailability or Power supply shortage. 
Sometimes we do pray for help to come from distant lands. But I was Graced to have reached the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martins Ngene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Breached Colonial Pipeline Using Compromised Password]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-04/hackers-breached-colonial-pipeline-using-compromised-password</id>
        <link href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-04/hackers-breached-colonial-pipeline-using-compromised-password"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T22:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The danger of oversimplification]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jmau111/the-danger-of-oversimplification-c14</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jmau111/the-danger-of-oversimplification-c14"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T22:46:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oversimplification can lead to terrible outcomes and confusions for the web.
Ux means user experience. The Ux designer's job is to bring awesome and meaningful experiences to users.
It does not mean everything must be simplistic and trivial.
Of course, Ux and intuitiveness are not enemies at all. They are not mutually exclusive, but they are not exactly the same idea. That's why I did not say "Ux vs. intuitiveness". While intuitiveness is essential, it should not be the ultimate goal at all costs.
Let's take a concrete example. A member of my family bought a brand new car recently. It has an automatic transmission. It's supposed to be way more accessible than a manual transmission, but it requires an adaptation period in reality.
At the beginning, the person was completely lost and even an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Maury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zig 0.8.0 Release Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://ziglang.org/download/0.8.0/release-notes.html</id>
        <link href="https://ziglang.org/download/0.8.0/release-notes.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T22:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Reliance on Stablecoins Harks Back to the Wild West of Finance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/articles/bitcoins-reliance-on-stablecoins-harks-back-to-the-wild-west-of-finance-11622115246</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/bitcoins-reliance-on-stablecoins-harks-back-to-the-wild-west-of-finance-11622115246"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T22:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOWTO: Be more productive (2005)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.aaronsw.com/weblog/productivity</id>
        <link href="http://www.aaronsw.com/weblog/productivity"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T22:18:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Websites to Practice Your Frontend Development Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codewell/7-websites-to-practice-your-frontend-development-skills-54de</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codewell/7-websites-to-practice-your-frontend-development-skills-54de"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T22:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building projects and solving real world problems is inarguably one of the best ways you can learn how to code. Theoretical is all good, but without applying the knowledge you learn, you will most likely not progress. We've made a list of 7 websites that can help you get better at frontend development through practice.
Table of Content:



 freeCodeCamp
Codewell
CSSBattle
Treehouse
Coderbyte
CodePen Challenges
7- Javascript30
1. freeCodeCamp



Inarguably one of the best resources to learn web development. Over 7000+ tutorials and tons of challenges to complete along the way to test what you've learnt. 
The tracks are straightforward and the best part? It's all free. 
2. Codewell



If you want to level up your HTML, CSS, and Javascript skills, Codewell offers real world Figma templates th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moemin Mamdouh 👨‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lol just got kicked out of  @ycombinator]]></title>
        <id>https://twitter.com/paulbiggar/status/1400904600421535744</id>
        <link href="https://twitter.com/paulbiggar/status/1400904600421535744"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T22:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make a chrome extension with javascript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ivavay/how-to-make-a-chrome-extension-with-javascript-5157</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ivavay/how-to-make-a-chrome-extension-with-javascript-5157"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T21:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[✨ What you'll be making
✨ First things first: HTML
  <body>
    <div class = "container">
        <div id = "chengyu">
            <h1></h1>
        </div> 
        <div id = "pingyin">
            <h3></h3>
        </div>
        <div id = "definition">
            <h2></h2>
        </div>
    </div>
  </body>  

Remember to link the script.js file and data.json in which you'll create later. 
✨ Style it to your taste: CSS
body {
    color: white;
    font-size: 40px;
    overflow: hidden; /* Hide scrollbars */
    -webkit-animation: fadein 2s; /* Safari, Chrome and Opera > 12.1 */
}

Then you'll need to add these lines in the css as well for the animation to take effect.
@keyframes fadein {
    from { opacity: 0; }
    to   { opacity: 1; }
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadein {
    from { opacity:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivy Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Carmack on JPEG]]></title>
        <id>https://twitter.com/ID_AA_Carmack/status/1400930510671601666</id>
        <link href="https://twitter.com/ID_AA_Carmack/status/1400930510671601666"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T21:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Search and Filter Components in React]]></title>
        <id>60b3480c11ffb70827ef9a88</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/search-and-filter-component-in-reactjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T21:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building a React app, you want your users to be able to search and get exact results. And if you are getting tons of items from an API, then you need to create a way for users to be able to find various items easily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Denmark parliament approves giant artificial island off Copenhagen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-57348415</id>
        <link href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-57348415"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T21:27:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Pair Programming Should Be Part of Every Team Dynamic]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/keraito/why-pair-programming-should-be-part-of-every-team-dynamic-240j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/keraito/why-pair-programming-should-be-part-of-every-team-dynamic-240j"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T21:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only when I started a new job earlier this year did I discover the concept of pair programming in an engineering team and since then I have become quite fond of it. I really like the interactions that it creates between team members and working together on a certain task. Having experienced a team where pair programming was not a thing and a team where it was, I can definitely say that there are a lot of benefits to pair programming and it can greatly contribute towards a team. In this article, I will go over what pair programming can do for your team and why your team should also adopt it.
No two developers are alike. Every developer has their own way plan of approaching a task, works differently, does things in another way, has different nuggets of information, and so on. This means that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chak Shun Yu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8088ify: Intel 8080 CP/M 2.2 to Intel 8086/8088 IBM PC DOS assembly translator]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ibara/8088ify</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ibara/8088ify"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T21:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clerky (YC S11) Is Hiring Senior Software Engineers (Remote)]]></title>
        <id>https://jobs.lever.co/clerky/295375d9-c3d9-4ec8-99e0-bc5ac6232a64?lever-origin=applied&amp;lever-source%5B%5D=HN</id>
        <link href="https://jobs.lever.co/clerky/295375d9-c3d9-4ec8-99e0-bc5ac6232a64?lever-origin=applied&amp;lever-source%5B%5D=HN"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T21:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning in Python – The Top New Scikit-Learn 0.24 Features You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>60ba33d7acb62507dd1d9050</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-python-new-scikit-learn-features-you-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scikit-learn is one of the most popular open-source and free machine learning libraries for Python.  The scikit-learn library contains a lot of efficient tools for machine learning and statistical modeling including classification, regression, clustering, and dimensionality reduction. Many data scientists, machine learning engineers, and researchers rely on this library for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyCon US 2021 Recordings are Available]]></title>
        <id>https://pycon.blogspot.com/2021/06/pycon-us-2021-recordings-are-complete.html?m=1</id>
        <link href="https://pycon.blogspot.com/2021/06/pycon-us-2021-recordings-are-complete.html?m=1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin Coroutines and Swift, revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/touchlab/kotlin-coroutines-and-swift-revisited-j5h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/touchlab/kotlin-coroutines-and-swift-revisited-j5h"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I wrote about a pattern for interop between Kotlin coroutines and RxSwift. I appreciate the attention it received, particularly where people have applied it to other reactive frameworks, and even including a code-generation plugin using the same ideas. I figure it's about time I talk about my own updated thinking on these patterns.
If you haven't read the previous article, I suggest going through that first for context.
We'll stick to the same repository class as the original article, and walk through exposing it to iOS.
class ThingRepository {
    suspend fun getThing(succeed: Boolean): Thing {
        delay(100)
        if (succeed) {
            return Thing(0)
        } else {
            error("oh no!")
        }
    }

    fun getThingStream(
        count: Int,
        suc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russell Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Automation with Python + Discord Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sayf_a_cc723da8bec754a8cd/network-automation-with-python-discord-webhooks-h36</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sayf_a_cc723da8bec754a8cd/network-automation-with-python-discord-webhooks-h36"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are we gonna Make?


In this epic tutorial we are going to be using discord webhooks and the power of python to receive notifications for when a device on our local network (at home) goes offline.
its a cool project 
it uses the power of python and discord!
A tutorial for those wanting to flex your muscle on python and logic building. 
Let's Roll!





  
  
  Phase I - The Plan


This project is going to fully depend on logic since we are embarking on coding something that's totally hybrid, but hey!...who cares? Below you'll find the flow chart of\n how this algorithm will flow.

from discord_webhook import DiscordEmbed, DiscordWebhook 
from datetime import datetime 
import subprocess
import time 
import io 

Let's start off by preparing a function that when called upon sends a disco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sayf A</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover from Deployment Hell – What I Learned After My Discord Bot Crashed on a 1000+ User Server]]></title>
        <id>60b8f5c7acb62507dd1d8500</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recovering-from-deployment-hell-what-i-learned-from-deploying-my-discord-bot-to-a-1000-user-server/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I deployed a Discord bot to a 1000+ user server. In the first hour, Deployment Hell struck and my bot crashed. In the next hour, I brought it back, surviving and even thriving in Deployment Hell. In this post, I'll show you how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing Push Notifications With Flutter and OneSignal-Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lordlamee/implementing-push-notifications-with-flutter-and-onesignal-part-1-3690</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lordlamee/implementing-push-notifications-with-flutter-and-onesignal-part-1-3690"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover Photo by Jamie Street on Unsplash
Your users are definitely not going to be on your app for 24 hours every day. However, you might want to remind them to check your app, or notify them of new things happening in your app even when it's closed. You use Push Notifications to achieve this. And contrary to popular belief, they're really easy to implement with Flutter and OneSignal.
A OneSignal Account
Setup your firebase project
https://firebase.google.com to get started.

On the next page, you could choose to enable or disable analytics. Your project should take a few seconds to be created depending on your internet connection
Setup your flutter project.
create flutter project
flutter create push_notifications_demo in your command line interface(command prompt).
add your app to the fire…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olamide Gabriel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Principles for user-centered front-end development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341793</id>
        <link href="https://colinoakley.medium.com/the-web-we-choose-to-build-e921510e3f1b"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colin Oakley:
• Accessible — Use semantic HTML, and make sure we meet the WCAG 2.1 AA standard as a minimum and it works with assisted technologies (this sits alongside the DWP Accessibility Manual)
• Agnostic — Build 
…
The post Principles for user-centered front-end development appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not a drill: VMware vuln with 9.8 severity rating is under attack]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/06/under-exploit-vmware-vulnerability-with-severity-rating-of-9-8-out-of-10/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/06/under-exploit-vmware-vulnerability-with-severity-rating-of-9-8-out-of-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to keep all constants in Flutter?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zhangrui/how-to-keep-all-constants-in-flutter-9fj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zhangrui/how-to-keep-all-constants-in-flutter-9fj"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clean and simple way to keep constants in Flutter is to make an own Dart library in the project for the constants.
For example, we have a project structure like this.

constats.dart
const String BUTTON_LABEL = 'Submit';

The const keyword is used to represent a compile-time constant. Variables declared with const keyword are implicitly final. Link
You can then use import statement to access to the constants:
import 'package:<project_name>/assets/constants.dart' as constants;
...
ElevatedButton(
  child: const Text(constants.BUTTON_LABEL),
)
...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rui.Z</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elijah Miller’s NEC v30 on a Pi hat]]></title>
        <id>https://virtuallyfun.com/wordpress/2021/06/04/elijah-millers-nec-v30-on-a-pi-hat/</id>
        <link href="https://virtuallyfun.com/wordpress/2021/06/04/elijah-millers-nec-v30-on-a-pi-hat/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T19:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pokegb: A gameboy emulator that only plays Pokémon Blue, in 68 lines of C++]]></title>
        <id>https://binji.github.io/posts/pokegb/</id>
        <link href="https://binji.github.io/posts/pokegb/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T18:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultra-processed food targets bone quality via endochondral ossification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41413-020-00127-9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41413-020-00127-9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T18:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel and AMD Contemplate Different Replacements for x86 Interrupt Handling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eejournal.com/article/we-interrupt-this-program/</id>
        <link href="https://www.eejournal.com/article/we-interrupt-this-program/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T18:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heroic Rat Retiring from Detecting Land Mines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/04/1003258540/after-years-of-detecting-land-mines-a-heroic-rat-is-hanging-up-his-sniffer</id>
        <link href="https://www.npr.org/2021/06/04/1003258540/after-years-of-detecting-land-mines-a-heroic-rat-is-hanging-up-his-sniffer"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T18:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn TypeScript Basics in this Beginner&#x27;s Guide]]></title>
        <id>60b2a4c611ffb70827ef9842</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-typescript-basics/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript has taken the development world by storm. No wonder it has over 15 million weekly downloads on npm. But what is TypeScript, and what do you need to know about it?  In this article, I am going answer those questions. By the end you'll have a grasp of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anatomy of a Linux DNS Lookup]]></title>
        <id>https://zwischenzugs.com/2018/06/08/anatomy-of-a-linux-dns-lookup-part-i/</id>
        <link href="https://zwischenzugs.com/2018/06/08/anatomy-of-a-linux-dns-lookup-part-i/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T17:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social virtual spaces with Elixir at Mozilla]]></title>
        <id>https://elixir-lang.org/blog/2021/06/02/social-virtual-spaces-with-elixir-at-mozilla/</id>
        <link href="https://elixir-lang.org/blog/2021/06/02/social-virtual-spaces-with-elixir-at-mozilla/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T17:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There are no results for tank man]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bing.com/images/search?q=tank+man</id>
        <link href="https://www.bing.com/images/search?q=tank+man"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haiku Monthly Activity Report – May 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.haiku-os.org/blog/pulkomandy/2021-06-03-haiku_activity_report_may_2021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.haiku-os.org/blog/pulkomandy/2021-06-03-haiku_activity_report_may_2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T16:43:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: InBalance (YC W21) – Short-term energy market forecasting]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27395238</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27395238"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T16:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why We Should End the Data Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://thereboot.com/why-we-should-end-the-data-economy/</id>
        <link href="https://thereboot.com/why-we-should-end-the-data-economy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T16:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a LLVM Micro C compiler in Haskell]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.josephmorag.com/posts/mcc0/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.josephmorag.com/posts/mcc0/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T15:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I :has()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341968</id>
        <link href="https://bkardell.com/blog/canihas.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T14:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just joked that we’re basically getting everything we want in CSS super fast (mostly referring to container queries, my gosh, can you imagine they are actually coming?). Now we might actually get parent selectors?! As in .parent:has(.child) { …
The post Can I :has() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neural Actor: Neural Free-View Synthesis of Human Actors with Pose Control]]></title>
        <id>http://gvv.mpi-inf.mpg.de/projects/NeuralActor/</id>
        <link href="http://gvv.mpi-inf.mpg.de/projects/NeuralActor/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T12:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greenlights Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6379</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/greenlights-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=greenlights-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Greenlights is the fascinating autobiography of Matthew McConaughey in which he takes us on a wild ride of his journey through a childhood of tough love, rising to fame and success in Hollywood, shifting his career, and more, guided by the green lights he saw that led him forward at each step. Read in: […]
The post Greenlights Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK and EU launch antitrust probes into Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ft.com/content/1836b3a0-cf7b-4dd1-9821-85f209e15667</id>
        <link href="https://www.ft.com/content/1836b3a0-cf7b-4dd1-9821-85f209e15667"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T11:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Unbelievable Demo]]></title>
        <id>https://brendangregg.com/blog/2021-06-04/an-unbelievable-demo.html</id>
        <link href="https://brendangregg.com/blog/2021-06-04/an-unbelievable-demo.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T04:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python for Bioinformatics: Use Machine Learning and Data Analysis for Drug Discovery]]></title>
        <id>60b98ebfacb62507dd1d8ec4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-for-bioinformatics-use-machine-learning-and-data-analysis-for-drug-discovery/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T02:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for a way to apply Python and machine learning to a real-world application? You should consider Bioinformatics. Bioinformatics is an interdisciplinary field that develops methods and software tools for understanding biological data, in particular when the data sets are large and complex. We just released a course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Van Buren is a victory against overbroad interpretations of the CFAA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/06/van-buren-victory-against-overbroad-interpretations-cfaa-protects-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/06/van-buren-victory-against-overbroad-interpretations-cfaa-protects-security"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T01:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ebullism at 1M Feet: Surviving Rapid/Explosive Decompression (2000)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.geoffreylandis.com/ebullism.html</id>
        <link href="http://www.geoffreylandis.com/ebullism.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T23:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Tutorial – How to Set Up a Front End Development Project]]></title>
        <id>60b11ff811ffb70827ef8f94</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-front-end-development-project/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T21:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say you plan to build a website. Before you start, you want to set up a few tools to make your life easier. But which tools should you have? The JavaScript ecosystem is changing so fast that it can be overwhelming to pick the best tools to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19312</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/03/computing-the-number-of-digits-of-an-integer-even-faster/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I my previous blog post, I documented how one might proceed to compute the number of digits of an integer quickly. E.g., given the integer 999, you want 3 but given the integer 1000, you want 4. It is effectively the integer logarithm in base 10. On computers, you can quickly compute the integer logarithm … Continue reading Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schofield&#x27;s Laws of Computing – What they Are and Why You Should Know Them]]></title>
        <id>60afd68611ffb70827ef86d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/schofields-laws-of-computing/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Schofield's Laws of Computing are principles that anyone who works with computers should know. They're focused on data portability, integrity, and security.  Jack Schofield was a prolific journalist who wrote for The Guardian and covered technology for nearly four decades. During that time, he wrote three particular articles called "Schofield's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lists in Python – A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>60b7c02cacb62507dd1d7b80</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lists-in-python-comprehensive-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s suppose you’re planning to visit your neighborhood store to stock up on essentials. What is the first thing you’d do?  Have the answer already? Yes, you'd probably write down a shopping list! Python also has a built-in data structure called List that’s very similar to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Hackintosh - Install MacOS Big Sur on a PC Using OpenCore]]></title>
        <id>60affbe411ffb70827ef8951</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-hackintosh/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Hackintosh is a non-Mac computer system, made with PC parts, that runs the macOS operating system. In this tutorial, you will learn how to create a Hackintosh. You will learn how to install macOS Big Sur (or any other version of macOS) using OpenCore. The main benefit of a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless vs Fully Managed Services: What&#x27;s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>60aa708711ffb70827ef5f4b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-fully-managed-service-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're new to cloud technologies, you might be confused about the difference between serverless technologies and managed services.  So in this article you'll learn what these terms mean and what the main differences are.    What Are Managed Services? A managed service let the end-user focus on using a service]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexagons and Beyond: Flexible, Responsive Grid Patterns, Sans Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341584</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/hexagons-and-beyond-flexible-responsive-grid-patterns-sans-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little while back, Chris shared this nice hexagonal grid. And true to its name, it’s using —wait for it — CSS Grid to form that layout. It’s a neat trick! Combining grid columns, grid gaps, and creative clipping …
The post Hexagons and Beyond: Flexible, Responsive Grid Patterns, Sans Media Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Lighthouse Scores and Core Web Vitals with DebugBear]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341494</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/monitoring-lighthouse-scores-and-core-web-vitals-with-debugbear/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DebugBear takes just a few seconds to start using. You literally point it at a URL you want to watch, and it’ll start watching it. You install nothing.
It’ll start running tests, and you’ve immediately got performance charts you can …
The post Monitoring Lighthouse Scores and Core Web Vitals with DebugBear appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Rules Rules Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6372</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/no-rules-rules-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=no-rules-rules-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T12:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: No Rules Rules explains the incredibly unique and efficient company culture of Netflix, including the amazing levels of freedom and responsibility it gives employees and how this innovative way of running the business is the very reason that Netflix is so successful. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: When Netflix started […]
The post No Rules Rules Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Booster with System.IO.Pipelines in C#]]></title>
        <id>https://goldytech.wordpress.com/2021/05/31/performance-booster-with-system-io-pipelines-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://goldytech.wordpress.com/2021/05/31/performance-booster-with-system-io-pipelines-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T11:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging iOS Safari]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341724</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/debugging-ios-safari/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do I debug Safari on iOS?
These are my general steps, starting with not even using iOS Safari.
1. Is this just a small-screen problem?
Lemme just use the device mode in Chrome quick.
Note that this does a …
The post Debugging iOS Safari appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Crash Course in WordPress Block Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341442</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-crash-course-in-wordpress-block-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blocks in WordPress are great. Drop some into the page, arrange them how you like, and you’ve got a pretty sweet landing page with little effort. But what if the default blocks in WordPress need a little tweaking? Like, what …
The post A Crash Course in WordPress Block Filters appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Mayorov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Custom Properties a “Menu of What Will Change”?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341572</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/are-custom-properties-a-menu-of-what-will-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PPK laid out an interesting situation in “Two options for using custom properties” where he and Stefan Judis had two different approaches for doing the same thing with custom properties. In one approach, hover and focus styles for a …
The post Are Custom Properties a “Menu of What Will Change”? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Standard Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6370</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-bitcoin-standard-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-bitcoin-standard-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Bitcoin Standard uses the history of money and gold to explain why Bitcoin is the way to go if the world wants to stick to having sound money and why it’s the only cryptocurrency to be focusing on right now. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Have you ever thought […]
The post The Bitcoin Standard Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code blocks, but better]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341720</id>
        <link href="https://ped.ro/blog/code-blocks-but-better"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T22:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pedro Duarte made a wishlist for styled code blocks in blog posts and documentation, then hand-rolls a perfect solution for that wishlist. For example, a feature to be able to highlight certain lines or words within the code block. The …
The post Code blocks, but better appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Front-End Testing is For Everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341342</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/front-end-testing-is-for-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing is one of those things that you either get super excited about or kinda close your eyes and walk away. Whichever camp you fall into, I’m here to tell you that front-end testing is for everyone. In fact, …
The post Front-End Testing is For Everyone appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgeny Klimenchenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jetpack Boost Handles Critical CSS For You]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341296</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jetpack-boost-handles-critical-css-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Critical CSS is one of those things I see in my performance reports but always seem to ignore. I know what it means. It means to put only the CSS required to render things immediately visible in a <style>…
The post Jetpack Boost Handles Critical CSS For You appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Design Of Everyday Things Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6244</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-design-of-everyday-things-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-design-of-everyday-things-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Design Of Everyday Things helps you understand why your inability to use some products isn’t your fault but instead is the result of bad design and how companies can use the principles of cognitive psychology to implement better design principles that actually solve your problems without creating more of them. Read in: 4 […]
The post The Design Of Everyday Things Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Functions: The Secret to Ultra-Productive Front-End Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340465</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/serverless-functions-the-secret-to-ultra-productive-front-end-teams/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T17:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern apps place high demands on front-end developers. Web apps require complex functionality, and the lion’s share of that work is falling to front-end devs:
building modern, accessible user interfaces
creating interactive elements and complex animations
managing complex application state
…
The post Serverless Functions: The Secret to Ultra-Productive Front-End Teams appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Lengstorf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local: Always Getting Better]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341482</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/local-always-getting-better/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T17:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been using Local for ages. Four years ago, I wrote about how I got all my WordPress sites running locally on it. I just wanted to give it another high five because it’s still here and still great. In …
The post Local: Always Getting Better appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Drama Of The Gifted Child Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6243</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-drama-of-the-gifted-child-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-drama-of-the-gifted-child-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T12:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Drama Of The Gifted Child is an international bestseller that will help you unearth your sad, suppressed memories from childhood that still haunt you today and teach you how to confront them so you can avoid passing them on to your children, release yourself from the pains of your past, and finally be […]
The post The Drama Of The Gifted Child Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing the number of digits of an integer quickly]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19288</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/28/computing-the-number-of-digits-of-an-integer-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T19:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose I give you an integer. How many decimal digits would you need to write it out? The number ‘100’ takes 3 digits whereas the number ’99’ requires only two. You are effectively trying to compute the integer logarithm in base 10 of the number. I say ‘integer logarithm’ because you need to round up … Continue reading Computing the number of digits of an integer quickly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Favicons for WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341163</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/dynamic-favicons-for-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T14:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typically, a single favicon is used across a whole domain. But there are times you wanna step it up with different favicons depending on context. A website might change the favicon to match the content being viewed. Or a site …
The post Dynamic Favicons for WordPress appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Park</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Hundred Souls Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6242</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/four-hundred-souls-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=four-hundred-souls-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Four Hundred Souls tells the history of African Americans from the perspective of 90 authors who share insights on 400 years of conflict, oppression, and faith that with all the hard work of those fighting for equality, things would get better someday. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Most American students can […]
The post Four Hundred Souls Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To $ or Not to $: Displaying Terminal Code Snippets]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341298</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/to-or-not-to-displaying-terminal-code-snippets/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T18:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s very popular to put a $ on lines that are intended to be a command in code documentation that involves the terminal (i.e. the command line).
Like this:
$ brew install somepackage
The point of that is that it …
The post To $ or Not to $: Displaying Terminal Code Snippets appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Show Images on Click]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341020</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-show-images-on-click/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most images on the web are superfluous. If I might be a jerk for a bit, 99% of them aren’t even that helpful at all (although there are rare exceptions). That’s because images don’t often complement the text they’re …
The post How to Show Images on Click appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Emperor Of All Maladies Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6241</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-emperor-of-all-maladies-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-emperor-of-all-maladies-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T12:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Emperor Of All Maladies details the beginnings and progress in our understanding of cancer, including how we first started learning about it, began developing ways to treat it and discovered ways to prevent it, and the biological effect that it has on us. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Virtually […]
The post The Emperor Of All Maladies Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Powerful Responsive Websites With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19274</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/26/all-models-are-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T19:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong, but some are useful is a common saying in statistics. It does not merely apply to statistics, however. It is general observation. Box (1976) wrote an  influential article on the topic. He says that you make progress by successively making models followed by experiments, followed by more models, and then more … Continue reading All models are wrong]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptoassets Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6240</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/cryptoassets-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cryptoassets-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T12:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Cryptoassets is your guide to understanding this revolutionary new digital asset class and explains the history of Bitcoin, how to invest in it and other cryptocurrencies, and how the blockchain technology behind it all works. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Have you ever heard of Bitcoin? Of course, you have; […]
The post Cryptoassets Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of Power Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6239</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-end-of-power-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-end-of-power-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The End Of Power explains why the old positions of power aren’t as powerful as they used to be due to recent changes in society and technology and how this shift has put more influence in the hands of everyday citizens like you and what it might mean for the future of our governments […]
The post The End Of Power Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spark Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6238</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/spark-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=spark-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Spark teaches you how to become an influential, un-fireable asset to your team at work by taking on the role of a leader regardless of your position, utilizing the power of creative thinking to make better decisions, and learning how to be more self-aware and humble. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the […]
The post Spark Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 22nd 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19268</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/22/science-and-technology-links-may-22nd-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T15:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most computer chips today in flagship phones and computers use a process based on a 5 nm or larger resolution. Finer resolutions usually translate into lower energy usage and lower heat production. Given that many of our systems are limited by heat or power, finer resolutions lead to higher performance. The large Taiwanese chip maker … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 22nd 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Counting the number of matching characters in two ASCII strings]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19258</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/21/counting-the-number-of-matching-characters-in-two-ascii-strings/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose that you give me two ASCII strings having the same number of characters. I wish to compute efficiently the number of matching characters (same position, same character). E.g., the strings ‘012c’ and ‘021c’ have two matching characters (‘0’ and ‘c’). The conventional approach in C would look as follow: uint64_t standard_matching_bytes(char * c1, char … Continue reading Counting the number of matching characters in two ASCII strings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Converting binary integers to ASCII characters: Apple M1 vs AMD Zen2]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19250</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/17/converting-binary-integers-to-ascii-characters-apple-m1-vs-amd-zen2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Programmers often need to write integers as characters. Thus given the 32-bit value 1234, you might need a function that writes the characters 1234. We can use the fact that the ASCII numeral characters are in sequence in the ASCII table: ‘0’+0 is ‘0’, ‘0’+1 is ‘1’ and so forth. With this optimization in mind, … Continue reading Converting binary integers to ASCII characters: Apple M1 vs AMD Zen2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 15th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19244</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/15/science-and-technology-links-may-15th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were rainforests near the south pole 90 million years ago. Though commercial exchanges are typically win-win for both the buyer and the seller, people tend to view the buyer as more likely to be taken advantage of. People with low self-esteem are more likely to blame the political system for their personal problems. Moscona … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 15th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>