<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-03T01:02:57.560Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-03T01:02:57.560Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Switched to Mattermost]]></title>
        <id>https://netfoundry.io/why-we-switched-to-mattermost/</id>
        <link href="https://netfoundry.io/why-we-switched-to-mattermost/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T23:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Opinión] El problema del liderazgo en los equipos de tecnología.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jresendiz27/opinion-el-problema-del-liderazgo-en-los-equipos-de-tecnologia-3m6p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jresendiz27/opinion-el-problema-del-liderazgo-en-los-equipos-de-tecnologia-3m6p"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T23:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Esto es mi opinión, la comparto y espero poder generar conciencia y un poco de debate sano; con la finalidad de mejorar o bien, comenzar con el camino de un liderazgo integral en la industria de tecnología.
Conforme pasan los años y uno va creciendo en TI (hablando específicamente en la industria del Software) te das cuenta de las fuertes deficiencias en educación emocional, comunicación y resolución de conflictos que existen en la industria.
Desafortunadamente es algo de lo que pecamos muchos en el área, nuestro egoísmo y gatekeeping nos impiden buscar un crecimiento organizacional íntegro y orgánico sin tener que aspirar siempre a ser el mejor en todo.
Estos problemas permean mucho más allá cuando contamos con posiciones de liderazgo y nos deja con una gran deficiencia al intentar ser lí…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan A. Reséndiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Helpful OS Module Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/6-helpful-os-module-methods-5e3k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/6-helpful-os-module-methods-5e3k"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T23:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
Aya Bouchiha,
6 useful os module methods.
getcwd(): this method helps you to get the absolute path of the current working directory as a string.
import os

print(os.getcwd())
# C:\Users\AyaBouchiha\Desktop\posts

mkdir(): lets you create a new directory if it does not exists, else it raises an error (FileExistsError)
import os

os.mkdir('python') # done :)

os.mkdir('python') # error (FileExistsError)

rmdir(): helps you to remove an empty directory.
import os

# done
os.mkdir('python/newFolder')  

# done
os.rmdir('python/newFolder')  

# error (FileNotFoundError)
os.rmdir('something/does-not-exists') 

# error (NotADirectoryError)
os.rmdir('user.json') 

remove(): lets you delete a file. If it does not exists, this method raises an error.
import os

# done
os.remove('posts/python/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Bouchiha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catalytic converter thefts in California: Why they are everywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.latimes.com/california/newsletter/2021-08-02/catalytic-converter-theft-essential-california</id>
        <link href="https://www.latimes.com/california/newsletter/2021-08-02/catalytic-converter-theft-essential-california"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T23:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon should redo union election over improprieties, NLRB officer recommends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-02/amazon-union-election-should-be-re-run-labor-official-says</id>
        <link href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-02/amazon-union-election-should-be-re-run-labor-official-says"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T22:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev log for Wonder Wanderer 2: Day 2 #LOWREZJAM]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/michaelprimo/dev-log-for-wonder-wanderer-2-day-2-lowrezjam-18bm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/michaelprimo/dev-log-for-wonder-wanderer-2-day-2-lowrezjam-18bm"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T22:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the second day for me on the LOWREZJAM.
I managed to do today a basic movement for the character, adding gravity, the direction and the force of it with a little drawing of a map includes, and two buttons with a fake jump (without friction) and a button that changes gravity (it's not like VVVVVV, you can use this ability to do some wall-running, but you will see). I hope to do better jumps, map collisions and some hazards next day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Primo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apprendre Vue.js 3 - Jour 3 : Vuex]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ericlecodeur/apprendre-vue-js-3-jour-3-vuex-28il</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ericlecodeur/apprendre-vue-js-3-jour-3-vuex-28il"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T22:33:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Si vous désirez plus de contenu francophone comme celui-ci, cliquer Follow ou suivez-moi sur Twitter


  
  
  Vuex - State Managment


  
  
  Le state management pour votre application Vue


La création de plusieurs components et plusieurs sous components entraine comme conséquence un partage des données et méthodes (via les Props et les Events) entre components qui devient vient très complex. Afin de simplifier cette gestion, Vue met à votre disposition la librairie Vuex.
Vuex permet de centraliser la gestion du state (des données et méthodes) de vos components en un seul endroit. Cet endroit est appelé le Store. 
Le store permet de sauvegarder et de modifier votre state et cela à partir de n'importe quel component de votre application.
Du coup, le store est donc ce que l'on appel le 's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Le Codeur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yellowcake Shaped the West]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hcn.org/articles/books-mining-how-yellowcake-shaped-the-west</id>
        <link href="https://www.hcn.org/articles/books-mining-how-yellowcake-shaped-the-west"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T22:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I went from struggling with math to becoming a data and analytics advocate]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mixpanel/how-i-went-from-struggling-with-math-to-becoming-a-data-and-analytics-advocate-1jm8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mixpanel/how-i-went-from-struggling-with-math-to-becoming-a-data-and-analytics-advocate-1jm8"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T22:26:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was written by Mixpanel Community Manager Jaz Broughton and originally appeared on Mixpanel's product analytics blog, The Signal.
I’ve struggled with math since high school.
It wasn’t that I was incapable of doing simple algebra here and there. My hangup was the topic in general. I always had a hard time applying any real focus on the abstract shapes and concepts with no tangible connection to what I actually cared about.
I’m sure this was my dad’s philosophy rubbing off on me. He’s been a carpenter my whole life (and a DJ, but that’s a story for another time). As a child, I would hear him saying things like, “You’re not going to have me in a class just learning numbers for the sake of it.”
Well, today I lead the  Mixpanel Community, a place full of stat-powered technical peop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mixpanel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FB users buying Oculus VR headsets to get customer service prioritization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.npr.org/2021/08/02/1023801277/your-facebook-account-was-hacked-getting-help-may-take-weeks-or-299</id>
        <link href="https://www.npr.org/2021/08/02/1023801277/your-facebook-account-was-hacked-getting-help-may-take-weeks-or-299"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T22:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go, Gorilla/mux and mongo demo]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iamelesq/go-gorilla-mux-and-mongo-demo-10j4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iamelesq/go-gorilla-mux-and-mongo-demo-10j4"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T22:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are we going to do?
Setup some tools for starting a containerised MongoDB and connecting to the shell.
Create a connection to the database with Go
perform some trivial CRUD.
get an MVP knocked up, not paint the Sistine Chapel.
Simple. Let's go.
I'm assuming you have docker installed, if not head over to the docker site, follow the installation instructions for you system. Please forgive anything in the following section that is Mac specific and an oversight to make it OS agnostic.  OK so all good, Docker installed. Let's get an image of MongoDB.
docker pull mongo

Now we have an image successfully pulled you'll want to be able to start a container running it. There's couple of things here, you should read up on detached/interactive modes for docker. It's fairly self explanatory and yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elesq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to improve your Docker containers security – [cheat sheet]]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.gitguardian.com/how-to-improve-your-docker-containers-security-cheat-sheet/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.gitguardian.com/how-to-improve-your-docker-containers-security-cheat-sheet/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T21:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passing Props to Child Components in React using TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/passing-props-to-child-components-in-react-using-typescript-2690</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/passing-props-to-child-components-in-react-using-typescript-2690"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T21:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I believe that if you are reading this article, you already have an idea of component hireraquia and the normal flow is to pass props from the parent component to the child component.
I believe we all had some friction trying to convert our JavaScript knowledge to TypeScript, even though it was the same the code became more verbose and suddenly you started questioning everything.
I continue with several challenges on a daily basis, however today I am fully aware of the advantages that TypeScript brings to my application development experience in React.
Exactly today I'm going to give a brief example of how we can pass props between components using TypeScript.
Pretend that the main page of your application is as follows:
// @src/App.tsx

import React, { useState } from "react";

import For…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Mendes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como probar media queries con Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/equimancho/como-probar-media-queries-con-chrome-4kb5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/equimancho/como-probar-media-queries-con-chrome-4kb5"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T21:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lo quieras o no, el desarrollo web moderno está directamente relacionado al diseño responsivo (responsive design). 
Tenemos media queries en todos lados inclusive Bootstrap y Tailwind tienen un sistema de grillas para poder adaptar con mayor facilidad el contenido según la pantalla o dispositivo.
Algunas veces pensamos que los Media Query son difíciles de probar, pero las Herramientas de Desarrollo (DevTools) de Chrome tiene escondida una gema para lidiar y probar fácilmente esos puntos de inflexión (breakpoints).
Para activar ese superpoder debemos realizar los siguientes pasos.
Abrir las Herramientas de Desarrollo (DevTools) de Chrome
Activar la vista Mobile
Asegurarse de seleccionar "Responsive" en la lista de dispositivos.
Mostrar media queries (show media queries)

Dependiendo de la cantidad de media queries definidos en los estilos de la página vas a poder ver 4 barras de diferentes colores.
Tamaño preestablecido (Gris):

Ancho máximo (Azul):

Ancho máximo y mínimo (Verde):

Ancho mínimo (Naranja)

La página de Bootstrap nos da una excelente oportunidad para ver esta utilidad en acción porque tiene definidos múltiples tipos de de media queries.

Además también puedes sobre el media query seleccionado hacer click con el botón secundario y ver el código fuente.

Si también quieres ver todos los media query en acción al mismo tiempo te recomiendo darle una mirada a Responsively.

Es un increíble proyecto código abierto (open source) que nos puede hacer el trabajo más fácil en el desarrollo.
That’s All Folks!
Happy Coding 🖖]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camilo Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Hide Your .env While You're Livestreaming]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cerchie/howto-hide-your-env-while-you-re-livestreaming-26hp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cerchie/howto-hide-your-env-while-you-re-livestreaming-26hp"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T21:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This article assumes basic knowledge of VSCode. 
Here's how to start using John Papa's VSCode extension Cloak to hide .env secrets, especially helpful when you're livestreaming! 
Search 'Cloak' in VSCode extensions and install it.

Open up a .env file with your secrets in it. It should look something like this:

Open up your Command Palette and hit 'Cloak: Hide Secrets'

And there you have it! Your secrets are hidden! You can un-hide them by running the 'Cloak: Show Secrets' command. 
Note: If you copy/paste, your secret will be visible in the file you pasted it in. 
PS- many thanks to @nickytonline
 who pointed out the usefulness of this extension!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucia Cerchie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is How To Make JS Promises [From Scratch]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cleancodestudio/this-is-how-to-implement-javascript-promises-from-scratch-357k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cleancodestudio/this-is-how-to-implement-javascript-promises-from-scratch-357k"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T21:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.ltag__user__id__386677 .follow-action-button {
      background-color: #339d15 !important;
      color: #ffffff !important;
      border-color: #339d15 !important;
    }
  
    
      
Clean Code StudioFollow

    
Clean Code Clean Life ~ Simplify
    
Today, we create our own JavaScript Promise implementation [From Scratch].
To create a new promise we simply use new Promise like so:
  new Promise((resolve, reject) => {
    ...
    resolve(someValue)
  })

We pass a callback that defines the specific behavior of the promise.
A promise is a container:
Giving us an API to manage and transform a value
That lets us manage and transform values that are not actually there yet.
Using containers to wrap values is common practice in the functional programming paradigm. There are different kinds of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clean Code Studio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File structure of Svelte apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/benjithorpe/file-structure-of-svelte-apps-18p0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/benjithorpe/file-structure-of-svelte-apps-18p0"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi again, the last time we talk about Getting Started with Svelte.
Once you install the packages, the structure should look like this:
my-app
│    
└── node_modules
│   └─ bin
│   │ ...
└── public
│   └─ build
│      │  bundle.css
│      │  bundle.js
│      │  bundle.js.map
│   favicon.png
│   global.css
│   index.html
└── scripts
│   │  setupTypeScript.js
└── src
│   │  App.svelte
│   │  main.js
│   .gitignore
│   package-lock.json
│   package.json
│   README.md
│   rollup.config.js

If you are scared, don't be! You won't touch 80% of them.
Now let's discuss the use of each folder and file.
In simple terms, these are just folders of all the tools(extra libraries or packages) the application needs to function. They are installed based on what is in the package.json file (will talk more on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Thorpe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vue.js is Wikimedia Foundation's future JavaScript framework]]></title>
        <id>https://lists.wikimedia.org/hyperkitty/list/wikitech-l@lists.wikimedia.org/thread/SOZREBYR36PUNFZXMIUBVAIOQI4N7PDU/</id>
        <link href="https://lists.wikimedia.org/hyperkitty/list/wikitech-l@lists.wikimedia.org/thread/SOZREBYR36PUNFZXMIUBVAIOQI4N7PDU/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T21:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Myth: DSA is Required Only To Crack Interviews #Busted | Netlist Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kaustuv942/myth-dsa-is-required-only-to-crack-interviews-busted-netlist-generation-14ji</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kaustuv942/myth-dsa-is-required-only-to-crack-interviews-busted-netlist-generation-14ji"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T21:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Confused why every SDE/SWE 


  
  
  You are on the right article!


In this article we will take a look at particularly interesting instance of web-dev where DFS, a well known graph algorithm fit the problem just too well.
Although day to day activities usually doesn't require such knowledge of graph algorithms, however, once in a blue moon comes about a problem, which demands an efficient solution which is next to impossible without graph theory.
Given a electrical circuit annotate its nodes. 

Rules: 
1. Equipotential points must given same names. 
2. No two nodes having different potential must have same names. 
3. A node is an endpoint of an circuit element. 
For e.g. each resistor has 2 nodes marked 1 and 2 in Fig 1.
4. N nodes are given to you. The graph is given to you in terms of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaustuv K Chattopadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AssemblyAI (YC S17) Is Hiring Python Developers and Account Execs]]></title>
        <id>https://apply.workable.com/assemblyai/</id>
        <link href="https://apply.workable.com/assemblyai/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T21:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpaceX installed 29 Raptor engines on a Super Heavy rocket last night]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/08/spacex-installed-29-raptor-engines-on-a-super-heavy-rocket-last-night/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/08/spacex-installed-29-raptor-engines-on-a-super-heavy-rocket-last-night/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T20:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gpsd bug may create a 1024 week time warp on October 23]]></title>
        <id>https://gitlab.com/gpsd/gpsd/-/issues/144</id>
        <link href="https://gitlab.com/gpsd/gpsd/-/issues/144"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T18:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Modules (The Native Ones)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345756</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-modules-the-native-ones/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T18:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They are actually called “CSS Module Scripts” and are a native browser feature, as opposed to the popular open-source project that essentially does scoped styles by creating unique class name identifiers in both HTML and CSS. 
Native CSS Modules are …
The post CSS Modules (The Native Ones) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does the internet work?]]></title>
        <id>61082bc93306a507d1bfc7b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-the-internet-work/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T17:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet is a part of our daily life and we use it constantly. But how does it actually work? We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how the internet works and basic networking principles.  Ian Frost teaches this course. He is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WireGuardNT, a high-performance WireGuard implementation for the Windows kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lists.zx2c4.com/pipermail/wireguard/2021-August/006887.html</id>
        <link href="https://lists.zx2c4.com/pipermail/wireguard/2021-August/006887.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T17:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to boost your popularity on OkCupid using CSRF and a JSON type confusion]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.azuki.vip/csrf/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.azuki.vip/csrf/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T17:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomy Photographer of the Year 2021 shortlist images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.rmg.co.uk/national-maritime-museum/astronomy-photographer-year-2021-shortlist-images</id>
        <link href="https://www.rmg.co.uk/national-maritime-museum/astronomy-photographer-year-2021-shortlist-images"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T16:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life before smartphones]]></title>
        <id>https://mattruby.substack.com/p/the-most-unbelievable-things-about</id>
        <link href="https://mattruby.substack.com/p/the-most-unbelievable-things-about"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T16:15:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why extraterrestrial life may not seem alien]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/arik-kershenbaum-on-why-alien-life-may-be-like-life-on-earth-20210318/</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/arik-kershenbaum-on-why-alien-life-may-be-like-life-on-earth-20210318/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T15:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Push for a “PBS for the Internet”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.axios.com/pbs-internet-online-information-nonprofit-e9a78344-ae58-4214-9cb6-974ab9576cb1.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.axios.com/pbs-internet-online-information-nonprofit-e9a78344-ae58-4214-9cb6-974ab9576cb1.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T15:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Who is hiring? (August 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28037366</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28037366"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T15:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Who wants to be hired? (August 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28037364</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28037364"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T15:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pegasus spyware found on journalists’ phones, French intelligence confirms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2021/aug/02/pegasus-spyware-found-on-journalists-phones-french-intelligence-confirms</id>
        <link href="https://www.theguardian.com/news/2021/aug/02/pegasus-spyware-found-on-journalists-phones-french-intelligence-confirms"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T14:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a Playable Synth Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345178</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-code-a-playable-synth-keyboard/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T14:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a little knowledge of music theory, we can use regular HTML, CSS and JavaScript — without any libraries or audio samples — to create a simple digital instrument. Let’s put that into practice and explore one method for creating …
The post How to Code a Playable Synth Keyboard appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bret Cameron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Heimdal (YC S21) – Carbon neutral cement]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28036927</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28036927"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T14:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lisp as an Alternative to Java (2000)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.norvig.com/java-lisp.html</id>
        <link href="http://www.norvig.com/java-lisp.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T14:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Kernel Module Programming Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/sysprog21/lkmpg/</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/sysprog21/lkmpg/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T14:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UK’s delta surge is collapsing]]></title>
        <id>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/08/the-u-k-s-delta-surge-is-collapsing-will-ours.html</id>
        <link href="https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/08/the-u-k-s-delta-surge-is-collapsing-will-ours.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T13:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six Years of Professional Clojure]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.nanit.com/6-years-of-professional-clojure-2b61cb6c1983</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.nanit.com/6-years-of-professional-clojure-2b61cb6c1983"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T11:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Strategy, Regression Testing And Maintenance (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a deep dive into the refactoring process itself, and cover incremental refactoring strategy, visual regression testing, and maintaining the refactored codebase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peg Parsing Series Overview (2019)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/@gvanrossum_83706/peg-parsing-series-de5d41b2ed60</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/@gvanrossum_83706/peg-parsing-series-de5d41b2ed60"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T08:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The quiet battle raging around open banking]]></title>
        <id>https://sifted.eu/articles/open-banking-finance-battle/</id>
        <link href="https://sifted.eu/articles/open-banking-finance-battle/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T07:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like a product but is secretly a subscription]]></title>
        <id>https://calpaterson.com/printers.html</id>
        <link href="https://calpaterson.com/printers.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T05:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sentenced by Algorithm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nybooks.com/articles/2021/06/10/prison-terms-sentenced-by-algorithm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.nybooks.com/articles/2021/06/10/prison-terms-sentenced-by-algorithm/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T02:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red delicious apples weren’t always horrible]]></title>
        <id>https://newengland.com/today/food/red-delicious-apple/</id>
        <link href="https://newengland.com/today/food/red-delicious-apple/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T02:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neat Elixir trick: Libraries can start processes too]]></title>
        <id>https://mattmower.com/2021/08/01/libraries-can-start-processes-too/</id>
        <link href="https://mattmower.com/2021/08/01/libraries-can-start-processes-too/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-01T10:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19419</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/31/science-and-technology-links-july-31st-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T19:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers built a microscope that might be 10 times better than the best available microscopes. Subsidizing college education can lower earnings due to lower job experience: The Post 9/11 GI Bill (PGIB) is among the largest and most generous college subsidies enacted thus far in the U.S. (…) the introduction of the PGIB raised college … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes In August (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2021. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basic HTML5 Template: Use This HTML Boilerplate as a Starter for Any Web Dev Project]]></title>
        <id>6053023028094f59be257c79</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basic-html5-template-boilerplate-code-example/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are building a new website, it is important to have a good starting foundation. In this article, I will explain what an HTML 5 boilerplate is and how to create a basic template to use in your projects.  What is an HTML 5 boilerplate?According to Wikipedia,  boilerplate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excel Text Function – How to Convert a Number to Text Format]]></title>
        <id>60f534d266c61b07d458ecf8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-text-function-how-to-convert-a-number-to-text-format/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to add a number to a text string, you can't do so directly since the format isn't maintained. Also, a number added to a text string doesn't have any formatting or all its decimal places.  The TEXT function comes in handy here, as it allows you to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Advanced Actor-Critic Methods: Reinforcement Learning Course]]></title>
        <id>610478b63306a507d1bfbb23</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-advanced-actor-critic-methods-reinforcement-learning-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actor-Critic Methods are very useful reinforcement learning techniques. Actor-critic methods are most useful for applications in robotics as they allow software to output continuous, rather than discrete actions. This enables control of electric motors to actuate movement in robotic systems, at the expense of increased computational complexity. We just released]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Hyperlink? Definition for HTML Link Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6102c9803306a507d1bfb0f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-hyperlink-definition-for-html-link-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Links are a defining featute of the Web and you'll find them everywhere.  As their name suggests, they create links, or connections, between pages. This allows us to navigate quickly and easily from one webpage to another.  You'll find many types of links on the Web.  There are links that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs Voice Typing – How to Use Speech-to-Text in a Google Doc]]></title>
        <id>60f5350266c61b07d458ed04</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-docs-voice-typing-how-to-use-speech-to-text-in-a-google-doc/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T20:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speech-to-Text is a really useful accessibility tool if typing is difficult for you. Or you can also use it if you like to think out loud and transcribe what you say. In this tutorial, I'll show you how to use speech-to-text in Google Docs. Do note, though, that this feature]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Shared ESLint Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345628</id>
        <link href="https://katydecorah.com/code/eslint-config/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T20:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like it was almost 9 years ago when Airbnb first published their JavaScript Style Guide. 112k stars on GitHub later, it seems like the de facto preset for Babel / ES Lint. But it’s not the only company …
The post A Shared ESLint Configuration appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conjuring Generative Blobs With The CSS Paint API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345256</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/conjuring-generative-blobs-with-the-css-paint-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T14:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Paint API (part of the magical Houdini family) opens the door to an exciting new world of design in CSS. Using the Paint API, we can create custom shapes, intricate patterns, and beautiful animations — all with a …
The post Conjuring Generative Blobs With The CSS Paint API appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Francis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6687</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/now-discover-your-strengths-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=now-discover-your-strengths-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Now, Discover Your Strengths shows you how to find your top five strengths by outlining what strengths are, how you get them, why they’re important to reaching your full potential, and how to discover your own through analyzing the times when your behavior is the most natural or instinctive and why. Read in: 4 […]
The post Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An E-Commerce Site With Angular 11, Commerce Layer And Paypal]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having an e-commerce store is crucial for any store owner as more and more customers are turning to online shopping. In this tutorial, we shall go through how to create an e-commerce site with Angular 11. The site will use the Commerce Layer as a headless e-commerce API and use Paypal to process payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Camera2 – How to Use the Camera2 API to Take Photos and Videos]]></title>
        <id>60f0501b66c61b07d458df00</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/android-camera2-api-take-photos-and-videos/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T22:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all use the camera on our phones and we use it a l-o-t. There are even some applications that have integrated the camera as a feature.  On one end, there is a standard way of interacting with the camera. On the other, there is a way to customize your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19408</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/29/measuring-memory-usage-virtual-versus-real-memory/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T21:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developers are often concerned with the memory usage of their applications, and rightly so. Software that uses too much memory can fail, or be slow. Memory allocation will not work the same way under all systems. However, at a high level, most modern operating systems have virtual memory and physical memory (RAM). When you write … Continue reading Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Explains the Open Graph Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345518</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-06-22-framework-building-open-graph-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T19:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An explanation of those new GitHub social media images:
[…] our custom Open Graph image service is a little Node.js app that uses the GitHub GraphQL API to collect data, generates some HTML from a template, and pipes it to 
…
The post GitHub Explains the Open Graph Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Equal Sign – How to Type the Does Not Equal Symbol]]></title>
        <id>60f534ec66c61b07d458ecfe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/not-equal-sign-how-to-type-the-does-not-equal-symbol/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T18:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The does not equal symbol, or ≠, is often not part of a standard keyboard setup – or it's well hidden. So if you need to write it, how do you do it? How to Write the Not Equal Sign on Desktop DevicesOn Windows: Use the Character MapThe Character Map is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Deploy 12 Apps to AWS, Azure, &amp; Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>6102ccd03306a507d1bfb150</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-deploy-12-apps-to-aws-azure-google-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T15:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing an app makes it simpler to deploy. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to deploy 12 apps to 3 popular hosting services. Scalable Scripts developed this course. They create courses on all sorts of languages and frameworks on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Basic Excel Tutorial – How to Automate Repetitive Tasks in a Spreadsheet]]></title>
        <id>60fc708a22b0e2078fcd0cdc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-repetitive-tasks-in-excel-with-vba/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use VBA, or Visual Basic for Applications, to automate my repetitive tasks. This saves me quite a lot of time in my day-to-day life.  Based on the fact that you're reading this tutorial, I assume that you would like to be able to do the same. So I will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So you want to self-publish books and courses on programming]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344993</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-you-want-to-self-publish-books-and-courses-on-programming/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Resig and I recently self-published our book on GraphQL. There are tons of how-tos for self-publishing a book, or even online classes, but very little in the way of why you would want to, or whether it’s even worth …
The post So you want to self-publish books and courses on programming appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Loren Sands-Ramshaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer-Friendly Passwordless Auth]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345260</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/developer-friendly-passwordless-auth/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T14:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’d wager to say that most websites that are business-minded have accounts. A way to log into them. Social media sites, eCommerce sites, CMS systems, you name it, having accounts people log into is at the heart of them. So… …
The post Developer-Friendly Passwordless Auth appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Such Thing As A CSS Absolute Unit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are absolute units? What are the differences between relative and absolute units, and how do we create accurate sizes on the web? In this article, Elad Shechter explains why CSS absolute units aren’t so absolute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elad Shechter)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari 15 Opinions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345404</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/safari-15-opinions/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T20:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was interesting that when Safari 15 was dropping at this last WWDC, in my circles at least, I mostly heard enthusiasm. Like the colors-in-the-browser-controls stuff was a neat trick and fun to play with. And there were other …
The post Safari 15 Opinions appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Absolute Value, Sign, Rounding and Modulo in CSS Today]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=320544</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-absolute-value-sign-rounding-and-modulo-in-css-today/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T14:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For quite a while now, the CSS spec has included a lot of really useful mathematical functions, such as trigonometric functions (sin(), cos(), tan(), asin(), acos(), atan(), atan2()), exponential functions (…
The post Using Absolute Value, Sign, Rounding and Modulo in CSS Today appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Tudor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Democracies Die Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6683</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-democracies-die-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-democracies-die-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How Democracies Die explores the foundational ideas of democracy by looking at historical events, especially in Latin America, that show how democracies have failed, whether it can happen again, and how to protect democracy from threats like mutual toleration, inequality, and political parties. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: When Donald […]
The post How Democracies Die Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating An Accessible Dialog From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dialogs are everywhere in modern interface design (for good or for bad), and yet many of them are not accessible to assistive technologies. In this article, we will dig into how to create a short script to create accessible dialogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kitty Giraudel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learnings From a WebPageTest Session on CSS-Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345169</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/learnings-from-a-webpagetest-session-on-css-tricks/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T23:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got together with Tim Kadlec from over at WebPageTest the other day to use do a bit of performance testing on CSS-Tricks. Essentially use the tool, poke around, and identify performance pain points to work on. You can watch …
The post Learnings From a WebPageTest Session on CSS-Tricks appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ES2021 Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345400</id>
        <link href="https://h3manth.com/ES2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T23:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hemanth HM very succinctly shows off ES2021 features. Gosh it doesn’t feel like that long ago that all we could talk about is ES2015, and now that’s over a half-decade behind us. 
There are new things like “arbitrarily chuck underscores …
The post ES2021 Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Logical Properties and Values]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344815</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-logical-properties-and-values/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T15:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that cross-browser support is at a tipping point, it’s a good time to take a look at logical properties and values. If you’re creating a website in multiple languages, logical properties and values are incredibly useful. Even if you’re …
The post CSS Logical Properties and Values appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global vs. Local Styling In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has strong opinions about how to organize JavaScript but not CSS. How can we develop patterns that encourage best CSS practices while also following the framework’s logic? The answer is surprisingly simple — to write well-structured CSS that balances global and local styling concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Dubovoy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying styled-components]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345297</id>
        <link href="https://www.joshwcomeau.com/react/demystifying-styled-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T00:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joshua Comeau digs into how styled-components works by re-building the basics. A fun and useful journey. 
styled-components seems like the biggest player in the CSS-in-React market. Despite being in that world, I haven’t yet been fully compelled by it. I’m …
The post Demystifying styled-components appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Built a Cross-Platform Desktop Application with Svelte, Redis, and Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344653</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-built-a-cross-platform-desktop-application-with-svelte-redis-and-rust/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T14:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Cloudflare, we have a great product called Workers KV which is a key-value storage layer that replicates globally. It can handle millions of keys, each of which is accessible from within a Worker script at exceptionally low latencies, …
The post How I Built a Cross-Platform Desktop Application with Svelte, Redis, and Rust appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slinkity]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345288</id>
        <link href="https://slinkity.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T14:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps the #1 reason I love Astro is that it brings the JavaScript component authoring experience to the Static Site Generator world with zero JavaScript (except bits you very specifically opt-in to). That HTML-first approach is also why I like …
The post Slinkity appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kindness Method Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6677</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-kindness-method-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-kindness-method-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T12:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Kindness Method by Shahroo Izadi teaches how self-compassion and understanding make forming habits easier than being hard on yourself, using the personal experiences of the author and what she’s learned as an addiction recovery therapist to show how self-esteem is the true key to behavior change. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post The Kindness Method Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Serverless Functions And The International Space Station]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby recently announced the launch of “functions”. In this article, Paul Scanlon explains how to get the current location of the International Space Station (ISS) as it orbits the Earth in real-time using [Gatsby Functions](https://www.gatsbyjs.com/docs/reference/functions/) and then display it on a 3D interactive globe using [React Three Fibre](https://github.com/pmndrs/react-three-fiber).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soundtracks Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6665</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/soundtracks-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=soundtracks-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T12:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Soundtracks is New York Times bestselling author Jon Acuff’s 2021 book that teaches you how to beat overthinking by challenging whether your thoughts are true, retiring unhelpful and unkind ideas, adopting thought-boosting mantras from others, using symbols to reinforce positive thoughts, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Is there […]
The post Soundtracks Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Attracting Clients To Your Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many web design agencies consider it a badge of honor that they win work exclusively through word-of-mouth recommendations. In this article, Paul Boag explains why that is entirely the wrong attitude and what to do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Time To Your Schedule As A Professional]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you running a business and have too many things going on at once? Meetings, bugs, customer feedback, new clients in addition to your already tight deadlines? Let’s face it, time management is hard, and it becomes even more difficult in the trying times we are in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[75 Hard Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6657</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/75-hard-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=75-hard-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: 75 Hard is a fitness challenge and book that teaches mental toughness by making you commit to five daily critical tasks for 75 days straight, including drinking a gallon of water, reading 10 pages of a non-fiction book, doing two 45-minute workouts, taking a progress picture, and following a diet. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post 75 Hard Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? We’ve collected some useful color tools and resources that we’ve discovered lately — to help you get the most out of your creativity. We’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [accessible front-end components](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/complete-guide-accessible-front-end-components/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fail Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6656</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-fail-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-fail-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T12:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Fail shows the surprising benefits of going through a difficult time through the experiences of the author, Elizabeth Day, including the failures in her life that she’s grateful for and how they’ve helped her grow, uncovering why we shouldn’t be so afraid of failure but instead embrace it. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post How To Fail Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From WordPress To A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at when it makes sense to migrate from a monolithic project to a headless setup and the benefits that come with it. In addition to a step-by-step guide on how to migrate WordPress to Storyblok Headless CMS, the problems that will arise during the process and how to deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Change Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6655</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-change-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-change-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T06:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Change by Katy Milkman identifies the stumbling blocks that are in your way of reaching your goals and improving yourself and the research-backed ways to get over them, including how to beat some of the worst productivity and life problems like procrastination, laziness, and much more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post How To Change Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Stopping Time Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6638</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-art-of-stopping-time-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-art-of-stopping-time-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T12:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Art of Stopping Time teaches a framework of mindfulness, philosophy, and time-management you can use to achieve Time Prosperity, which is having plenty of time to reach your dreams without overwhelm, tumult, or constriction. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: What would you say if I asked you what the […]
The post The Art Of Stopping Time Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining End-To-End Quality With Visual Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding visual elements to your tests, you can gain more options to add meaningful ways in maintaining a high level of quality for your app. Colby Fayock explains how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Colby Fayock)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Insights I Gained While Researching Vue.js Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web app accessibility appears difficult because it seems that there is little information on the subject available online. Let’s take a closer look at the accessible use of framework features, concrete Vue.js traits, as well as community initiatives and vetted patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are You Doing With Your Life Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6595</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/what-are-you-doing-with-your-life-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=what-are-you-doing-with-your-life-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: What Are You Doing With Your Life is a book by the great philosopher and teacher Jiddu Krishnamurti, who turns traditional ideas about happiness and the purpose of life on its head by diving into the details of life’s most important questions so you can live with intention and joy more consistently. Read in: […]
The post What Are You Doing With Your Life Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISR vs DPR: Big Words, Quick Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two strategies for incrementally building websites that are growing in popularity: Incremental Static Regeneration and Distributed Persistent Rendering. What’s the difference? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cassidy Williams)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Do That With A JavaScript Data Grid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll get to see some pretty groundbreaking things you can achieve with modern JavaScript grids and discover new ways to augment a data grid to make it engaging, responsive, and accessible. All this will be illustrated using Kendo UI Data Grids and their features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Way Of Integrity Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6594</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-way-of-integrity-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-way-of-integrity-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T12:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Way Of Integrity uses science, spirituality, humor, and Dante’s Divine Comedy to teach you how to find well-being, healing, a sense of purpose, and much more by rediscovering integrity, or the recently lost art of living true to yourself by what you do, think and say. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post The Way Of Integrity Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19380</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/14/faster-sorted-array-unions-by-reducing-branches/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing an index, a database or a search engine, you frequently need to compute the union of two sorted sets. When I am not using fancy low-level instructions, I have most commonly computed the union of two sorted sets using the following approach: v1 = first value in input 1 v2 = first value … Continue reading Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Broken Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Too often dealing with filters can be frustrating. Let’s get them right. That means never freeze the UI on a single input, provide text input fallback and never auto-scroll users on a single input. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Dynamic Header With Intersection Observer]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, attaching an event listener to constantly fire a callback on scroll can be performance-intensive. But there is a better way with Intersection Observer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From jQuery To Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’re taking a closer look at different approaches and strategies on how we can migrate a web application that uses jQuery framework, and start using one of the coolest React frameworks in the market: Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Introduction (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS refactoring is not an easy task — it needs to be done in a way that doesn't create problems. First we need to analyze the existing codebase, audit CSS codebase health, discover weaknesses, agree on the approach, and convince management to invest time and resources into the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19369</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/10/science-and-technology-links-july-10th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use CRISPR, a state-of-the-art gene editing technique, to edit the genes of live human patients in a clinical trials. A clinical trial has begun regarding an HIV vaccine. If you choose to forgo meat to fight climate change, you may lower your individual’s lifetime warming contribution by 2 to 4%. Age-related testosterone loss may … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making A Strong Case For Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility is often overlooked or bolted on to the end of a project. Let’s figure out how to implement and advocate for accessibility from the inception of a project to the release or handoff and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Todd Libby)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools And Practices To Speed Up The Vue.js Development Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though Vue.js claims to have an approachable minimalist framework that can be incrementally adaptable, it can be a little bit overwhelming when starting as a Vue.js newbie. In this article, we’re looking at ways to make writing Vue.js a breeze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Uma Victor)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Figma Interactive Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Components in Figma allows designers to create a component with states (hover, active, clicked, focus) and make it interactive so that every copy of the component will inherit those same interactions by default. Let’s explore how it can reduce the time and effort needed to create interactions for your mock-ups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emiliano Cicero)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an array of Headless CMSes out there. In this article, we delve into headless CMS features to satisfy your content editors, marketers and yourself as a developer. For the experience headless practitioner, this could be a checklist to see what’s new out there. For those starting out on their headless journey, this could be a guide on what to look for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emmanuel Tissera)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HSL Colors In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ahmad Shadeed explains what HSL is, how to use it, and shares some of the useful use-cases and examples that you can use right away in your current projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>