<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-07-10T00:56:59.383Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-07-10T00:56:59.383Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Official. We Can Now Harvest Usable Lithium from Seawater]]></title>
        <id>https://interestingengineering.com/lithium-from-seawater</id>
        <link href="https://interestingengineering.com/lithium-from-seawater"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T00:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Audio Is Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://non.tuxfamily.org/wiki/2021-02-07%20Linux%20Audio%20is%20Dead</id>
        <link href="https://non.tuxfamily.org/wiki/2021-02-07%20Linux%20Audio%20is%20Dead"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T00:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to achieve sustainable remote work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/cultural-comment/how-to-achieve-sustainable-remote-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.newyorker.com/culture/cultural-comment/how-to-achieve-sustainable-remote-work"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T23:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncover the Real Senior Developer w/ Tomasz Waraksa]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linearb/uncover-the-real-senior-developer-w-tomasz-waraksa-29nd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linearb/uncover-the-real-senior-developer-w-tomasz-waraksa-29nd"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T23:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should you be hiring a software developer or a senior software developer…and what’s the difference? And how can you know during an interview? 
To help answer these questions, Tomasz Waraksa, a tenured senior software developer with decades of hiring experience, joins the Dev Interrupted podcast to explain how companies should rethink their approach to hiring a senior software developer, and what it means when one joins your team.
Listen to the full episode







  
  
  Episode Highlights include:



The different between a regular and senior developer
What to ask a senior software developer during the hiring process
How this senior role has changed over the decades
What you should expect from a senior developer after hiring one
Join the Dev Interrupted Discord Server


With over 1200 members, the Dev Interrupted Discord Community is the best place for Engineering Leaders to engage in daily conversation. No sales people allowed. Join the community >>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Bronsdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creep – a pretty sweet 4px wide pixel font]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/romeovs/creep</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/romeovs/creep"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T23:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breadth First Search (BFS) Algorithm]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/breadth-first-search-bfs-algorithm-1m5c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/breadth-first-search-bfs-algorithm-1m5c"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T23:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hi guys, on this beautiful day we'll talk about Breadth-First Search
Breadth-First Search: is an algorithm that traverses and searches in trees and graphs using recursion and queue data structure, this algorithm comes to avoid processing a node more than once.



Space complexlity
O(V)




Time complexity
O(V+E)



Google maps 
Cheney's algorithm
Search Engines
Peer to Peer Networking
Ford-Fulkerson algorithm
Initialize a queue 


Mark the node as visited by inserting it to a list


Insert the vertices into the queue


While len(queue) > 0:
Delete the first item of the queue 
mark as visited and push all adjacents unvisited nodes of the deleted Item.
more details...
If you are not familiar with python, I recommend you check this series
# CODE FROM https://favtutor.com/blogs/breadth-first-s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Bouchiha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[⭐️⭐️ tsParticles 1.31.0 and 2K stars on GitHub 🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/matteobruni/tsparticles-1-31-0-and-2k-stars-on-github-36e6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/matteobruni/tsparticles-1-31-0-and-2k-stars-on-github-36e6"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T22:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tsParticles 1.31.0


First of all, thanks to all users that left a stars to this project, it's growing fast for being just a new particles library.

I wanted to release the 1.31.0 version when 2K stars reached since it was a close target.
Now let's see what's new in this version
Added zIndex options, closes #979
Added particles groups to options
Infection is now a plugin, and it's included and is not included in the slim version
Changed particles move distance options to an horizontal/vertical object, single number still valid




Here we can see the new Z Index effect, particles are in different "layers" and opacity is not affected by configuration.
Let's set a new target to 3K stars from now, thanks for the new star ⭐️
 / 
        tsparticles
      
    

A lightweight TypeScript library for creating particles. Dependency free (*), browser ready and compatible with React, Vue, Angular, Svelte, jQuery, Preact, Inferno
         
This library is available on the two most popular CDNs and it's easy and ready to use, if you were using particles.js it's even easier.
You'll find the instructions below, with all the links you need, and don't be scared by TypeScript, it's just the source language.
The output files are just JavaScript. 🤩
CDNs and npm have all the sources you need in Javascript, a bundle browser ready (tsparticles.min.js) and all files splitted for import syntax.
If you are still interested some lines below there are some instructions for migrating from the old particles.js library.
Library installation


Hosting / CDN

Please use this hosts or your own to…
View on GitHub
You can see other configurations and articles in my profile
[JS] How to create beautiful and realistic confetti animation with tsParticles
Matteo Bruni ・ Jun 29 ・ 6 min read
#showdev
        #javascript
        #html
        #webdev
      
tsParticles Fireworks Effect 2.0
Matteo Bruni ・ Jun 16 ・ 1 min read
#codepen
        #showdev
        #javascript
        #html]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matteo Bruni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I accidentally took down GitHub Actions (2019)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.teddykatz.com/2019/11/12/github-actions-dos.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.teddykatz.com/2019/11/12/github-actions-dos.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T22:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 405 : Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dwane/day-405-generation-5cfa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dwane/day-405-generation-5cfa"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T21:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[liner notes:
Professional : Not a bad day. Didn't have any meetings so I was able to put some things into their final states where it doesn't rely on me doing anything else and it's in another person's hands. Reviewed some pull requests. Got some pull requests I made merged. Oh and when I went to work on that social media site that has been giving me trouble again said my activity may be against their community guide lines. I have done nothing expect accept an invite from a co-worker and was added to a work test group. That's it! This social media site sucks!!! I had to upload a photo of myself to be reviewed. I still don't have access and they have my photo. Terrible!


Personal : So I got the thumbnail generation stuff worked out. I was also able to get the front end to pull the videos that have thumbnails and show them on the videos archive page. I think I'll have it all ready for the next live streams on Sunday. I want to get the videos in the dashboard so I can edit, deleted, get thumbnails generated for old videos etc. That will probably come after my next thing which is to get the details and transcripts of the archived videos automatically created with an API I've recently come across.




Going to focus on finishing putting together the radio show for tomorrow and then work on some stuff for the live stream on Sunday. The new "Black Widow" movie came out so I may watch that or maybe work on my side project. That's about it.
Have a great night and weekend!
peace piece
https://dwane.io / https://HIPHOPandCODE.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HIPHOP and CODE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript Coding by Playing Games 🎮]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/suprabhasupi/learn-javascript-coding-by-playing-games-4d8a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/suprabhasupi/learn-javascript-coding-by-playing-games-4d8a"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T21:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You will learn the basics of JavaScript by creating the following ten games:
CheckiO



Teachers all over the world use CheckiO as an extra-tool during their courses so that students could practice their skills when learning new material.
JSRobot



Learn JavaScript by playing a platform game
JSDares



You learn programming by completing dares. These are short puzzles in which you have to copy the example, in as few lines of code as possible.
Coding Game



CodinGame is a challenge-based training platform for programmers where you can improve your coding skills with fun exercises (25+ languages supported)
Robocode



Robocode is a programming game, where the goal is to develop a robot battle tank to battle against other tanks in Java or .NET. The robot battles are running in real-time and on-screen.
Code Combat



CodeCombat is an HTML5 role-playing game (RPG) that teaches you fundamental programming concepts. CodeCombat supports 5 programming languages.
Screeps



Screeps is a fun game and has a unique angle to it.
Untrusted



The game presents you with a roguelike-like playing environment and a console window with the JavaScript code generating each level.
Crunchzilla



Crunchzilla offers interactive tutorials that get people excited about programming. Play with code, build, and learn.
Elevator Saga



This is a game of programming!
Thanks for reading!
Hope you enjoyed reading the article 😉 


  
    
 Twitter
      
      
        👩🏻‍💻  suprabha.me
      

        🌟  Instagram]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suprabha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the every Method in an array]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rthefounding/using-the-every-method-in-an-array-1j64</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rthefounding/using-the-every-method-in-an-array-1j64"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T21:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The every method works with arrays to check if every element passes a particular test. It returns a Boolean value true if all values meet the criteria, false if not.


Example, the following code would check if every element in arr is positive.




function check(arr) {
return arr.every(function(num) {
  return num > 0;
})

}
console.log(check([1, 2, 3, -4, 5]));

check([1, 2, 3, -4, 5]) should return false




  
  
  Using the some Method



The some method works with arrays to check if any element passes a particular test. It returns a Boolean value true if any of the values meet the criteria, false if not.
Ex:




function check(arr) {
return arr.some(function(num) {
  return num > 0;
})

}
console.log(check([1, 2, 3, -4, 5]));
// would return true]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Randy Rivera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VPN – A Very Precarious Narrative]]></title>
        <id>https://overengineer.dev/blog/2019/04/08/very-precarious-narrative.html</id>
        <link href="https://overengineer.dev/blog/2019/04/08/very-precarious-narrative.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T21:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add Redux Toolkit to a React-Redux application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mmeurer00/how-to-add-redux-toolkit-to-a-react-redux-application-i9f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mmeurer00/how-to-add-redux-toolkit-to-a-react-redux-application-i9f"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T21:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table Of Contents



Introduction
Installation
Create Redux Store
Create Slicers
Add Reducers to Store
Performing Asynchronous Logic and Data Fetching
Conclusion
Over the last couple days I realized I wasn't alone in learning the wonders of redux toolkit. So for those of you that are in the same boat as me, get ready for some ducks!



Redux Toolkit is package that was built on top of Redux an open-source JS library for managing application state. The package allows the user to avoid unnecessary boilerplate code, and supplies APIs that make applications DRYer and more maintainable. If you'd like to read more about Redux Toolkit and its features, I have another blog post available here. 
Today we'll be focusing on how to implement Redux toolkit in a React-Redux application. 



First and fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxine Meurer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SafeButler (YC S17) is hiring a remote digital marketing associate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.safebutler.com/careers</id>
        <link href="https://www.safebutler.com/careers"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T21:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surveilling the Gamers: Privacy Impacts of the Video Game Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3881279</id>
        <link href="https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3881279"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive two columns layout in flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/trindade7/responsive-two-columns-layout-in-flutter-4omd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/trindade7/responsive-two-columns-layout-in-flutter-4omd"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple column layouts on large screens that collapse to drawers or popup's on small screens are extremely common on responsive apps. In this tutorial I will show you how to create exactly that.
The full code can be found on github.
responsive flutter layout item list demo
Before we start coding let's define exactly what we want to achieve and tackle each part in incremental steps. This will help us focus on the task and keep track of our progress as we go along.
In a nutshell, we want a widget that updates how the children are displayed depending on the screen size of the Window. It should split into two panes when on large screens; on small screens it should show only one pane and open a popup for the second pane as needed:
Flexible layout
Two panes for big screens and one for small scr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>José Trindade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate a Git repository with 2^28 commits—one for every 7-character shorthash]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/not-an-aardvark/every-git-commit-shorthash</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/not-an-aardvark/every-git-commit-shorthash"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uber and Lyft surge pricing drives SF customers back to taxis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sfexaminer.com/news/rideshare-surge-pricing-drives-angry-sf-customers-back-to-taxis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.sfexaminer.com/news/rideshare-surge-pricing-drives-angry-sf-customers-back-to-taxis/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:36:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Modelling / Database Design]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jinxankit/data-modelling-database-design-4hhc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jinxankit/data-modelling-database-design-4hhc"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Database design is structuring data and organised relationships in a database. It goes beyond how the database further works.
dbdigram.io for designing a database so hitting a random try for Bank Database design. 
Requirements
Create and manage accounts { owner, branch, balance details...}
Record all transactions history from accounts -> to accounts etc.
Perform money transfer between 2 accounts consistently within a transactions
Maintaining a Loan Records
Database Design
The basics of database design are identifying what data needs to get stored, grouping such data into tables or collections and adding relationships between related data points. The whole database design process involves
Using Entity-Relationship(ER) diagrams to visualize the objects that get stored and their relationships…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What was your win this week?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/what-was-your-win-this-week-4h3g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/what-was-your-win-this-week-4h3g"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there!
Looking back on your week, what was something you're proud of?
All wins count — big or small 🎉
Examples of 'wins' include:
Starting a new project
Fixing a tricky bug
Kicking back with friends... or whatever else might spark joy ❤️ 
Congrats on your wins this week!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gracie Gregory (she/her)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Read – Eloquent Ruby – Ch 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/baweaver/let-s-read-eloquent-ruby-ch-1-g13</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/baweaver/let-s-read-eloquent-ruby-ch-1-g13"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps my personal favorite recommendation for learning to program Ruby like a Rubyist, Eloquent Ruby is a book I recommend frequently to this day. That said, it was released in 2011 and things have changed a bit since then.
This series will focus on reading over Eloquent Ruby, noting things that may have changed or been updated since 2011 (around Ruby 1.9.2) to today (2021 — Ruby 3.0.x).
Without further ado, let’s get started!
Note: This is an updated version of a previous unfinished Medium series of mine you can find here.
We start in with an introduction on writing code that looks and feels like Ruby.
The first example in practice is the following class:
class Document
  attr_accessor :title, :author, :content

  def initialize(title, author, content)
    @title = title
    @author = a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Weaver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merge High Order Component and Compound Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/didof/merge-high-order-component-and-compound-pattern-56e5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/didof/merge-high-order-component-and-compound-pattern-56e5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Compound Pattern allows you to associate one or more sub-components to a component. These can be repeated and reallocated. Above all, they allow you to encapulate the structure, style and logic relating to a portion of the UI.
The High Order Component is the extension in the React context of the High Order Function. Basically it is a function that wraps a component and enhances it and/or injects additional functionality.
Have you ever tried to use the second over the first? If so, you will have realized that React will complain. I'll tell you more - he's right.
Create Compound Component (more)
Create High Order Component (more)
Merging... it fails!
Reasoning to the solution
Abstract away the problem
If you are already aware of both patterns skip to step 3
Repo with full code
To better …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Di Donato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 React Libraries Every Project Should Use in 2021]]></title>
        <id>60e8864de8ee9b08300ecc3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-react-libraries-every-project-needs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are literally 100s of great React libraries to choose from, but which libraries do you need most for your React projects?  In this article, we're going to break down five libraries you need for your React projects. Each of them will cover virtually every major tool you need, plus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Homer – A tool to build interactive textbooks]]></title>
        <id>https://usehomer.app</id>
        <link href="https://usehomer.app"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T19:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[:focus-visible in WebKit]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344334</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.igalia.com/mrego/2021/06/07/focus-visible-in-webkit-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a nice update from Manuel Rego Casasnovas. Igalia has this idea to sort of crowd-source important web platform features that need to get worked on (that’s the sort of work they do). They call it Open Prioritization. …
The post :focus-visible in WebKit appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What&#x27;s New in React 18? Concurrency, Batching, the Transition API and More]]></title>
        <id>60e81c50134ad707be00f79f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-new-in-react-18/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! In this article, I'm going to show you what's new in the latest of version of React – React 18 – in under 8 minutes.  First, you might be wondering whether the latest set of changes will break anything with your current setup, or whether you will have to learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automatically Generate C# Code Snippets in Visual Studio]]></title>
        <id>60dcb93727f80207bcdbc17e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automatically-generate-code-snippets-visual-studio/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you use code snippets in Visual Studio, it can make your coding process a lot easier and faster. But what are code snippets? And how can you use them? In this article, we'll look at how you can create code snippets in C#. Just keep in mind that snippets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[760+ Free Online Programming &amp; Computer Science Courses You Can Start This July]]></title>
        <id>5f9c986d740569d1a4ca1a04</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-online-programming-cs-courses/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nine years ago, universities like MIT and Stanford first opened up free online courses to the public. Today, close to 1,000 schools around the world have created thousands of free online courses. I’ve compiled this list of 760+ such free online courses that you can start this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Earthly – Better Builds]]></title>
        <id>https://earthly.dev/</id>
        <link href="https://earthly.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T16:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a NoSQL Database with RavenDB]]></title>
        <id>60ae6b0d11ffb70827ef7fe6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-nosql-database-with-ravendb/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T15:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you look at any website or application today, somewhere under the hood there is a database. After all, we live in the world of Big Data. And the volume of data is growing exponentially.  With so much data at hand, we need ever more sophisticated ways to store it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating programming: AI is transforming the coding of computer programs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2021/07/07/ai-is-transforming-the-coding-of-computer-programs</id>
        <link href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2021/07/07/ai-is-transforming-the-coding-of-computer-programs"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T14:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Favicons in Action]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343598</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-favicons-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T14:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever heard of favicons made with SVG? If you are a regular reader of CSS-Tricks, you probably have. But does your website actually use one?
The task is more non-trivial than you might think. As we will see in this …
The post SVG Favicons in Action appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philippe Bernard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Pabio (YC S21) – Interior design and furniture rental as a service]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27783939</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27783939"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T14:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A simple mistake that stuffed up world temperature records for 90 years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2021-07-09/global-temperature-record-mistake/100244736</id>
        <link href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2021-07-09/global-temperature-record-mistake/100244736"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T14:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpriteStack Voxel Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://spritestack.io/</id>
        <link href="https://spritestack.io/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T13:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Diller: The movie business as before is finished and will never come back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.npr.org/2021/07/08/1014095135/barry-diller-headed-2-hollywood-studios-he-now-says-the-movie-business-is-dead</id>
        <link href="https://www.npr.org/2021/07/08/1014095135/barry-diller-headed-2-hollywood-studios-he-now-says-the-movie-business-is-dead"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T12:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Born To Win Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6553</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/born-to-win-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=born-to-win-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T12:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Born To Win is a book by Zig Ziglar and his son Tom Ziglar in which they explore how planning and preparation is the only way to win in life and shows you how to use these tools in combination with a vision for your life, goals, and thinking positively to become a winner […]
The post Born To Win Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NDA expired, let’s spill the beans on a weird startup]]></title>
        <id>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2021/07/nda-expired-lets-spill-the-beans-on-a-weird-startup/</id>
        <link href="https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2021/07/nda-expired-lets-spill-the-beans-on-a-weird-startup/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T11:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passive radiative cooling below ambient airtemperature under direct sun (2014) [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://web.stanford.edu/group/fan/publication/Raman_Nature_515_540_2014.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://web.stanford.edu/group/fan/publication/Raman_Nature_515_540_2014.pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T10:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making A Strong Case For Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility is often overlooked or bolted on to the end of a project. Let’s figure out how to implement and advocate for accessibility from the inception of a project to the release or handoff and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Todd Libby)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMake Part 1 – The Dark Arts]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/07/cmake-part-1-the-dark-arts/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/07/cmake-part-1-the-dark-arts/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T07:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A small town in Sweden fights to preserve Elfdalian, a dying forest language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pri.org/stories/2021-05-06/small-town-sweden-fights-preserve-elfdalian-dying-forest-language</id>
        <link href="https://www.pri.org/stories/2021-05-06/small-town-sweden-fights-preserve-elfdalian-dying-forest-language"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T07:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Cat Person” and Me]]></title>
        <id>https://slate.com/human-interest/2021/07/cat-person-kristen-roupenian-viral-story-about-me.html</id>
        <link href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2021/07/cat-person-kristen-roupenian-viral-story-about-me.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T23:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner JavaScript Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344024</id>
        <link href="https://wesbos.com/javascript"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T22:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wes has a heck of a set of “notes” for learning JavaScript. It’s organized like a curriculum, meaning if you teach JavaScript, you could do a lot worse. It’s actually more like 85 really fleshed-out blog posts organized into sections …
The post Beginner JavaScript Notes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cauliflower and Chaos, Fractals in Every Floret]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/08/science/cauliflower-fractals.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/08/science/cauliflower-fractals.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Own Feature Toggle with Next.js and React in Under 30 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>60e59724134ad707be00e5d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-feature-toggles-in-next-js-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T17:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will show you how to build the Feature Toggle mechanism in your Next.JS application.  We are going to use Next.JS, React, and TypeScript. We will deploy our application to Vercel to demonstrate the real-life example. You can find the code and video in the summary at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Accessible Vue Applications]]></title>
        <id>60e3ae66134ad707be00dbdb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-accessible-vue-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T16:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing web pages used to involve writing HTML, CSS, and a little scripting code like JavaScript for functionality.  But over time, we've developed new and more advanced technologies and frameworks to create webpages. We now use things like reusable components, routing, and rendering to the document object model (DOM).  These]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React JS in This Free 7-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>60df723627f80207bcdbcf36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-js-in-this-free-7-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T15:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Google trends, React is the most popular JavaScript frontend framework. Unless you're in the U.S. state of Nebraska, that is. 😀 Google Trends (React vs Angular)React is a declarative, efficient, and flexible JavaScript library for building user interfaces. We just released a full React course on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Struggle to Use and Animate a Conic Gradient in SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343623</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/my-struggle-to-use-and-animate-a-conic-gradient-in-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T14:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wonderful company I work for, Payoneer, has a new logo, and my job was to recreate it and animate it for a loader component in our app. I’ll explain exactly how I did it, share the problems I …
The post My Struggle to Use and Animate a Conic Gradient in SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amit Sheen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Command Line Tool with Nodejs and Fauna]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343574</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-command-line-tool-with-nodejs-and-fauna/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T14:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Command line tools are one of the most popular applications we have today. We use command line tools every day, and they range from git, npm or yarn. Command line tools are very fast and useful for automating applications and …
The post Building a Command Line Tool with Nodejs and Fauna appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fortune Ikechi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript Works: deep dive into call, apply, and bind]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.sessionstack.com/how-javascript-works-deep-dive-into-call-apply-and-bind-415f6729c902</id>
        <link href="https://blog.sessionstack.com/how-javascript-works-deep-dive-into-call-apply-and-bind-415f6729c902"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T12:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hero Code Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6552</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-hero-code-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-hero-code-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T12:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Hero Code is Admiral William H. McRaven’s guide to becoming a hero, identifying the traits of real-life heroes through inspiring stories of bravery and determination, including many of McRaven’s own experiences as a four-star admiral and in his personal life. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: What is a hero? […]
The post The Hero Code Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reconstructing Roman Industrial Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/07/reconstructing-roman-industrial-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/07/reconstructing-roman-industrial-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T11:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools And Practices To Speed Up The Vue.js Development Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though Vue.js claims to have an approachable minimalist framework that can be incrementally adaptable, it can be a little bit overwhelming when starting as a Vue.js newbie. In this article, we’re looking at ways to make writing Vue.js a breeze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Uma Victor)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The historical significance of DEC and the PDP-7, -8, -11 and VAX]]></title>
        <id>https://liam-on-linux.livejournal.com/81341.html</id>
        <link href="https://liam-on-linux.livejournal.com/81341.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T10:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Politics of Fernando Pessoa]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/issues/ii129/articles/nick-burns-the-politics-of-fernando-pessoa</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/issues/ii129/articles/nick-burns-the-politics-of-fernando-pessoa"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T05:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Private Life of a Cat (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://daily.jstor.org/the-private-life-of-a-cat/</id>
        <link href="https://daily.jstor.org/the-private-life-of-a-cat/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T01:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a JavaScript Object? Key Value Pairs and Dot Notation Explained]]></title>
        <id>60e521aa134ad707be00e41d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-javascript-object/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T22:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Objects are one of the most valuable things you can learn in JavaScript. You can use them to take your programs to the next level.  An object is a collection of data – or key value pairs – which consist of variables and functions that you can access using dot notation. Now]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controlling Marantz amplifier using Arduino via “Remote” socket]]></title>
        <id>https://smallhacks.wordpress.com/2021/07/07/controlling-marantz-amplifier-using-arduino-via-remote-socket/</id>
        <link href="https://smallhacks.wordpress.com/2021/07/07/controlling-marantz-amplifier-using-arduino-via-remote-socket/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at Building with Astro]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343495</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-look-at-building-with-astro/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astro is a brand new framework for building websites. To me, the big thing is that it allows you to build a site like you’re using a JavaScript framework (and you are), but the output is a zero-JavaScript static site. …
The post A Look at Building with Astro appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy Listening Acid Trip: An elevator ride through Sixties psychedelic pop]]></title>
        <id>https://dangerousminds.net/comments/easy_listening_acid_trip_an_elevator_ride_through_sixties_psychedelic_pop</id>
        <link href="https://dangerousminds.net/comments/easy_listening_acid_trip_an_elevator_ride_through_sixties_psychedelic_pop"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T18:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Machine Learning – Tips and Resources to Learn ML the Practical Way]]></title>
        <id>60ccd1794dc1a607ed7b4feb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-machine-learning-practical-tips-and-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T17:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of people want to learn machine learning these days. But the daunting bottom-up curriculum that most ML teachers propose is enough discourage a lot of newcomers.  In this tutorial I flip the curriculum upside down and will outline what I think is the fastest and easiest way to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Web’s Worst Default]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343388</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-webs-worst-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of great defaults when it comes to browsers and the web. Think about all the accessibility features that are baked into HTML so that you don’t have to do weird stuff, like this example from Manuel…
The post The Web’s Worst Default appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundaries Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6551</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/boundaries-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=boundaries-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Boundaries explains, with the help of modern psychology and Christian ideals, how to improve your mental health and personal growth by establishing guidelines for self-care that include saying no more often and standing firm in your decisions rather than letting people walk all over you. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: […]
The post Boundaries Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Figma Interactive Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Components in Figma allows designers to create a component with states (hover, active, clicked, focus) and make it interactive so that every copy of the component will inherit those same interactions by default. Let’s explore how it can reduce the time and effort needed to create interactions for your mock-ups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emiliano Cicero)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Body Toggle]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343438</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/body-toggle/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I appreciate the clarity of this trick that Mikael Ainalem posted over on Reddit:
It’s a one-liner that toggles the class on the <body> so you can mock up different states and toggle between them on click.
<body onclick="this.classList.toggle("active");"
Could …
The post Body Toggle appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve got one question about Jetpack for you.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343560</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ive-got-one-question-about-jetpack-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And maybe an optional follow-up if you’re up for it.
Automattic, the makers of Jetpack and many other WordPress-y things, have sponsored my site (me = Chris Coyier; site = CSS-Tricks) for quite a while. I use Jetpack myself, …
The post I’ve got one question about Jetpack for you. appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dilemma of Naming Font Size Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343149</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-dilemma-of-naming-font-size-variables/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Normally, a project will have a set of pre-determined font sizes, usually as variables named in such a way that seeks some semblance of order and consistency. Any project of considerable size can use something like that. There are always …
The post The Dilemma of Naming Font Size Variables appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lexelius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Nothing Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6550</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/do-nothing-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=do-nothing-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T12:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Do Nothing explores the idea that our focus on being productive all the time is making us less effective because of how little rest we get, identifying how the consequences of overworking ourselves, and the benefits of taking time off, make a compelling argument that we should spend more time doing nothing. Read in: […]
The post Do Nothing Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an array of Headless CMSes out there. In this article, we delve into headless CMS features to satisfy your content editors, marketers and yourself as a developer. For the experience headless practitioner, this could be a checklist to see what’s new out there. For those starting out on their headless journey, this could be a guide on what to look for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emmanuel Tissera)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Explained Simply: Containers, Pods and Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/kubernetes-explained-simply-containers-pods-and-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T14:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you zone out every time someone mentions “Kubernetes,” “containers,” or “pods,” this article is for you. No complex diagrams involved!
As a front-end developer, you don’t have to know how to configure an infrastructure from scratch. However, if you …
The post Kubernetes Explained Simply: Containers, Pods and Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lari Maza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trigonometry in CSS and JavaScript: Beyond Triangles]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343671</id>
        <link href="https://tympanus.net/codrops/2021/06/04/trigonometry-in-css-and-javascript-beyond-triangles/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T14:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web design is such a rectangle-based design medium that literally any deviation from it feels fresh. Michelle Barker gets into using math in various ways to programmatically draw lines, shapes, and animations that end up looking both beautiful and have …
The post Trigonometry in CSS and JavaScript: Beyond Triangles appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bullet Journal Method Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6544</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-bullet-journal-method-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-bullet-journal-method-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T12:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Bullet Journal Method explains the unique system for organizing and taking notes that millions are using to be more productive, improve their mindfulness, prioritize tasks, schedule appointments, solidify ideas, and most of all, set goals, make plans to achieve them and track their progress. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: […]
The post The Bullet Journal Method Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HSL Colors In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ahmad Shadeed explains what HSL is, how to use it, and shares some of the useful use-cases and examples that you can use right away in your current projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fourteenth Fourth]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343496</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-fourteenth-fourth/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T13:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s CSS-Tricks birthday! Somehow that keeps coming around every year. It’s that time where I reflect upon that past year. It’s like the annual vibe check. 
I’m writing this just days after my current home state of Oregon has …
The post The Fourteenth Fourth appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Width Space]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343435</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zero-width-space/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T20:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The name zero-width space is antithetical, but it’s not without uses. In text, maybe you’d use it around slashes because you want to be sure the words are treated individually but not have any physical space around the slash:…
The post Zero-Width Space appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342995</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/good-meetings/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T14:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like it or not, meetings are essential to a good working environment and communication. Therefore, it’s crucial that we work on making them as productive as possible. Today we’ll explore myriad ways to keep meetings coordinated, well documented, and talk …
The post Good Meetings appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Drasner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Data Detective Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6524</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-data-detective-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-data-detective-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T12:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Data Detective will make you smarter by showing how you can understand statistics well enough to see how they, and the beliefs and cognitive biases they can make you have, make such a huge impact in your life, for better or for worse, and how to separate fact from fiction. Read in: 4 […]
The post The Data Detective Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Testing Flow As It Should Be]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many tools and approaches, email still has quite a few pain points, both for developers and email marketers. Email is difficult because it has too many aspects to set and a few instances with no common rules to follow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andriy Zapisotskyi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s A (Front-End Testing) Trap! Six Common Testing Pitfalls And How To Solve Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When writing front-end tests, you’ll find a lot of pitfalls along the way. Let’s explore common mistakes developers make, and how to avoid them. Testing doesn’t need to be painful, after all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6523</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/what-happened-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=what-happened-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: What Happened is Hillary Clinton’s post-mortem on the events and surprising result of her bid for the 2016 United States presidential election, including why she ran for president in the first place, what made it so hard for her to come out on top, and how the loss affected her after election night. Read […]
The post What Happened Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compressing JSON: gzip vs zstd]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19354</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/30/compressing-json-gzip-vs-zstd/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T20:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON is the de facto standard for exchanging data on the Internet. It is relatively simple text format inspired by JavaScript. I say “relatively simple” because you can read and understand the entire JSON specification in minutes. Though JSON is a concise format, it is also better used over a slow network in compressed mode. … Continue reading Compressing JSON: gzip vs zstd]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lives Of The Stoics Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6516</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/lives-of-the-stoics-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lives-of-the-stoics-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Lives Of The Stoics is Ryan Holiday’s latest book, in which he and co-author Stephen Hansel take a deep dive into the experiences and beliefs of some of the earliest philosophers and followers of stoic virtues like justice, courage, and temperance. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: The art of Stoicism […]
The post Lives Of The Stoics Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web Workers In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is single-threaded. This makes it increasingly hard to write smooth and responsive apps. Workers have a bad rep, but can be an important and useful tool in any web developer's toolbelt for these kinds of problems. Let’s get up to speed on Workers on the Web!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Surma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Shades Of July (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome July with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from around the world, they are available with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hood Feminism Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6513</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/hood-feminism-summary-and-review/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hood-feminism-summary-and-review"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Hood Feminism explores the idea that traditional feminism only seeks to improve life for white women and not all women, arguing that true equality and inclusivity means seeking to lift all women, including those of color. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Would you agree that feminism isn’t actually feminism until […]
The post Hood Feminism Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down Bulky Builds With Netlify And Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static Generation is great for performance — until the app gets too big and build-times go through the roof. Today, we’ll have a look at how Netlify’s fresh On-Demand Builders can fix that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 40 With Mike Cavaliere: What Is Chakra UI For React?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Chakra UI. What is it and how can it help with your React projects? Drew McLellan talks to expert Mike Cavaliere to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened To You Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6510</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/what-happened-to-you-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=what-happened-to-you-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T12:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: What Happened To You is Oprah’s look into trauma, including how traumatic experiences affect our brains throughout our lives, what they mean about the way we handle stress, and why we need to see it as both a problem with our society and our brains if we want to get through it. Read in: […]
The post What Happened To You Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Custom Emmet Snippets In VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Manuel explains why Emmet is one of his favorite productivity tools for writing HTML and CSS, and how you can create custom Emmet snippets in Visual Studio Code to help you improve your front-end workflows even more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (June 26th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19349</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/26/science-and-technology-links-june-26th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T16:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reportedly, half of us own a smartphone. It is often reported that women or visible minority earn less money. However, ugly people are doing comparatively even more poorly. We have highly efficient and cheap solar panels. However, we must also quickly dispose of them after a few years which leads to trash. Handling an increasing … Continue reading Science and Technology links (June 26th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Multi-Author Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how we can connect different types of content in a Next.js application. With this technique, we can add any kind of one-to-one, one-to-many, or even many-to-many relationship to our projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dom Habersack)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run A UX Audit For A Major EdTech Platform (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a case study of how a UX audit affects a UI. It explains how a famous educational platform can be analyzed edX against Jakob Nielsen’s usability guidelines. To get started, Mark Lankmiller shares all of the criteria and metrics he used for his UX audit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mark Lankmilier)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: support an experimental template for YouTube feed 📺 Demo | Source

Aggregate content from any YouTube channel rss url https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=<replace_with_channel_id>
Videos are embedded via iframe and loading accelerated by youtube-lite-embed
Ads are reduced thanks to YouTube's policy for embedded videos 🙃
Works on mobile devices with butter smooth horizontal scroll.
Caveat: the template works only with YouTube content. You cannot mix textual RSS feed or other video sources such as Vimeo.
Changed: Default HTML template meta tag adjusted to match convention
Changed: sources in template data is now ordered by last update timestamp (as opposed to alphabetical)
Thank you @PiyushLosalka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long should you work on a problem ?]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19336</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/14/how-long-should-you-work-on-a-problem/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T21:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lev Reyzin says that working too long on a problem might be unproductive: I, personally, have diminishing (or negative?) returns to my creative work as I explicitly work on a problem past some amount of time. I often have insights coming to me out of nowhere while I’m relaxing or enjoying hobbies on nights or … Continue reading How long should you work on a problem ?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (June 12th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19326</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/12/science-and-technology-links-june-12th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T16:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We completed the sequencing of the human genome. AstraZeneca’s drug Lynparza cut combined risk of recurrence of breast cancer or death by 42% among women in study. Glycine and N-acetylcysteine supplementation improves muscle strength and cognition. We found Egypt’s ancient capital. It has been lost of 3,400 years. It is unclear why it was abandoned. … Continue reading Science and Technology links (June 12th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>