<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-21T16:12:57.792Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-21T16:12:57.792Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's start the journey to learn together Full-Stack Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/scotty252/let-s-start-the-journey-to-learn-together-full-stack-development-40a0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/scotty252/let-s-start-the-journey-to-learn-together-full-stack-development-40a0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, My name is James Scott and I am a students of CS, as most students would know just got into college for Bachelors.
I will be utilizing this summer to learn Web development basic languages like HTML, CSS, JavaScript and more...
🙏 🌍, I decided to create this space with the aim of documenting my programming road, organizing materials and inspirations that I have saved in millions of folders 🗂️ and notes 📚.
You want to join me?👀
I am working hard towards becoming a Full Stack Web Developer, learning…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scotty252</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Serverless Applications using CDK and SAM]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/build-serverless-applications-using-cdk-and-sam-4oig</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/build-serverless-applications-using-cdk-and-sam-4oig"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS recently announced the public preview of Serverless Application Model (SAM) support for CDK. SAM is an open-source framework that can be used to build, test and deploy serverless applications on AWS. It provides a Lambda-like execution environment that lets you locally build, test, and debug applications. Previously this could only be defined by SAM templates but now it is also possible through the AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)!

I will guide you through a small demo project to demonstrate how to buil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lorenz Vanthillo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sublime Text 4 is here, can it convert you? (Snack Pack #6)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/blaketweeted/sublime-text-4-is-here-can-it-convert-you-snack-pack-6-53p0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/blaketweeted/sublime-text-4-is-here-can-it-convert-you-snack-pack-6-53p0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It hasn't converted me.






  
  
  Benefits Large files and memory


VSCode is without a doubt a fantastic experience when you get your workflow set up. VSCode also is a memory hog in comparison to Sublime Text 4. 
Not an extensive test. 
My VSCode has extensions running vs. a clean install of Sublime Text 4. The same project and tabs are open in each editor.
The difference in memory is vast. 


This doesn't bug me. My laptop has plenty of memory to use. If your workstation is limited, it's worth the men…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blake Campbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript tricky interview questions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sabbir185/javascript-tricky-interview-questions-26ho</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sabbir185/javascript-tricky-interview-questions-26ho"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the truthy and falsy values of javascript?


JavaScript falsy means false of boolean condition context. Mainly, six expressions are called falsy. They are false, ‘’(empty string), undefined, null, NaN and 0. And the rest of the expression treats truthy. For example –
let value = NaN;

if(value) {
    console.log( “Truthy value”);
} else {
    console.log( “Falsy value” );
}

Output: False value, because here boolean condition expression is false.
null and undefined both are reserve keywords of java…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SABBIR AHMMED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Array Handbook – JS Array Methods Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6098ce302cd0545b5e944d0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, an array is a collection of elements or items. Arrays store data as elements and retrieve them back when you need them.  The array data structure is widely used in all programming languages that support it. In this handbook, I'll teach you all about arrays in JavaScript. You'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building REST API using AWS with Serverless, Node.js, Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/building-rest-api-using-aws-with-serverless-node-js-express-2bk3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/building-rest-api-using-aws-with-serverless-node-js-express-2bk3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started


To get started, you'll need the Serverless Framework installed. You'll also need your environment configured with AWS credentials. 
Then, let's install a few dependencies. We'll install the express framework, as well as the serverless-http:
$ npm install --save express serverless-http 

Then create a file index.js and initialize it like so:
const serverless = require('serverless-http');
const express = require('express')
const app = express()

app.get('/', function (req, res) {
  res.send(…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salah856</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API's From Dev to Production - Part 10]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/newday-technology/api-s-from-dev-to-production-part-10-9j1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/newday-technology/api-s-from-dev-to-production-part-10-9j1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Series Introduction


Welcome to Part 10 of this blog series that will go from the most basic example of a .net 5 webapi in C#, and the journey from development to production with a shift-left mindset. We will use Azure, Docker, GitHub, GitHub Actions for CI/C-Deployment and Infrastructure as Code using Pulumi.
In this post we will be looking at:
SAST - Static Application Security Testing is used to secure software by reviewing/scanning the source code of the software to identify sources of vulnerabilities.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FACEBOOK Clone Using just HTML & CSS - Beginners Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/somanathgoudar/facebook-clone-using-just-html-css-beginners-tutorial-2fe5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/somanathgoudar/facebook-clone-using-just-html-css-beginners-tutorial-2fe5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I Built Facebook Clone using just HTML & CSS. I Just Love to build these to practice my HTML & CSS Skills. I made a tutorial video to help beginners to improve there html & css skills to build real world projects.
Tutorial Video:




Github: https://github.com/somanath-goudar/html-css-projects
Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_nTrhTr5fnBGjOxnkPUmmA
Tiktok Clone & Instagram Reels Clone with just HTML & CSS.
You may also like my other posts:
Build a YouTube Clone with just HTML & CSS + Responsive - …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Somanath Goudar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Make an Average of 250$ Every Month on Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sunilc_/how-i-make-an-average-of-250-every-month-on-twitter-3c60</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sunilc_/how-i-make-an-average-of-250-every-month-on-twitter-3c60"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I realised the importance of having an online presence sometime in the last year when I saw how much money people were making by using Twitter as a Marketing channel. Since I was new to marketing & selling products on the internet, it was shocking to me how one can leverage social media to build businesses online.
I didn't know how to make money through an online presence, but the main thing I realised was that having an online presence is important and it can definitely benefit me one way or the other in t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunil Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte for the Experienced React Dev]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340825</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svelte-for-the-experienced-react-dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is an accelerated introduction to Svelte from the point of view of someone with solid experience with React. I’ll provide a quick introduction, and then shift focus to things like state management and DOM interoperability, among other things. …
The post Svelte for the Experienced React Dev appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340919</id>
        <link href="https://csshell.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collection of common CSS mistakes, and how to fix them
From Stefánia Péter. 
Clever idea for a site! Some of them are little mind-twisters that could bite you, and some of them are honing in on best practices that …
The post CSS Hell appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We're Building Glenstack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/glenstack/how-we-re-building-glenstack-8p4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/glenstack/how-we-re-building-glenstack-8p4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glenstack is a production-ready, modern data platform. And as such, we are embracing the latest and greatest technologies as we deliver our application quickly, securely, and with the features our customers demand.
We want Glenstack to be performant for users, regardless of where they are located. To us, this means we must be distributed. We can't have a single server in us-east-1 because every single user would have to wait for a round-trip request to Virginia which is a significant delay for most of the w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Brimble</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[String em Python!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devshy/string-em-python-47a3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devshy/string-em-python-47a3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O que é uma string?


 Como criar uma string em python?


 Strings são como matrizes!


 Como acessar estes elementos?


 Iterando Strings?!


 Tamanho de uma string!


 Validando caracteres em uma string!


 Conclusão 
Summaryze Forem 🌱



  
  
  O que é uma string?


Em python, uma string são sequências imutáveis de caractere. Ou seja, eles são imutáveis já que para se modificar uma string é necessário que se crie uma nova. 
Para criar uma string, é bastante fácil. Basta criarmos uma variável, e atribui…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevShy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Data Visualizations with D3 and ReactJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codesphere/creating-data-visualizations-with-d3-and-reactjs-10ei</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codesphere/creating-data-visualizations-with-d3-and-reactjs-10ei"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[D3 is a lot more than just a graphing library, it's a toolset for efficiently editing the DOM and creating visualizations based on data.
If all you want is to quickly insert a generic bar graph into your app, then D3 is probably not for you, but if you want the ability to customize your visualizations from the ground up, then D3 is the industry standard.
In this tutorial, we are going to create three different simple visualizations with D3 in React. 
Now while these things can be done without D3 and aren't …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saji Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🚀10 Trending projects on GitHub for web developers - 21st May 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iainfreestone/10-trending-projects-on-github-for-web-developers-21st-may-2021-2c6h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iainfreestone/10-trending-projects-on-github-for-web-developers-21st-may-2021-2c6h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trending Projects is available as a weekly newsletter please sign up at www.iainfreestone.com to ensure you never miss an issue.
Docz makes it easy to write and publish beautiful interactive documentation for your code. Create MDX files showcasing your code and Docz turns them into a live-reloading, production-ready site.
 / 
        docz
      
    




  
    
  
  
    
  
  
    
  


Docz makes it easy to write and publish beautiful interactive documentation for your code.
Create MDX files showcasing y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iain Freestone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG) From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSON in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/json-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Neal tweeted a heck of a little CSS trick the other day, putting JSON inside CSS and plucking it out with JavaScript. Valid values for custom properties are quite liberal! So this looks for a CSS rule (e.g. a …
The post JSON in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340933</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/learn/css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ooo look at this mighty SEO flex from Google: Learn CSS! Well deserved — this is great content. Twenty-three chapters taking you through all the fundamentals of CSS with extra content, like relevant podcasts, interactive examples, and even quizzes to …
The post Learn CSS! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 11 Tutorial: Code a Project from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>60a6b3ab906c5207e3a7f5fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-11-tutorial-code-a-project-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T19:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is one of the most popular web frameworks. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create an Angular 11 project from scratch. It uses a public API to create a game database website. You will gain a great foundation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Modern C++ by Building an Audio Plugin]]></title>
        <id>60a694ab906c5207e3a7f544</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-modern-cpp-by-building-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of C++ courses teach you how to build toy projects with no real-world application. But it can often be more helpful to write programs people would actually use. We just released a 5-hour C++ course that will teach you how to write modern C++ code by building an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Version Control Using Git]]></title>
        <id>60a4b5c7906c5207e3a7e2bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-version-control-and-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn what version control is and how you can contribute to open-source projects using Git.  We'll get through the fundamentals of Git and I'll give you the knowledge that is indispensable for any web developer. What is Git?Git is a version control software which lets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript - A Free 7-hour Interactive Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>60a36742906c5207e3a7da6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-interactive-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last four months, I have recorded what is probably the most interactive JavaScript course that has ever been created. The reason I have done this is because I often see new coders fall into the same pitfalls again and again when trying to learn JavaScript, with the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340715</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/can-we-create-a-resize-hack-with-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow new developments in CSS, you’ve likely heard of the impending arrival of container queries. We’re going to look at the basics here, but if you’d like another look, check out Una’s “Next Gen CSS: @container” article. …
The post Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fit-content and fit-content()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340897</id>
        <link href="https://www.quirksmode.org/blog/archives/2021/04/fitcontent_and.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s some hardcore deep-dive CSS nerdery from PPK. If you can wrap your mind around min-content (the smallest an element can be based on the content it contains) and max-content (the largest the content of an element can push it) …
The post fit-content and fit-content() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340731</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/notion-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Public Beta of the Notion API dropped! Woot! Here’s their guide. I’ve been a Notion user and fan for a long time, for both personal and professional team use. They even sponsored a few videos around here a …
The post Notion API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Selectors to Style Your Web Page]]></title>
        <id>60a341f5906c5207e3a7da61</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-css-selectors-to-style-webpage/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS selectors are one of the most important parts of CSS. They give you the ability to target HTML elements on your web page that you want to style. Without CSS selectors, you wouldn't be able to style your page to look how you want. Thankfully CSS selectors have been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Web3? The Decentralized Internet of the Future Explained]]></title>
        <id>60a42386906c5207e3a7dfe2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet is going through a paradigm shift. Learn the differences between Web2 and Web3, and why many developers and companies are shifting their approach in building apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize for Change in Software Development]]></title>
        <id>60a469ec906c5207e3a7e1b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-for-change-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you work at Magic Money Corp, which runs on just three lines of JavaScript: let input = { step1: 'collect underpants' } doStuff(input)  profit(input) // $$$!!! Now imagine that something's wrong with doStuff and you need to take it down for maintenance. What happens if you temporarily comment out the second]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340692</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-loader-a-different-way-to-work-with-external-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVGs are awesome: they are small, look sharp on any scale, and can be customized without creating a separate file. However, there is something I feel is missing in web standards today: a way to include them as an external …
The post svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Break into Ethereum, Crypto, and Web3 as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>60a53182906c5207e3a7e588</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/breaking-into-ethereum-crypto-web3-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I've been talking about my move into the Web3, Ethereum, and crypto space since making the switch from a traditional web, mobile, and cloud background. Since making that move, a shocking number of people have reached out to me who are also thinking about doing the same.  It's really]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinned Audio WordPress Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340613</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pinned-audio-wordpress-theme/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m afraid I have to start this with a whole backstory, as the journey here is the point, not so much the theme.
A fella wrote to me a while back outlining a situation he was in. His company has …
The post Pinned Audio WordPress Theme appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freelance Development Pricing Guide – Should Freelancers Bill by the Hour?]]></title>
        <id>60a3780f906c5207e3a7db5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-different-ways-to-charge-for-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you offer your services as a freelance developer, you have a major say in how you price your project.  But how do you go about charging for a website project? "Well, I just bill by the hour and send an invoice every week or month." ...I hear you say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Neon Text With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340420</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-neon-text-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neon text can add a nice, futuristic touch to any website. I’ve always loved the magic of neon signs, and wanted to recreate them using CSS. I thought I’d share some tips on how to do it! In this article, …
The post How to Create Neon Text With CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia O'Dwyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340716</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T22:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Addy Osmani on images in HTML:
The humble <img> element has gained some superpowers over the years. Given how central it is to image optimization on the web, let’s catch up on what it can do and how it can 
…
The post The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Love Letter to HTML & CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339522</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-love-letter-to-html-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I see you. In the back there, behind JavaScript and React and PHP and all those “real” programming languages, I see you. And I appreciate you.
The post A Love Letter to HTML & CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Kolodziej</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euismod]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340594</id>
        <link href="https://www.euismod.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interactive tool for learning grid syntax from Etesam Ansari. In the Learn section, it teaches you some concepts (involving multiple bits of the grid syntax) then gives you a task to complete by filling out the right syntax. I’m …
The post Euismod appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Generated Social Media Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340136</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/auto-generated-social-media-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking about social media images again. You know, the images that (can) show up when you share a link in places like Twitter, Facebook, or iMessage. You’re essentially leaving money on the table without them, because they …
The post Auto-Generated Social Media Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340343</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-stylesheet-feature-flags-with-sass-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[!default is a Sass flag that indicates conditional assignment to a variable — it assigns a value only if the variable was previously undefined or null. Consider this code snippet:
$variable: 'test' !default;
To the Sass compiler, this line …
The post Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Babcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: favicon update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Display CLI version in footer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early — when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Newly Supported, Modern CSS Pseudo-Class Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group Editor’s Draft for [Selectors Level 4](https://drafts.csswg.org/selectors-4/) includes several pseudo-class selectors that already have proposal candidates in most modern browsers. This guide will cover ones that currently have the best support along with examples to demonstrate how you can start using them today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: The Ordinary Made Extraordinary (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s the little things in web life that make us look twice. From carousels to documentation to cookie disclaimers, here are some sites taking the mundane and sprinkling in a little magic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>