<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-13T00:58:21.948Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-13T00:58:21.948Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django Infinite scrolling with javascript fetch api and function based view.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tochimclaren/django-infinite-scrolling-with-javascript-fetch-api-and-function-based-view-47fo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tochimclaren/django-infinite-scrolling-with-javascript-fetch-api-and-function-based-view-47fo"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T23:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, I will take you straight through the process of adding inifinte pagination in your django application like it's abc complete code is down below
Note: this is for absolute beginner
django-infinite-scroll
First thing first, we create our django project.
mkdir django-infinite-scroll

cd django-infinite-scroll

pipenv shell #this initializes with Pipfile and creates the environment

We install our django application
pipenv install django

We create a new django project
django-admin startproject core .

We create our app blog and add it to INSTALLED_APPS.
python manage.py startapp blog

INSTALLED_APPS = [
    'django.contrib.admin',
    'django.contrib.auth',
    'django.contrib.contenttypes',
    'django.contrib.sessions',
    'django.contrib.messages',
    'django.contrib.staticfiles',…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tochimclaren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🐳 Docker para desarrolladores]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fernandocutire/docker-para-desarrolladores-bk6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fernandocutire/docker-para-desarrolladores-bk6"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T23:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker es una herramienta maravillosa para desarrolladores y el concepto de empaquetar tus dependencias en un solo lugar que corre en cualquier lugar suena casi utóṕico.
Cómo leer un Dockerfile
Problemas comunes al correr tu Dockerfile
Analizar Dockerfile de una SPA
Cómo construir tus propios dockerfile
Keywords básicas sobre los Dockerfile
Qué es alpine y porqué es usado
Donde buscar imágenes para tus contenedores
Usaré un ejemplo para que podamos entender mejor el funcionamiento de un Dockerfile, un ejemplo para una aplicación de react

FROM node:current-alpine3.14

WORKDIR /usr/src/app

COPY package.json /app

COPY . .

RUN npm set progress=false && npm install

EXPOSE 8086

CMD ["npm", "start"]


Si empleamos la similitud entre un contenedor de esos que los barcos transportan y los doc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Cutire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Websites To Practice You Coding And Your Problem Solving Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/11-websites-to-practice-you-coding-and-your-problem-solving-skills-51k9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/11-websites-to-practice-you-coding-and-your-problem-solving-skills-51k9"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[11 websites to practice your coding and problem-solving skills



coderbyte
topcoder
codewars
Leetcode
hackerrank
exercism
codechef
coderbyte
coderfights
SPOJ
codeforces
Youtube Courses, Projects To Learn Javascript


You Complete Guide To Set Object In Javascript


All JS String Methods In One Post!



To Contact Me:
email:developer.aya.b@gmail.com
telegram: Aya Bouchiha
Have a nice day!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Bouchiha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2020 Census Statistics Highlight Local Population Changes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.census.gov/newsroom/press-releases/2021/population-changes-nations-diversity.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.census.gov/newsroom/press-releases/2021/population-changes-nations-diversity.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T22:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's child protection features spark concern within its own ranks: sources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reuters.com/technology/exclusive-apples-child-protection-features-spark-concern-within-its-own-ranks-2021-08-12/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/exclusive-apples-child-protection-features-spark-concern-within-its-own-ranks-2021-08-12/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T22:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build End-to-End Encryption in 51 lines of Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mrinal/build-end-to-end-encryption-in-51-lines-of-rust-340p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mrinal/build-end-to-end-encryption-in-51-lines-of-rust-340p"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T22:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/ 
        ockam
      
    
Ockam is a rust library that makes it simple for distributed applications to guarantee end-to-end integrity, authenticity, and confidentiality of data.
In this post, we'll create two small Rust programs called Alice and Bob. Alice and Bob will send each other messages, over the network, via a cloud service. They will mutually authenticate each other and will have a cryptographic guarantee that en-route messages were not tampered or forged.
The intermediary cloud service and attackers on the network will not be able to see or change the contents of en-route messages. In later examples we'll also see how we can have this end-to-end protection even when the communication path between Alice and Bob is more complex - with multiple transport connections, a variety of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mrinal Wadhwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styling issues with response Templates Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thomasbnt/styling-issues-with-response-templates-buttons-20jf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thomasbnt/styling-issues-with-response-templates-buttons-20jf"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T21:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello here! I'm Thomas and 22 years old. I really in love of DEV.to(gether) and sometimes I contribute to the code. 
I started a few years ago to contribute to Open Source projects, basically I love helping people. 
This merger allowed me to better understand some aspects of web developers, to say that you are never alone with a problem, that you can always be helped. You just have to ask!
I have already seen this possibility issue, but never created a new issue on the repository. it's absolutely nothing but seeing buttons with a default style, it stings my eyes 😵 

#13747
    
  
michael-tharrington
         posted on May 12, 2021
      
Describe the bug
The moderator templates button under response templates is not styled.
Expected behavior
The buttons should be styled so that you can s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Bnt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tty only]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jackdoe/tty-only-1ijn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jackdoe/tty-only-1ijn"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T21:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used only the tty (no X installed) for 5 nights. It was relaxing, and now I go back to it every time I am overwhelmed. 
I have to seriously re-think the way I spend time on my
BTW, browsing was actually way better than I thought, between eww, w3m, lynx, links2 and links2 -g, and sometimes just reading the html dump, I was able to navigate the modern web with reasonable success.
I bought used t440p laptop, they go from 100 to 300E. Super sturdy machine, like the opposite of my xps. Very easy to open, and very hackable.
Install debian and do some basic fixes to make the tty usable.
rate (whoa slow keyboard rate pisses me off)
add 'kbdrate -r 30 -d 0' to /etc/rc.local
ctrl+/ etc
super annoying that ctrl+/ sends Delete and I want to bind it to undo, to do that you have to:
$ showkeys

press …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>borislav nikolov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you on TikTok?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/are-you-on-tiktok-546h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/are-you-on-tiktok-546h"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T21:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know about you, but I frequently find myself lost in TikTok's #techtok content. There are so many brilliant content creators and software developers there sharing clips of their skills, inner monologues, humor, and beyond. Who knew that so much could be communicated and captured in just a few seconds? 🤯 
I also wanted to let you know that, whether you're on TikTok or not, there's an awesome opportunity to be featured on the CodeLand 2021 program using your skills and personality as a developer...
CodeLand Recess is a community-sourced track of short TikTok-style videos that will lend some fun, humor, and developer-realness to the day's events. We'd love to see a video submission from you! 
All CodeLand Recess video submissions are due by August 20th by 11:59 PM PT (6 AM UTC the following day). Get yours in soon! Instructions and examples here. 
CodeLand Recess!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gracie Gregory (she/her)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Exceptions: Under the Hood]]></title>
        <id>https://monkeywritescode.blogspot.com/p/c-exceptions-under-hood.html</id>
        <link href="https://monkeywritescode.blogspot.com/p/c-exceptions-under-hood.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T21:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing secure systems (Part 1): Why it matters]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/02jandal/developing-secure-systems-part-1-why-it-matters-327j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/02jandal/developing-secure-systems-part-1-why-it-matters-327j"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T21:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security breaches, leaks, and other attacks feature in the news almost weekly, often as the result of insecure systems. While it will always be an arms race between attackers and “defenders”, there is actually a lot that can be done by any developer to significantly decrease the risk of being the next successful target.
A couple of weeks ago Coop, one of Sweden’s largest grocery store chains, along with many other retailers in both Sweden and other countries, was hit by a large ransomware attack that effectively shut down entire stores for several days. Currently in the news is the Pegasus Project, which has uncovered espionage against presidents, journalists, human rights activists, and others using vulnerabilities in iMessage.
But not only people and organizations with large targets on t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Dalheimer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stay alert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346608</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/richharris/stay-alert-d"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T21:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago, Chris wrote up his thoughts about how alert(), confirm(), and prompt() were being deprecated by Chrome and collected a bunch of thoughts from developers. If certain features can essentially be turned off by …
The post Stay alert appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coursedog (YC W19) Is Hiring a VP of Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28161397</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28161397"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure CSS Flex Box Responsive Design - No Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/techsnack/pure-css-flex-box-responsive-design-no-media-queries-p7o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/techsnack/pure-css-flex-box-responsive-design-no-media-queries-p7o"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T20:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Design Doesn't Have To Be Hard







  
  
  With Flex Box we can easily make our webpage act as a responsive container without media queries!


To start with we are going to quickly create a file with the following HTML inside of it
<div class="viewport flex-parent flex-col">
    <div class="nav flex-parent space-around">
        <div class="box-1"></div>
        <div class="box-2"></div>
        <div class="box-3"></div>
    </div>
    <div class="content flex-parent">
        <div class="sidebar-left"></div>
        <div class="main-area"></div>
        <div class="sidebar-right"></div>
    </div>
    <div class="footer flex-parent space-evenly">
        <div class="box-4"></div>
        <div class="box-5"></div>
        <div class="box-6"></div>
    </div>
</div>

...and th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TechSnack - Technology Tutorials</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How green is blue hydrogen?]]></title>
        <id>https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/ese3.956</id>
        <link href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/ese3.956"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T20:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MasquerBot: A Telegram Bot for true paranoids]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ra101/a-telegrambot-for-true-paranoids-16po</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ra101/a-telegrambot-for-true-paranoids-16po"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T20:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://t.me/MasquerBot







Introducing 𝗠𝗮𝘀𝗾𝘂𝗲𝗿𝗕𝗼𝘁! It is a telegram bot that can hide any given text message inside any given image, by manipulating the very pixels of that image (steganography)
• URL changes every 6 hrs, with 130 char long, therefore making it impossible to trace by anyone other than Telegram.
𝘍𝘢𝘳 𝘣𝘦𝘵𝘵𝘦𝘳 𝘥𝘰𝘤𝘶𝘮𝘦𝘯𝘵𝘢𝘵𝘪𝘰𝘯 𝘪𝘴 𝘰𝘯 𝘨𝘪𝘵𝘩𝘶𝘣, 𝘭𝘪𝘯𝘬𝘴 𝘢𝘵 𝘵𝘩𝘦 𝘦𝘯𝘥.
📈 𝗪𝗼𝗿𝗸𝗳𝗹𝗼𝘄:
• It works by creating an ECDSA encryption 🔑🗝key pair, returns you the 🔑public key, to distribute.
• To encrypt, one will have to send your 🔑key along with ✉text and 🖼image.
• The bot will encrypt the text and hide it then it will return the 🖼 encode-image.
• You as a recipient will send the encoded-image to the bot. and it will take your 🗝private key from the 📒database and will send you the hidden ✉text.
PS: Icon is not just eye-candy for otakus. try "/icon" command, within the bot. I bet you will love it. 😉
⚡𝗟𝗶𝗻𝗸𝘀:
https://github.com/ra101/MasquerBot
https://lbry.tv/@ra101/MasquerBot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parth Agarwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The pain and anguish of using IndexedDB: problems, bugs and oddities]]></title>
        <id>https://gist.github.com/pesterhazy/4de96193af89a6dd5ce682ce2adff49a</id>
        <link href="https://gist.github.com/pesterhazy/4de96193af89a6dd5ce682ce2adff49a"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T20:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git password authentication is shutting down]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-08-12-git-password-authentication-is-shutting-down/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-08-12-git-password-authentication-is-shutting-down/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T20:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharge Your Coding in Visual Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dealeron/supercharge-your-coding-in-visual-studio-159h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dealeron/supercharge-your-coding-in-visual-studio-159h"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T20:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard Shortcuts



  
  
  Hold Down Alt when Selecting Text


Let’s say you have a list of variables and you decide to change the scope from public to protected. You could use find and replace on the selected text, or you could just copy/paste over each modifier. Another option is block selecting. Holding down the Alt key while selecting allows you to include multiple lines to the position of the cursor rather than the entire line. The result is that when you type, cut or paste, it applies to every line selected. You could select all the public modifiers and simply type or paste protected to edit them all at once.

Cut and paste? What is so special about these? In Visual Studio. If you have nothing selected, the cut command will cut the entire line and paste will insert the entire line…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Hintze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trabalhe para fora em 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devsincero/trabalhe-para-fora-em-2021-16fd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devsincero/trabalhe-para-fora-em-2021-16fd"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T20:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quem já tem uma boa experiência na área de programação, em 2021, tem chances muito maiores de conseguir um bom emprego, ganhando em moeda estrangeira e com atividades que exijam menor responsabilidade e tempo diário. 
Um programador de alta qualidade técnica, se estiver ainda na área técnica, estará vivenciando os cenários abaixo, que são bem ruins e praticamente eram o destino no nosso mercado antes da pandemia. Eu levantei alguns pontos interessantes abaixo. Segue o fio:
Seu perfil no LinkedIn, quando bem preenchido e cheio de boas experiências, atrai inúmeras consultorias do Brasil. Se o seu perfil está preenchido em Inglês, melhor ainda - o mercado internacional de software está de braços abertos para você. Espera-se que você esteja recebendo muitos convites diários para processos sele…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Programador Sincero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The deceptive PR behind Apple’s “expanded protections for children”]]></title>
        <id>https://piotr.is/2021/08/12/apple-csam/</id>
        <link href="https://piotr.is/2021/08/12/apple-csam/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T19:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US real estate a safe haven for billions in dirty money, report says]]></title>
        <id>https://www.icij.org/investigations/fincen-files/a-kleptocrats-dream-us-real-estate-a-safe-haven-for-billions-in-dirty-money-report-says</id>
        <link href="https://www.icij.org/investigations/fincen-files/a-kleptocrats-dream-us-real-estate-a-safe-haven-for-billions-in-dirty-money-report-says"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T19:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Online – HTML, CSS, and JS Code Editor List [Browser IDE Tools]]]></title>
        <id>610655c93306a507d1bfc0e6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-online-html-css-js-code-editor-list-browser-ide-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T19:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many benefits to coding in an online IDE or code editor. With these tools you don't need to set anything up locally, you can easily share your work, and they are often free to use. In this article, you'll learn what a code editor and an IDE are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scanning “private” content]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/865756/a7f67aaa8ea52862/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/865756/a7f67aaa8ea52862/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T19:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML and CSS – Inline Style, External Stylesheet, CSS Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>6115261272231b077cdaebfe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-and-css-inline-style-external-stylesheet-css-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T18:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're learning about web development, you probably hear about HTML and CSS pretty quickly. Well, what are these tools and how do you use them?  You can think of HTML as the structure and framing of a house. And when you want to make that structure look good, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Websites Where You Can Learn How to Code for Free]]></title>
        <id>6107c0203306a507d1bfc551</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-websites-where-you-can-learn-how-to-code-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T18:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this day and age, it seems like everyone is learning to code. Maybe you want to know how websites work, or you think back fondly on the old blogging platforms where you could hack together some HTML to personalize them. Or maybe you are curious to learn what all]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commodore 64 BASIC and KERNAL on Atari 8-bit hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/unbibium/atari64</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/unbibium/atari64"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T17:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet of Snitches]]></title>
        <id>https://puri.sm/posts/internet-of-snitches/</id>
        <link href="https://puri.sm/posts/internet-of-snitches/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T17:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pigiron, a MIDI Routing Utility with OSC]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/plewto/Pigiron</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/plewto/Pigiron"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T16:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overthinking]]></title>
        <id>https://kerkour.com/blog/overthinking/</id>
        <link href="https://kerkour.com/blog/overthinking/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T16:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laravel Authentication Tutorial – How to Set Up Basic Auth in Laravel 8]]></title>
        <id>610fefc23306a507d1c00896</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basic-authentication-in-laravel8-using-laravel-breeze/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T15:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication is an important feature and basic requirement in web applications these days. And developers spend lots of time building authentication modules for every application they create.  But this manual approach can get tiring and is a bit unproductive. This is where Laravel really shines. It, along with Laravel Breeze,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Packaging Con 2021: a conference for package management devs and communities]]></title>
        <id>https://packaging-con.org/</id>
        <link href="https://packaging-con.org/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T15:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install and Set Up Flutter on Ubuntu 16.04+]]></title>
        <id>610e15c63306a507d1bffb45</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-and-setup-flutter-on-ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T15:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter is a Dart-based toolkit that helps you build the front end of your apps. It really shines in cross-platform mobile app development and aims to be a viable option for web and desktop as well.  In its mobile app flavor, Flutter provides many UI abstractions to build interfaces. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fishdraw: Procedurally Generated Fish Drawings]]></title>
        <id>https://fishdraw.glitch.me/</id>
        <link href="https://fishdraw.glitch.me/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T15:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Modern Clean Architecture]]></title>
        <id>6112e3c972231b077cdad299</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modern-clean-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T15:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clean Architecture is a term coined by Robert C. Martin. The main idea is that entities and use cases are independent of frameworks, UI, the database, and external services. A Clean Architecture style has a positive effect on maintainability because: We can test domain entities and use cases without a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Form – Input Type and Submit Button Example]]></title>
        <id>6113ee6272231b077cdadbd3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-form-input-type-and-submit-button-example/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T15:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forms are one of the most important parts of the web. Without them, there wouldn't be an easy way to collect data, search for resources, or sign up to receive valuable information.  You can embed forms on websites with the HTML form element. Inside the form element, several inputs are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit raises $410M in new funding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/08/12/technology/reddit-new-funding.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/08/12/technology/reddit-new-funding.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T14:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Web Components in WordPress is Easier Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345687</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-web-components-in-wordpress-is-easier-than-you-think/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T14:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that we’ve seen that web components and interactive web components are both easier than you think, let’s take a look at adding them to a content management system, namely WordPress.
There are three major ways we can add them. …
The post Using Web Components in WordPress is Easier Than You Think appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Rhea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A future for SQL on the web]]></title>
        <id>https://jlongster.com/future-sql-web</id>
        <link href="https://jlongster.com/future-sql-web"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T14:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physicists Create a Bizarre ‘Wigner Crystal’ Made Purely of Electrons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/physicists-create-a-bizarre-wigner-crystal-made-purely-of-electrons-20210812/</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/physicists-create-a-bizarre-wigner-crystal-made-purely-of-electrons-20210812/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T14:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch YC S21: Meet the Batch, Thread #6]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28156460</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28156460"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T14:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Deep Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://sebastianraschka.com/blog/2021/dl-course.html</id>
        <link href="https://sebastianraschka.com/blog/2021/dl-course.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T13:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter's new font, Chirp, is apparently giving some users headaches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnet.com/news/twitters-new-font-chirp-is-apparently-giving-some-users-headaches/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnet.com/news/twitters-new-font-chirp-is-apparently-giving-some-users-headaches/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T13:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Figma Plugins And Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/Figma-tools-plugins-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/Figma-tools-plugins-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Figma plugins that will help you fix all the little slowdowns and boost your productivity. From color management and image assets to SVG shapes and animation. That’s our new guide to Figma.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Janet John)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FastAPI Course – Code APIs Quickly]]></title>
        <id>610aec303306a507d1bfdf07</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fastapi-helps-you-develop-apis-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T13:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FastAPI makes it quicker and easier to develop APIs with Python. We just published a crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use FastAPI.  Tomi Tokko developed this course. Tomi has made many popular courses both on his own channel and the freeCodeCamp]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darts: A Python library for easy manipulation and forecasting of time series]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/unit8co/darts</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/unit8co/darts"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T12:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life Improvements Since the 1990s]]></title>
        <id>https://www.gwern.net/Improvements</id>
        <link href="https://www.gwern.net/Improvements"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T11:52:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Value?]]></title>
        <id>https://dwyer.co.za/what-is-value.html</id>
        <link href="https://dwyer.co.za/what-is-value.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T11:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Strong Law of Small Numbers [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.maa.org/sites/default/files/pdf/upload_library/22/Ford/Guy697-712.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://www.maa.org/sites/default/files/pdf/upload_library/22/Ford/Guy697-712.pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T11:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book Review: Your Computer Is on Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theregister.com/2021/08/06/your_computer_is_on_fire_review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.theregister.com/2021/08/06/your_computer_is_on_fire_review/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T11:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typography in Alien (2014)]]></title>
        <id>https://typesetinthefuture.com/2014/12/01/alien/</id>
        <link href="https://typesetinthefuture.com/2014/12/01/alien/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T10:32:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MathML Progress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.igalia.com/2021/08/09/MathML-Progress.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.igalia.com/2021/08/09/MathML-Progress.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-12T10:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary Search Tree Algorithms for JavaScript Beginners]]></title>
        <id>61025c793306a507d1bfad64</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-tree-algorithms-for-javascript-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T23:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently had the chance to teach high school students how to code. There are not that many beginner-friendly tutorials on algorithms coded in JavaScript which is the language they were learning. So I decided to make one. In this article, I will try my best to explain some core]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement iOS-Specific Components and APIs]]></title>
        <id>610d4a303306a507d1bff2ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-ios-components-apis/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T23:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the end goals of a React Native project is to have a minimal amount of platform-specific logic and code. Most APIs can be built so the platform-specific code is abstracted away by the framework. This gives you a single way to interact with them and easily create cross-platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wanna see a whiter white?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346388</id>
        <link href="https://kidi.ng/wanna-see-a-whiter-white/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T19:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heck of a CSS trick here from Dongsung Kim. 
There are hidden HDR videos playing at the corners of this page. When a HDR-capable browser encounters one, it switches to HDR mode. For some reason, CSS backdrop-filter + brightness >100% 
…
The post Wanna see a whiter white? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Static vs. Dynamic vs. Jamstack: Where’s The Line?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345889</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/static-vs-dynamic-vs-jamstack-wheres-the-line/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T14:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll often hear developers talking about “static” vs. “dynamic” sites, or you may have heard someone use the term Jamstack. What do these terms mean, and when does a “static” site become either a Jamstack or dynamic site? These …
The post Static vs. Dynamic vs. Jamstack: Where’s The Line? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Neumegen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Napkin]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346384</id>
        <link href="https://www.napkin.io/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T14:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We took a surface level look at Pipedream the other day, which really does look cool. It’s like a much more modern and fancy version of what Yahoo Pipes was. A better comparison might be Zapier, except you …
The post Napkin appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Smashing Workshops on Front-End & Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/new-smashing-online-workshops-aug-oct-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/new-smashing-online-workshops-aug-oct-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we build and establish a successful, bulletproof design system? What’s the state of HTML Email? And what are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s find out. With our [brand new online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) on front-end & design — to help us all boost skills online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Machine Stops (1909) [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://web.cs.ucdavis.edu/~rogaway/classes/188/materials/the%20machine%20stops.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://web.cs.ucdavis.edu/~rogaway/classes/188/materials/the%20machine%20stops.pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T12:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Origins of Political Order Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6720</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-origins-of-political-order-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-origins-of-political-order-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Origins of Political Order emphasizes how the historical development of political systems worldwide can be traced back to the natural inclination of humans to favor blood relationships. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Human nature is a curious thing. We all have different aspirations, principles, various perspectives on life, yet we’re […]
The post The Origins of Political Order Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling Mounting And Unmounting Of Navigation Routes In React Native]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/mounting-unmounting-navigation-routes-react-native/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/mounting-unmounting-navigation-routes-react-native/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often you need two different sets of navigation stacks for pre and post user authentication. Usually, to see more content, you have to be authenticated in some way. Let’s look at how to mount and unmount navigation stack based on a met condition in React Native.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Don)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View Source (on Mobile)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346392</id>
        <link href="https://neatnik.net/view-source/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wished you could see the HTML source of a web page while on a mobile browser, which generally doesn’t offer that feature? If you have a desktop machine around, there are ways, but what I mean …
The post View Source (on Mobile) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible Markdown in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345861</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsible-markdown-in-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown truly is a great format. It’s close enough to plain text so that anyone can quickly learn it, and it’s structured enough that it can be parsed and eventually converted to you name it.
That being said: parsing, processing, …
The post Responsible Markdown in Next.js appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kitty Giraudel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WooCommerce With Apple Pay and Google Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345799</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/woocommerce-with-apple-pay-and-google-pay/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Got a WooCommerce store? It behooves you to offer a variety of payment methods. Just anecdotally, I’m sure both you and me have been annoyed and even abandoned purchases when a merchant, online or …
The post WooCommerce With Apple Pay and Google Pay appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Nesting, specificity, and you]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346355</id>
        <link href="https://kilianvalkhof.com/2021/css-html/css-nesting-specificity-and-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Kilian Valkhof on CSS nesting which isn’t available in browsers yet, but will be soon. There are a few differences he notes between CSS nesting and nesting in Sass or Less though. Take, for example, the following code:
div 
…
The post CSS Nesting, specificity, and you appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cookieless Alternative To Embed HTML, CSS And JS Code Snippets]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/cookieless-alternative-embed-html-css-js-code-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/cookieless-alternative-embed-html-css-js-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embedding code examples with third-party scripts often leads to tracking or cookies. We always wanted to have a simple website with a good UX, so setting cookies for no reason wasn’t an option for us. Now, with Indiepen, we are proud to introduce a privacy-friendly alternative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Henrik Fricke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 41 With Eva PenzeyMoog: Designing For Safety]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/smashing-podcast-episode-41/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/smashing-podcast-episode-41/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about designing for safety. What does it mean to consider vulnerable users in our designs? Drew McLellan talks to expert Eva PenzeyMoog to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choice Words about the Upcoming Deprecation of JavaScript Dialogs]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346368</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/choice-words-about-the-upcoming-deprecation-of-javascript-dialogs/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It might be the very first thing a lot of people learn in JavaScript:
alert("Hello, World");
One day at CodePen, we woke up to a ton of customer support tickets about their Pens being broken, which ultimately boiled down to …
The post Choice Words about the Upcoming Deprecation of JavaScript Dialogs appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Large, Small, and Dynamic Viewports]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346316</id>
        <link href="https://www.bram.us/2021/07/08/the-large-small-and-dynamic-viewports/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got viewport units (e.g. vw, vh, vmin, vmax), and they are mostly pretty great. It’s cool to always have a unit available that is relative to the entire screen. But when you ask people what …
The post The Large, Small, and Dynamic Viewports appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the CSS Paint API: Image Fragmentation Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345642</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/exploring-the-css-paint-api-image-fragmentation-effect/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T14:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous article, I created a fragmentation effect using CSS mask and custom properties. It was a neat effect but it has one drawback: it uses a lot of CSS code (generated using Sass). This time I am …
The post Exploring the CSS Paint API: Image Fragmentation Effect appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kaizen Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6712</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/kaizen-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=kaizen-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T12:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Kaizen is Japanese for “change for the better” or “continuous improvement,” and is also the title of a book by Sarah Harvey which explains this business philosophy that has expanded into the personal growth arena to give a clear pathway to reaching your goals through consistent incremental changes. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post Kaizen Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/3 From A To Z: Core Concepts (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-core-concepts-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-core-concepts-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What exactly is HTTP/3? Why was it needed so soon after HTTP/2 (which was only finalized in 2015)? How can or should you use it? And especially, how does this improve web performance? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robin Marx)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Gobbler]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346259</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-gobbler/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T19:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great little project from Ross Moody: 
SVG Gobbler is a browser extension that finds the vector content on the page you’re viewing and gives you the option to download, optimize, copy, view the code, or export it as an image.
…
The post SVG Gobbler appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Nuxt Features past v2.10]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346290</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/new-nuxt-features-past-v2-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T15:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nuxt offers an incredible developer experience, with a lot of performance and application setup best practices baked in. In recent releases, they’ve been working on taking this developer experience to the next level, with some newer features that speed up …
The post New Nuxt Features past v2.10 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Drasner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Infinite Utility Helpers Using Inline CSS Custom Properties and calc()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345467</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/efficient-infinite-utility-helpers-using-inline-css-custom-properties-and-calc/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T14:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently wrote a very basic Sass loop that outputs several padding and margin utility classes. Nothing fancy, really, just a Sass map with 11 spacing values, looped over to create classes for both padding and margin on each side. …
The post Efficient Infinite Utility Helpers Using Inline CSS Custom Properties and calc() appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bounce Back Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6708</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/bounce-back-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=bounce-back-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Bounce Back is a book by Susan Kahn, a business coach who will teach you the psychology of resilience from the perspectives of Greek philosophy, Sigmund Freud, and modern neuroscience, so you can recover quickly from professional blunders of all kinds by changing your thinking. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: […]
The post Bounce Back Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Useful VSCode Extensions For Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code can be supercharged wuth hundreds of [VS Code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/). In this article, Leonardo shares four useful extensions that help him in his daily work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Disabled Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we make disabled buttons more inclusive? When do they work well, and when do they fail on us? And finally, when do we actually need them, and how can we avoid them? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Socialism Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6696</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/socialism-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=socialism-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Socialism by Michael Newman outlines the history of the governmental theory that everything should be owned and controlled by the community as a whole, including how this idea has impacted the world in the last 200 years, how its original aims have been lost, and ways we might use it in the future. Read in: […]
The post Socialism Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Children And Iteration Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll discuss and learn about the use case of iterating over React `children` and the ways to do it. In particular, we will deep dive into one of the utility methods, `React.Children.toArray`, that React gives us, which helps to iterate over the children in a way which ensures performance and determinism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arihant Verma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How fast can you pipe a large file to a C++ program?]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19429</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/08/03/how-fast-can-you-pipe-a-large-file-to-a-c-program/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T17:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under many operating systems, you can send data from from one process to another using ‘pipes’. The term ‘pipe’ is probably used by analogy with plumbing and we often use the the symbol ‘|‘ to represent a pipe (it looks like a vertical pipe). Thus, for example, you can sort a file and send it … Continue reading How fast can you pipe a large file to a C++ program?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Resilient JavaScript UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resilience is intrinsic to the web and therefore us, web developers. This article explores how graceful degradation, defensive coding, observability, and a healthy attitude towards failures better equips us before, during, and after an error occurs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Callum Hart)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goals! Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6694</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/goals-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=goals-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T12:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Goals! By Brian Tracy shows you how to unleash the power of goal setting to help you get or become whatever you want, identifying ways to set goals that lead you to success by being specific, challenging yourself, thinking positively, preparing, adjusting your timelines on big goals, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite […]
The post Goals! Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Strategy, Regression Testing And Maintenance (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a deep dive into the refactoring process itself, and cover incremental refactoring strategy, visual regression testing, and maintaining the refactored codebase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19419</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/31/science-and-technology-links-july-31st-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T19:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers built a microscope that might be 10 times better than the best available microscopes. Subsidizing college education can lower earnings due to lower job experience: The Post 9/11 GI Bill (PGIB) is among the largest and most generous college subsidies enacted thus far in the U.S. (…) the introduction of the PGIB raised college … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes In August (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2021. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6687</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/now-discover-your-strengths-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=now-discover-your-strengths-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Now, Discover Your Strengths shows you how to find your top five strengths by outlining what strengths are, how you get them, why they’re important to reaching your full potential, and how to discover your own through analyzing the times when your behavior is the most natural or instinctive and why. Read in: 4 […]
The post Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An E-Commerce Site With Angular 11, Commerce Layer And Paypal]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having an e-commerce store is crucial for any store owner as more and more customers are turning to online shopping. In this tutorial, we shall go through how to create an e-commerce site with Angular 11. The site will use the Commerce Layer as a headless e-commerce API and use Paypal to process payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19408</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/29/measuring-memory-usage-virtual-versus-real-memory/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T21:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developers are often concerned with the memory usage of their applications, and rightly so. Software that uses too much memory can fail, or be slow. Memory allocation will not work the same way under all systems. However, at a high level, most modern operating systems have virtual memory and physical memory (RAM). When you write … Continue reading Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Such Thing As A CSS Absolute Unit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are absolute units? What are the differences between relative and absolute units, and how do we create accurate sizes on the web? In this article, Elad Shechter explains why CSS absolute units aren’t so absolute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elad Shechter)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Democracies Die Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6683</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-democracies-die-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-democracies-die-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How Democracies Die explores the foundational ideas of democracy by looking at historical events, especially in Latin America, that show how democracies have failed, whether it can happen again, and how to protect democracy from threats like mutual toleration, inequality, and political parties. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: When Donald […]
The post How Democracies Die Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating An Accessible Dialog From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dialogs are everywhere in modern interface design (for good or for bad), and yet many of them are not accessible to assistive technologies. In this article, we will dig into how to create a short script to create accessible dialogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kitty Giraudel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global vs. Local Styling In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has strong opinions about how to organize JavaScript but not CSS. How can we develop patterns that encourage best CSS practices while also following the framework’s logic? The answer is surprisingly simple — to write well-structured CSS that balances global and local styling concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Dubovoy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kindness Method Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6677</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-kindness-method-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-kindness-method-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T12:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Kindness Method by Shahroo Izadi teaches how self-compassion and understanding make forming habits easier than being hard on yourself, using the personal experiences of the author and what she’s learned as an addiction recovery therapist to show how self-esteem is the true key to behavior change. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post The Kindness Method Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Serverless Functions And The International Space Station]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby recently announced the launch of “functions”. In this article, Paul Scanlon explains how to get the current location of the International Space Station (ISS) as it orbits the Earth in real-time using [Gatsby Functions](https://www.gatsbyjs.com/docs/reference/functions/) and then display it on a 3D interactive globe using [React Three Fibre](https://github.com/pmndrs/react-three-fiber).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soundtracks Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6665</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/soundtracks-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=soundtracks-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T12:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Soundtracks is New York Times bestselling author Jon Acuff’s 2021 book that teaches you how to beat overthinking by challenging whether your thoughts are true, retiring unhelpful and unkind ideas, adopting thought-boosting mantras from others, using symbols to reinforce positive thoughts, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Is there […]
The post Soundtracks Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Attracting Clients To Your Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many web design agencies consider it a badge of honor that they win work exclusively through word-of-mouth recommendations. In this article, Paul Boag explains why that is entirely the wrong attitude and what to do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Time To Your Schedule As A Professional]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you running a business and have too many things going on at once? Meetings, bugs, customer feedback, new clients in addition to your already tight deadlines? Let’s face it, time management is hard, and it becomes even more difficult in the trying times we are in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[75 Hard Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6657</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/75-hard-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=75-hard-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: 75 Hard is a fitness challenge and book that teaches mental toughness by making you commit to five daily critical tasks for 75 days straight, including drinking a gallon of water, reading 10 pages of a non-fiction book, doing two 45-minute workouts, taking a progress picture, and following a diet. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post 75 Hard Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? We’ve collected some useful color tools and resources that we’ve discovered lately — to help you get the most out of your creativity. We’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [accessible front-end components](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/complete-guide-accessible-front-end-components/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From WordPress To A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at when it makes sense to migrate from a monolithic project to a headless setup and the benefits that come with it. In addition to a step-by-step guide on how to migrate WordPress to Storyblok Headless CMS, the problems that will arise during the process and how to deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining End-To-End Quality With Visual Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding visual elements to your tests, you can gain more options to add meaningful ways in maintaining a high level of quality for your app. Colby Fayock explains how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Colby Fayock)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Insights I Gained While Researching Vue.js Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web app accessibility appears difficult because it seems that there is little information on the subject available online. Let’s take a closer look at the accessible use of framework features, concrete Vue.js traits, as well as community initiatives and vetted patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISR vs DPR: Big Words, Quick Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two strategies for incrementally building websites that are growing in popularity: Incremental Static Regeneration and Distributed Persistent Rendering. What’s the difference? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cassidy Williams)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Do That With A JavaScript Data Grid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll get to see some pretty groundbreaking things you can achieve with modern JavaScript grids and discover new ways to augment a data grid to make it engaging, responsive, and accessible. All this will be illustrated using Kendo UI Data Grids and their features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19380</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/14/faster-sorted-array-unions-by-reducing-branches/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing an index, a database or a search engine, you frequently need to compute the union of two sorted sets. When I am not using fancy low-level instructions, I have most commonly computed the union of two sorted sets using the following approach: v1 = first value in input 1 v2 = first value … Continue reading Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Broken Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Too often dealing with filters can be frustrating. Let’s get them right. That means never freeze the UI on a single input, provide text input fallback and never auto-scroll users on a single input. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>