<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-07-13T01:00:01.911Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-07-13T01:00:01.911Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving From Dev to CEO w/ Stephen Magill]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linearb/evolving-from-dev-to-ceo-w-stephen-magill-8n3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linearb/evolving-from-dev-to-ceo-w-stephen-magill-8n3"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T00:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most prolific companies of our time are run by former developers. 
That’s why on this week's episode of Dev Interrupted we bring in former-developer-turned-CEO, Stephen Magill of Muse.dev, to chat about what it takes to make the jump from developer to business leader.
Listen to the full episode







  
  
  Episode Highlights include:



Why more companies are being led by former developers
The pros and cons of having a technical vs communication background
What Stephen wishes he knew before taking on a leadership role
Great advice for developers who aspire to become business leaders
Join the Dev Interrupted Discord Server


With over 1200 members, the Dev Interrupted Discord Community is the best place for Engineering Leaders to engage in daily conversation. No sales people allowed. Join the community >>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Bronsdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNDERSTANDING CALLBACKS, PROMISES, GENERATORS AND ASYNC/AWAIT]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mcube25/understanding-callbacks-promises-generators-and-async-await-j1c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mcube25/understanding-callbacks-promises-generators-and-async-await-j1c"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T00:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are few fields in JavaScript that provide an equal amount of possible solutions and tools to the handling of asynchronous code. There is a reason for the existence  of the vast amount of tools. Handling asynchronous code in a readable and manageable way has always been challenging in JavaScript. We are going to try to understand callbacks, promises, generators and async await so as to know when to use each tool and how they actually differ.
Callbacks are the oldest and simplest way to deal with asynchronous code in JavaScript. Callbacks are also known as higher order functions. They functions passed into functions and they are executed at some point. let us have a look at an example code
let x = function () {
    console.log("i am called from inside a function");
};

let y = function…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Muhktar Musa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free resources to master algorithms & data structure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/free-resources-to-master-algorithms-data-structure-2nfj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/free-resources-to-master-algorithms-data-structure-2nfj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T23:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, this is #day_30 which is the end of the series of data structure and algorithms, we talked about many types of data strucutre (linear and non-linear) such as stacks, queues, hash tables, heaps ,linked list, additionnaly, we discussed not only sorting algorithms like merge sort and quick sort, but also searching algorithms such as binary search, linear search, as well as interpolation search.


In this post, I'm going to share with you the most useful and helpful resources to study & master data structure and algorithms.
The Algorithm Design Manual by Steve S. Skiena
Introduction to Algorithm by Thomas H. Cormen
Grokking Algorithms: An illustrated guide for programmers and other curious people by Aditya Bhargava
Data Structure and Algorithms in Java by Robert Lafore
 Algorithms in a nutshell: A Practical Guide by George T.Heineman
Data Structures and Algorithms Made Easy
Algorithms by Sanjoy Dasgupta
Advanced Data Structures by Peter Brass
 Youtube

 Udemy

 Coursera

 EDx

 Geeksforgeeks

 Javatpoint

 Programiz

 FreeCodeCamp

 Tutorialspoint

 Hackerearth

 Medium




  
  
  Free courses to learn data structure and algorithms




Data structure & algorithms for beginners (1h)
Intro to data structure from freecodecamp (3h)
Introduction to data structure & algorithms by treehouse (5h)
Data Structures Easy to Advanced Course - Full Tutorial from a Google Engineer (8h)
Data structure using C & C++ (10h)
small introduction to data structure and algorithms by CS Dojo (13 video)
introduction to data structure and algorithms by Caleb Curry (17 video)
data structure using C++ (94 video)
Data structure and algorithms playlist (112 video)
If you have any additional resources to add to this post let us know in the comments section, please.
Have an amazing day!
telegram]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Bouchiha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schrödinger's Code]]></title>
        <id>https://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?id=3468263</id>
        <link href="https://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?id=3468263"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T23:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Positive Energy Warp Drive from Hidden Geometric Structures]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2104.06488</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2104.06488"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T23:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Approved fracking compounds can form PFAS a.k.a. “forever chemicals”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/12/climate/epa-pfas-fracking-forever-chemicals.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/12/climate/epa-pfas-fracking-forever-chemicals.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T23:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Borgs are giant extrachromosomal elements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2021.07.10.451761v1?rss=1</id>
        <link href="https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2021.07.10.451761v1?rss=1"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T23:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Compose vs Kubernetes Development Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loft/docker-compose-vs-kubernetes-development-tools-3n1f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loft/docker-compose-vs-kubernetes-development-tools-3n1f"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T22:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Kasper Siig
When getting started with Docker, many developers quickly turn to Docker Compose to run their applications. Compose offers many advantages, such as having your configuration stored as code, making it easy to maintain and expand upon. Unfortunately, although it is possible to use Compose with Kubernetes, it's not the recommended approach.
Devs will often bang their head against the wall trying to make this scenario work when they start using Kubernetes, without knowing that there's a better way. After all, they have become used to Compose and have integrated it deeply into their workflow. It can be hard to let go.
This article will go over why it's best to leave Compose out of Kubernetes, and give resources to help you with improving your workflow without it. You'll be introd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rich Burroughs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Ross and the “Fundamental Attribution Error”]]></title>
        <id>https://nonzero.substack.com/p/ode-to-a-world-saving-idea-f4b</id>
        <link href="https://nonzero.substack.com/p/ode-to-a-world-saving-idea-f4b"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T22:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of Nomography]]></title>
        <id>https://kartsci.org/kocomu/computer-history/the-art-of-nomography/</id>
        <link href="https://kartsci.org/kocomu/computer-history/the-art-of-nomography/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T22:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filter array with multiple conditions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/itushthegiant/filter-array-with-multiple-conditions-5928</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/itushthegiant/filter-array-with-multiple-conditions-5928"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ive been working on my first "React" project and this project I build is a "Park Browser" which is basically an app that helps you search for a specific national park in USA either by address, city or state.

It was really hard to understand how can I filter through an array with multiple conditions and also pass those conditions from a child component to parent.

Parent:

Child:

It seemed like its working but there was another problem,

It is pretty simple what the "continue" method does,
It helped me a-lot with understanding how to pass data from child to parent and how to use multiple conditions to filter and array.
I hope this post helped you with your errors,
Good Luck!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Etamar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Java Applications Today: July 12, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ksilz/how-to-build-java-applications-today-july-12-2021-4im4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ksilz/how-to-build-java-applications-today-july-12-2021-4im4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR


TIOBE Index July 2021, Spring blesses GraphQL, tuning Hibernate’s query plan cache, GitHub previews AI coding assistant, Quarkus 2.0.1, Spring Cloud Hoxton.SR12, and a terrible chart.
This is issue 44 of my weekly newsletter, “How To Build Java Applications Today”. I read all the Java newsletters, so you don’t have to! And it’s “Java news with a smile”.
If you like my newsletter, then subscribe to it on Substack! Or read it on dev.to,  the Java Cafe, or Medium. Even better: Share it with people who may be interested.
If everything seems under control, you're not going fast enough‌.
Mario Andretti, American race car driver (born 1940), encourages us to release faster. Or so I think.
My host country England lost the European Football Championship to Italy last night (that’s soccer fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karsten Silz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Chatbot with vanilla JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ugwutotheeshoes/build-a-chatbot-with-vanilla-javascript-5akn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ugwutotheeshoes/build-a-chatbot-with-vanilla-javascript-5akn"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:53:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I visited a website and while surfing through it, the website’s chatbot caught my attention. I had been looking for a new project to work on, so I got to researching how I could build a chatbot using vanilla JavaScript. While building this project from scratch I stumbled across a lot of difficulties based on the knowledge I had and when I say 'from scratch', I just mean I did not use any additional libraries or APIs while building. Part of this code is based on existing blog posts, articles, and YouTube videos. Also note that this project is more of an insight into JavaScript fundamentals, not any form of artificial intelligence (AI) or machine learning. The main prerequisite for understanding this article is the knowledge of HTML, CSS, and vanilla JavaScript.
Let’s create a fold…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmanuel Ugwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I run natively 'Big Commerce Stencil CLI' on Apple Silicon M1 Chip]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/caglaroptimum7/how-can-i-run-natively-big-commerce-stencil-cli-on-apple-silicon-m1-chip-3m1h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/caglaroptimum7/how-can-i-run-natively-big-commerce-stencil-cli-on-apple-silicon-m1-chip-3m1h"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am a front-end engineer who mostly works on a Bigcommerce platform. Bigcommerce uses a handlebar with the 'stencil command line interface' and it requires 'node version manager' (nvm).
I switched my Intel Macbook Pro with M1 Chip Macbook Pro then I couldn't realize this migration will be a little bit ticky.
I installed homebrew then node and nvm packages then I followed the steps on bigcommerce developer website. 
However, almost every project gives different errors but all of them are related to the 'node' version. I've gotten few-hour research on Google but these were not about BigCommerce 'stencil-cli',
Jump to 'TL;DR'
# For ARM based macs // for bash
arch -x86_64 /bin/zsh

# For ARM based macs // for Fish Shell
arch -x86_64 /usr/local/bin/fish

brew install node
brew install nvm

# which is LTS for v12
nvm install 12.13.0
nvm alias default 12.13.0
npm install -g @bigcommerce/stencil-cli

Then start your project with
stencil start -o


Please check out our website to get more information about BigCommerce Development and Marketing.
Thanks for reading, Happy hacking 🧡]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caglar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to change details label when open/closed without JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rouilj/how-to-change-details-label-when-open-closed-without-javascript-1n3c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rouilj/how-to-change-details-label-when-open-closed-without-javascript-1n3c"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wish the details element would support different labels (provided by the summary tag) for its open and closed states.
Consider a label of "Closed, click to open" when the details element is closed and "Open, click to close" when open:

Sadly only one summary tag is supported by the details element. However you can use an empty summary with a ::before pseudo-element to implement this.
Save the following to a file:
<html>
  <body>
  <style>
    #widget1 div { padding-inline-start: 1em; max-width: 20em;}
    #widget1 summary::before { content: "Closed, click to open";}
    #widget1[open] summary::before { content: "Open, click to close";}
    #widget1[open] summary { height: 2em;}
  </style>

  <p> Text before details.</p>
  <details id="widget1">
    <summary></summary>
    <div>
    A widget can be in one of two states. The default closed
    state displays only the triangle and the label inside summary
    (or a user agent-defined default string if no summary).
    </div>
  </details>
  <p>Text after details.</p>
  <body>
</html>

to experiment.
Note that it might not be accessible. I didn't try to see if adding a live region aria label to the summary would cause the label change to be announced. I suspect it will not, but refining this is left as an exercise for the reader. Add your experimental findings to the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Rouillard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is AWS Infinidash?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/what-is-aws-infinidash-a5k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/what-is-aws-infinidash-a5k"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of today, AWS offers over 200 products and services with its own, unique name and functionality. Getting familiar with them is not an easy task and most AWS professionals only keep up to date with them in their respective fields. For example, if you are managing containers there are currently 17 ways to run them on AWS. This means 17 different services with their own and different pricing models.
On June 30, 2021, Joe Nash raised the question on Twitter about what happens if a small and dedicated group of developers start tweeting about a made-up AWS product. Would it appear in job specifications within a week? He suggested the word Infinidash but was open to other suggestions. He made it clear that “the intended joke here was that AWS product brands are completely impenetrable and indi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mishi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are the Interface predicate and Interface functions?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wagnernegrao/what-are-the-interface-predicate-and-interface-functions-36o7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wagnernegrao/what-are-the-interface-predicate-and-interface-functions-36o7"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing the post about Consumer Interface, I thought it interesting to write about Predicate Interface and  Function Interface.
We go to start with Predicate Interface, this interface is an interface functional a little different from Consumer Interface that receives a parameter and does not return anything. The Predicate interface receives a parameter and returns a value boolean. The function that an interface receives is primarily some comparison that can have with returns a boolean.
see an example:
List<Integer> numbers = Arrays.asList(1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10);


numbers.stream().filter((c) -> (c % 2) == 0)

In the example above, we have a creation of a list and after that is created a filter to know what the pair numbers are. I'm using this example because the method 'filter' receives an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wagner Negrão</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Card on File with React Native]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mootrichard/card-on-file-with-react-native-4b3e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mootrichard/card-on-file-with-react-native-4b3e"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we’ll show you how to accept payments in a React Native application using Square’s In-App Payments SDK and React Native plugin. I’ll also show you how to safely store customer card details so that they don’t have to be manually re-entered or re-swiped for future transactions.
In payment industry terms, this capability is known as Card on File, or CoF for short. For frequent transactions, e.g. ordering a Lyft or a Lime, having a card stored makes for a much snappier, lower-friction in-app user experience. Entering card details every time would be very tedious.

As a security-minded developer, I know you might be wondering: Is it safe to store a user’s credit card details? Is this even legal?
If you use Square, the answer is yes. Using the Square In-App Payments (IAP) SDK m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Moot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qventus (YC W15) is hiring a senior data scientist to help solve healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://jobs.lever.co/qventus/2f0ee88c-89aa-4374-b724-87bffd5a2086</id>
        <link href="https://jobs.lever.co/qventus/2f0ee88c-89aa-4374-b724-87bffd5a2086"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s $16k Quote for a $700 Fix Is Why Right to Repair Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thedrive.com/news/41493/teslas-16000-quote-for-a-700-fix-is-why-right-to-repair-matters</id>
        <link href="https://www.thedrive.com/news/41493/teslas-16000-quote-for-a-700-fix-is-why-right-to-repair-matters"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T20:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TinyPICO – tiny fully-featured ESP32 board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tinypico.com/</id>
        <link href="https://www.tinypico.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T20:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defender (1981) by Eugene Jarvis and Sam Dicker]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/mwenge/defender</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/mwenge/defender"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T19:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet `:has`, A Native CSS Parent Selector]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344355</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The reasons that are often cited that make container queries difficult or impossible is things like infinite loops—e.g. changing the width of an element, invalidating a container query, which changes the width again, which makes the container query take effect, …
The post Meet `:has`, A Native CSS Parent Selector appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Website is hosted on an Casio fx-9750GII Calculator]]></title>
        <id>http://fxip.as203478.net/</id>
        <link href="http://fxip.as203478.net/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T19:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use the 'tail' command to monitor everything]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.robertelder.org/intro-to-tail-command/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.robertelder.org/intro-to-tail-command/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T19:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Turing in America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.privatdozent.co/p/alan-turing-in-america-221</id>
        <link href="https://www.privatdozent.co/p/alan-turing-in-america-221"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T18:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contrastive Representation Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://lilianweng.github.io/lil-log/2021/05/31/contrastive-representation-learning.html</id>
        <link href="https://lilianweng.github.io/lil-log/2021/05/31/contrastive-representation-learning.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T17:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temozolomide Is Explosive]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.sciencemag.org/pipeline/archives/2021/07/12/temozolimide-is-explosive</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.sciencemag.org/pipeline/archives/2021/07/12/temozolimide-is-explosive"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T17:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Suplias (YC S21) – B2B inventory for mom and pop stores in Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27812565</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27812565"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T17:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Build Toys]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.aaronkharris.com/why-build-toys</id>
        <link href="https://blog.aaronkharris.com/why-build-toys"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T16:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heirloom]]></title>
        <id>https://silashouseblog.blogspot.com/2021/06/heirloom.html</id>
        <link href="https://silashouseblog.blogspot.com/2021/06/heirloom.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T14:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the Specificity of :where() as a CSS Reset]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343613</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-the-specificity-of-where-as-a-css-reset/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T14:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t know about you, but I write these three declarations many times in my CSS:
ul {
  padding: 0;
  margin: 0;
  list-style-type: none;
}
You might yell at me and say I can just put those in my CSS …
The post Using the Specificity of :where() as a CSS Reset appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mojtaba Seyedi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handwriting is better than typing when learning a new language, study finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencealert.com/handwriting-is-better-than-typing-when-learning-to-read-study-finds</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencealert.com/handwriting-is-better-than-typing-when-learning-to-read-study-finds"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T14:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updating the Go Memory Model]]></title>
        <id>https://research.swtch.com/gomm</id>
        <link href="https://research.swtch.com/gomm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T14:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Use SPSS to Explore and Analyze Data]]></title>
        <id>60e753aa134ad707be00f2c1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/spss-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SPSS Statistics is a software package used for interactive, or batched, statistical analysis. We just released a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the popular statistical application SPSS from IBM. This course provides a concise overview of how you can use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Introduction (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS refactoring is not an easy task — it needs to be done in a way that doesn't create problems. First we need to analyze the existing codebase, audit CSS codebase health, discover weaknesses, agree on the approach, and convince management to invest time and resources into the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feel Great Lose Weight Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6571</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/feel-great-lose-weight-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=feel-great-lose-weight-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Feel Great Lose Weight by Dr. Rangan Chatterjee is a book that goes beyond fad diets and quick fixes for weight problems and instead dives into the science of how your body really works when you put food into it and how you can use this information to be fitter and feel better. Read […]
The post Feel Great Lose Weight Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI vs ML – What’s the Difference Between Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning?]]></title>
        <id>60e981aae8ee9b08300ed1ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-vs-ml-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T11:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence and machine learning are two popular and often hyped terms these days. And people often use them interchangeably to describe an intelligent software or system.  But even though both AI and ML are based on statistics and mathematics, they are not the same thing. In this article, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organic and regenerative agriculture are revitalizing rural Montana economies]]></title>
        <id>https://montanafreepress.org/2021/07/06/regenerative-agriculture-evitalizing-rural-montana-economies/</id>
        <link href="https://montanafreepress.org/2021/07/06/regenerative-agriculture-evitalizing-rural-montana-economies/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T11:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google BigQuery Beginner&#x27;s Guide – How to Analyze Large Datasets]]></title>
        <id>60e76d88134ad707be00f347</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-bigquery-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T11:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gone are the days of storing your data in a CSV file or an Excel spreadsheet. If you want to quickly analyze millions of data rows in seconds, BigQuery is the way to go. In this getting started guide, we'll learn about BigQuery and how we can use it to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risk Assessment of GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://gist.github.com/0xabad1dea/be18e11beb2e12433d93475d72016902</id>
        <link href="https://gist.github.com/0xabad1dea/be18e11beb2e12433d93475d72016902"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T11:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 90 supports Fetch Metadata Request Headers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/security/2021/07/12/firefox-90-supports-fetch-metadata-request-headers/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/security/2021/07/12/firefox-90-supports-fetch-metadata-request-headers/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T10:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A piece of symbolic artwork created by Neanderthals: study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.livescience.com/neanderthal-symbolic-carving-germany.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.livescience.com/neanderthal-symbolic-carving-germany.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T07:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction to Medieval Geomancy (1999)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.princeton.edu/~ezb/geomancy/geohome.html</id>
        <link href="http://www.princeton.edu/~ezb/geomancy/geohome.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T04:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alfvenic reconnecting plasmoid thruster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/journal-of-plasma-physics/article/an-alfvenic-reconnecting-plasmoid-thruster/F296E45CC504E8FF2586EA79117E2514</id>
        <link href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/journal-of-plasma-physics/article/an-alfvenic-reconnecting-plasmoid-thruster/F296E45CC504E8FF2586EA79117E2514"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T01:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The B-52’s’ “Rock Lobster” brought John Lennon back to music (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://ultimateclassicrock.com/john-lennon-rock-lobster-b-52s/</id>
        <link href="https://ultimateclassicrock.com/john-lennon-rock-lobster-b-52s/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T18:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotting a cherry-picked paper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.notion.so/Spotting-a-cherry-picked-paper-19a91d062ef8481b964895a7a43c8429</id>
        <link href="https://www.notion.so/Spotting-a-cherry-picked-paper-19a91d062ef8481b964895a7a43c8429"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T07:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Year in the Metabolist Future of 1972 (2014)]]></title>
        <id>https://failedarchitecture.com/2014/06/a-year-in-the-metabolist-future-of-1972/</id>
        <link href="https://failedarchitecture.com/2014/06/a-year-in-the-metabolist-future-of-1972/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T06:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wielding lamps and torches shed new light on Stone Age cave art]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencenews.org/article/stone-age-cave-art-lighting-torch-lamp</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencenews.org/article/stone-age-cave-art-lighting-torch-lamp"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T05:51:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19369</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/10/science-and-technology-links-july-10th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use CRISPR, a state-of-the-art gene editing technique, to edit the genes of live human patients in a clinical trials. A clinical trial has begun regarding an HIV vaccine. If you choose to forgo meat to fight climate change, you may lower your individual’s lifetime warming contribution by 2 to 4%. Age-related testosterone loss may … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 React Libraries Every Project Should Use in 2021]]></title>
        <id>60e8864de8ee9b08300ecc3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-react-libraries-every-project-needs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T20:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are literally 100s of great React libraries to choose from, but which libraries do you need most for your React projects?  In this article, we're going to break down five libraries you need for your React projects. Each of them will cover virtually every major tool you need, plus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[:focus-visible in WebKit]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344334</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.igalia.com/mrego/2021/06/07/focus-visible-in-webkit-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a nice update from Manuel Rego Casasnovas. Igalia has this idea to sort of crowd-source important web platform features that need to get worked on (that’s the sort of work they do). They call it Open Prioritization. …
The post :focus-visible in WebKit appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What&#x27;s New in React 18? Concurrency, Batching, the Transition API and More]]></title>
        <id>60e81c50134ad707be00f79f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/whats-new-in-react-18/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! In this article, I'm going to show you what's new in the latest of version of React – React 18 – in under 8 minutes.  First, you might be wondering whether the latest set of changes will break anything with your current setup, or whether you will have to learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automatically Generate C# Code Snippets in Visual Studio]]></title>
        <id>60dcb93727f80207bcdbc17e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automatically-generate-code-snippets-visual-studio/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you use code snippets in Visual Studio, it can make your coding process a lot easier and faster. But what are code snippets? And how can you use them? In this article, we'll look at how you can create code snippets in C#. Just keep in mind that snippets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[760+ Free Online Programming &amp; Computer Science Courses You Can Start This July]]></title>
        <id>5f9c986d740569d1a4ca1a04</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-online-programming-cs-courses/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nine years ago, universities like MIT and Stanford first opened up free online courses to the public. Today, close to 1,000 schools around the world have created thousands of free online courses. I’ve compiled this list of 760+ such free online courses that you can start this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a NoSQL Database with RavenDB]]></title>
        <id>60ae6b0d11ffb70827ef7fe6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-nosql-database-with-ravendb/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T15:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you look at any website or application today, somewhere under the hood there is a database. After all, we live in the world of Big Data. And the volume of data is growing exponentially.  With so much data at hand, we need ever more sophisticated ways to store it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Favicons in Action]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343598</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-favicons-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T14:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever heard of favicons made with SVG? If you are a regular reader of CSS-Tricks, you probably have. But does your website actually use one?
The task is more non-trivial than you might think. As we will see in this …
The post SVG Favicons in Action appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philippe Bernard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Born To Win Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6553</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/born-to-win-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=born-to-win-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T12:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Born To Win is a book by Zig Ziglar and his son Tom Ziglar in which they explore how planning and preparation is the only way to win in life and shows you how to use these tools in combination with a vision for your life, goals, and thinking positively to become a winner […]
The post Born To Win Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making A Strong Case For Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility is often overlooked or bolted on to the end of a project. Let’s figure out how to implement and advocate for accessibility from the inception of a project to the release or handoff and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Todd Libby)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner JavaScript Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344024</id>
        <link href="https://wesbos.com/javascript"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T22:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wes has a heck of a set of “notes” for learning JavaScript. It’s organized like a curriculum, meaning if you teach JavaScript, you could do a lot worse. It’s actually more like 85 really fleshed-out blog posts organized into sections …
The post Beginner JavaScript Notes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Own Feature Toggle with Next.js and React in Under 30 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>60e59724134ad707be00e5d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-feature-toggles-in-next-js-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T17:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will show you how to build the Feature Toggle mechanism in your Next.JS application.  We are going to use Next.JS, React, and TypeScript. We will deploy our application to Vercel to demonstrate the real-life example. You can find the code and video in the summary at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Accessible Vue Applications]]></title>
        <id>60e3ae66134ad707be00dbdb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-accessible-vue-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T16:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing web pages used to involve writing HTML, CSS, and a little scripting code like JavaScript for functionality.  But over time, we've developed new and more advanced technologies and frameworks to create webpages. We now use things like reusable components, routing, and rendering to the document object model (DOM).  These]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Struggle to Use and Animate a Conic Gradient in SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343623</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/my-struggle-to-use-and-animate-a-conic-gradient-in-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T14:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wonderful company I work for, Payoneer, has a new logo, and my job was to recreate it and animate it for a loader component in our app. I’ll explain exactly how I did it, share the problems I …
The post My Struggle to Use and Animate a Conic Gradient in SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amit Sheen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Command Line Tool with Nodejs and Fauna]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343574</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-command-line-tool-with-nodejs-and-fauna/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T14:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Command line tools are one of the most popular applications we have today. We use command line tools every day, and they range from git, npm or yarn. Command line tools are very fast and useful for automating applications and …
The post Building a Command Line Tool with Nodejs and Fauna appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fortune Ikechi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hero Code Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6552</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-hero-code-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-hero-code-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T12:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Hero Code is Admiral William H. McRaven’s guide to becoming a hero, identifying the traits of real-life heroes through inspiring stories of bravery and determination, including many of McRaven’s own experiences as a four-star admiral and in his personal life. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: What is a hero? […]
The post The Hero Code Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools And Practices To Speed Up The Vue.js Development Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though Vue.js claims to have an approachable minimalist framework that can be incrementally adaptable, it can be a little bit overwhelming when starting as a Vue.js newbie. In this article, we’re looking at ways to make writing Vue.js a breeze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Uma Victor)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at Building with Astro]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343495</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-look-at-building-with-astro/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astro is a brand new framework for building websites. To me, the big thing is that it allows you to build a site like you’re using a JavaScript framework (and you are), but the output is a zero-JavaScript static site. …
The post A Look at Building with Astro appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Web’s Worst Default]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343388</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-webs-worst-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of great defaults when it comes to browsers and the web. Think about all the accessibility features that are baked into HTML so that you don’t have to do weird stuff, like this example from Manuel…
The post The Web’s Worst Default appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boundaries Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6551</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/boundaries-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=boundaries-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Boundaries explains, with the help of modern psychology and Christian ideals, how to improve your mental health and personal growth by establishing guidelines for self-care that include saying no more often and standing firm in your decisions rather than letting people walk all over you. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: […]
The post Boundaries Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Figma Interactive Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Components in Figma allows designers to create a component with states (hover, active, clicked, focus) and make it interactive so that every copy of the component will inherit those same interactions by default. Let’s explore how it can reduce the time and effort needed to create interactions for your mock-ups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emiliano Cicero)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Body Toggle]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343438</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/body-toggle/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I appreciate the clarity of this trick that Mikael Ainalem posted over on Reddit:
It’s a one-liner that toggles the class on the <body> so you can mock up different states and toggle between them on click.
<body onclick="this.classList.toggle("active");"
Could …
The post Body Toggle appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve got one question about Jetpack for you.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343560</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ive-got-one-question-about-jetpack-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And maybe an optional follow-up if you’re up for it.
Automattic, the makers of Jetpack and many other WordPress-y things, have sponsored my site (me = Chris Coyier; site = CSS-Tricks) for quite a while. I use Jetpack myself, …
The post I’ve got one question about Jetpack for you. appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dilemma of Naming Font Size Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343149</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-dilemma-of-naming-font-size-variables/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Normally, a project will have a set of pre-determined font sizes, usually as variables named in such a way that seeks some semblance of order and consistency. Any project of considerable size can use something like that. There are always …
The post The Dilemma of Naming Font Size Variables appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lexelius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Nothing Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6550</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/do-nothing-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=do-nothing-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T12:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Do Nothing explores the idea that our focus on being productive all the time is making us less effective because of how little rest we get, identifying how the consequences of overworking ourselves, and the benefits of taking time off, make a compelling argument that we should spend more time doing nothing. Read in: […]
The post Do Nothing Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an array of Headless CMSes out there. In this article, we delve into headless CMS features to satisfy your content editors, marketers and yourself as a developer. For the experience headless practitioner, this could be a checklist to see what’s new out there. For those starting out on their headless journey, this could be a guide on what to look for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emmanuel Tissera)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Explained Simply: Containers, Pods and Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/kubernetes-explained-simply-containers-pods-and-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T14:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you zone out every time someone mentions “Kubernetes,” “containers,” or “pods,” this article is for you. No complex diagrams involved!
As a front-end developer, you don’t have to know how to configure an infrastructure from scratch. However, if you …
The post Kubernetes Explained Simply: Containers, Pods and Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lari Maza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trigonometry in CSS and JavaScript: Beyond Triangles]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343671</id>
        <link href="https://tympanus.net/codrops/2021/06/04/trigonometry-in-css-and-javascript-beyond-triangles/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T14:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web design is such a rectangle-based design medium that literally any deviation from it feels fresh. Michelle Barker gets into using math in various ways to programmatically draw lines, shapes, and animations that end up looking both beautiful and have …
The post Trigonometry in CSS and JavaScript: Beyond Triangles appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bullet Journal Method Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6544</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-bullet-journal-method-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-bullet-journal-method-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T12:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Bullet Journal Method explains the unique system for organizing and taking notes that millions are using to be more productive, improve their mindfulness, prioritize tasks, schedule appointments, solidify ideas, and most of all, set goals, make plans to achieve them and track their progress. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: […]
The post The Bullet Journal Method Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HSL Colors In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ahmad Shadeed explains what HSL is, how to use it, and shares some of the useful use-cases and examples that you can use right away in your current projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fourteenth Fourth]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343496</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-fourteenth-fourth/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T13:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s CSS-Tricks birthday! Somehow that keeps coming around every year. It’s that time where I reflect upon that past year. It’s like the annual vibe check. 
I’m writing this just days after my current home state of Oregon has …
The post The Fourteenth Fourth appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Data Detective Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6524</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-data-detective-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-data-detective-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T12:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Data Detective will make you smarter by showing how you can understand statistics well enough to see how they, and the beliefs and cognitive biases they can make you have, make such a huge impact in your life, for better or for worse, and how to separate fact from fiction. Read in: 4 […]
The post The Data Detective Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Testing Flow As It Should Be]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many tools and approaches, email still has quite a few pain points, both for developers and email marketers. Email is difficult because it has too many aspects to set and a few instances with no common rules to follow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andriy Zapisotskyi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s A (Front-End Testing) Trap! Six Common Testing Pitfalls And How To Solve Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When writing front-end tests, you’ll find a lot of pitfalls along the way. Let’s explore common mistakes developers make, and how to avoid them. Testing doesn’t need to be painful, after all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6523</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/what-happened-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=what-happened-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: What Happened is Hillary Clinton’s post-mortem on the events and surprising result of her bid for the 2016 United States presidential election, including why she ran for president in the first place, what made it so hard for her to come out on top, and how the loss affected her after election night. Read […]
The post What Happened Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compressing JSON: gzip vs zstd]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19354</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/30/compressing-json-gzip-vs-zstd/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T20:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON is the de facto standard for exchanging data on the Internet. It is relatively simple text format inspired by JavaScript. I say “relatively simple” because you can read and understand the entire JSON specification in minutes. Though JSON is a concise format, it is also better used over a slow network in compressed mode. … Continue reading Compressing JSON: gzip vs zstd]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lives Of The Stoics Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6516</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/lives-of-the-stoics-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lives-of-the-stoics-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Lives Of The Stoics is Ryan Holiday’s latest book, in which he and co-author Stephen Hansel take a deep dive into the experiences and beliefs of some of the earliest philosophers and followers of stoic virtues like justice, courage, and temperance. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: The art of Stoicism […]
The post Lives Of The Stoics Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web Workers In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is single-threaded. This makes it increasingly hard to write smooth and responsive apps. Workers have a bad rep, but can be an important and useful tool in any web developer's toolbelt for these kinds of problems. Let’s get up to speed on Workers on the Web!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Surma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Shades Of July (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome July with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from around the world, they are available with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hood Feminism Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6513</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/hood-feminism-summary-and-review/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hood-feminism-summary-and-review"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Hood Feminism explores the idea that traditional feminism only seeks to improve life for white women and not all women, arguing that true equality and inclusivity means seeking to lift all women, including those of color. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Would you agree that feminism isn’t actually feminism until […]
The post Hood Feminism Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down Bulky Builds With Netlify And Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static Generation is great for performance — until the app gets too big and build-times go through the roof. Today, we’ll have a look at how Netlify’s fresh On-Demand Builders can fix that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 40 With Mike Cavaliere: What Is Chakra UI For React?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Chakra UI. What is it and how can it help with your React projects? Drew McLellan talks to expert Mike Cavaliere to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Custom Emmet Snippets In VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Manuel explains why Emmet is one of his favorite productivity tools for writing HTML and CSS, and how you can create custom Emmet snippets in Visual Studio Code to help you improve your front-end workflows even more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (June 26th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19349</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/26/science-and-technology-links-june-26th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T16:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reportedly, half of us own a smartphone. It is often reported that women or visible minority earn less money. However, ugly people are doing comparatively even more poorly. We have highly efficient and cheap solar panels. However, we must also quickly dispose of them after a few years which leads to trash. Handling an increasing … Continue reading Science and Technology links (June 26th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Multi-Author Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how we can connect different types of content in a Next.js application. With this technique, we can add any kind of one-to-one, one-to-many, or even many-to-many relationship to our projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dom Habersack)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run A UX Audit For A Major EdTech Platform (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a case study of how a UX audit affects a UI. It explains how a famous educational platform can be analyzed edX against Jakob Nielsen’s usability guidelines. To get started, Mark Lankmiller shares all of the criteria and metrics he used for his UX audit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mark Lankmilier)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: support an experimental template for YouTube feed 📺 Demo | Source

Aggregate content from any YouTube channel rss url https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=<replace_with_channel_id>
Videos are embedded via iframe and loading accelerated by youtube-lite-embed
Ads are reduced thanks to YouTube's policy for embedded videos 🙃
Works on mobile devices with butter smooth horizontal scroll.
Caveat: the template works only with YouTube content. You cannot mix textual RSS feed or other video sources such as Vimeo.
Changed: Default HTML template meta tag adjusted to match convention
Changed: sources in template data is now ordered by last update timestamp (as opposed to alphabetical)
Thank you @PiyushLosalka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long should you work on a problem ?]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19336</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/14/how-long-should-you-work-on-a-problem/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T21:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lev Reyzin says that working too long on a problem might be unproductive: I, personally, have diminishing (or negative?) returns to my creative work as I explicitly work on a problem past some amount of time. I often have insights coming to me out of nowhere while I’m relaxing or enjoying hobbies on nights or … Continue reading How long should you work on a problem ?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>