<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-29T00:55:00.663Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-29T00:55:00.663Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test ActionMailer `deliver_later` in RSpec Controller Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jbranchaud/test-actionmailer-deliverlater-in-rspec-controller-tests-44h7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jbranchaud/test-actionmailer-deliverlater-in-rspec-controller-tests-44h7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T00:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot can happen when a Rails controller action gets called. This includes transactional emails getting queued up for delivery. To ensure our controller's behavior stays consistent as our app evolves we can write RSpec tests.
Among other things these tests can ensure that transactional emails get queued for delivery at the appropriate times.
This post documents a couple different methods I've used for those tests.
ActionMailer::Base.deliveries


If you have your queue_adapter set to :inline, then a deliver_later will happen synchronously. So, the email will immediately end up in the deliveries box.
describe '#welcome' do
  it 'sends the welcome email to the user' do
    valid_params = { user_id: user.id }

    expect {
      post :invite, params: valid_params
    }.to change { ActionMailer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Branchaud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peloton Axes Free 'Just Run' Feature from Treadmill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pcmag.com/news/peloton-axes-free-just-run-feature-from-treadmill-bricking-it-for-non-subscribers</id>
        <link href="https://www.pcmag.com/news/peloton-axes-free-just-run-feature-from-treadmill-bricking-it-for-non-subscribers"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T00:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[part 4: insertion, search in binary search tree0]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/part-4-insertion-search-in-binary-search-tree-4h44</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/part-4-insertion-search-in-binary-search-tree-4h44"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T23:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hi, this is part 4 of the tree data structure we'll explain binary search tree operations with their implementation such as insertion, and search.
Let's say we want to insert 17 in this binary search tree.



        20
      /    \
    12      23
  /   \    /  \
7     15  21   35

Since 17 < 20, we will go to the left sub-tree.
17 > 12, we will go the right.
17 > 15 and the no more child in the right's why we will go to the right and insert it.
so this binary search tree above will be like this:



        20
      /     \
    12       23
  /   \     /  \
7     15   21   35
        \
         17

We need to know that the inserted node will be always one of the binary search tree leaves.
while the root is None(null) store the previous root in a variable 


if the previousRoot is less than …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Bouchiha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conviction to Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/commdao/conviction-to-code-1fph</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/commdao/conviction-to-code-1fph"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T23:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I reached a great milestone moment in this coding journey recently. 
For the past month and a half I've tried to buckle down on my routine and study habits. I know it's repeated often (and with good reason) to make your own projects. Don't only follow along in a tutorial. And I've been trying to stick to that. I've also started writing some of the code with pen and paper, hoping to have it be better ingrained.
But with coding being so different from most of the things I've done before, progress felt stagnant still. A little different from imposter syndrome, but I'd get frustrated and just wonder 
am I really ever going to be able to learn this coding stuff?
And then I remember, this feeling isn't so different at all. 
Well, I didn't come to that realization on my own. WebDevSimplified has …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>commdao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EVERYTHING About the Azure Pipelines Scale Set Agents (VMSS)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/everything-about-the-azure-pipelines-scale-set-agents-vmss-cp2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/everything-about-the-azure-pipelines-scale-set-agents-vmss-cp2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T23:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are going to cover everything you need to know about the Scale Set Agents in Azure Pipelines, and how to use them to make your builds more elastic and flexible.
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video with the whole explanation and demo, which to be fair is much more complete than this post.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/3oILIG4i71g
If you rather prefer reading, well... let's just continue :)
So, Scale Set Agents in Azure Pipelines.
As the name says those are agents that you can install and run in Azure Virtual Machine Scale Sets, or VMSS.
As such, they can be scaled horizontally automatically, to make your build faster, more elastic, and eventually more flexible.
But Dave, I hear you asking,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide 'CoderDave' Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many people don’t want to work unless it’s from home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vox.com/recode/22543409/remote-work-from-home-jobs-supply-demand-hiring-platforms</id>
        <link href="https://www.vox.com/recode/22543409/remote-work-from-home-jobs-supply-demand-hiring-platforms"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T23:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Your Cluster Swim]]></title>
        <id>https://bartoszsypytkowski.com/make-your-cluster-swim/</id>
        <link href="https://bartoszsypytkowski.com/make-your-cluster-swim/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T23:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple Test Reveals If Your Mental Images Are More Vivid Than Other People's]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencealert.com/this-simple-test-reveals-if-your-mental-images-are-more-vivid-than-other-people-s</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-simple-test-reveals-if-your-mental-images-are-more-vivid-than-other-people-s"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T22:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube reinstates Right Wing Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/youtube-reinstates-channel-devoted-exposing-conservative-extremism-rcna1286</id>
        <link href="https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/youtube-reinstates-channel-devoted-exposing-conservative-extremism-rcna1286"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T22:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System *Things]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343040</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/system-things/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T22:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think we’re all largely aware of named colors in CSS:
color: OldLace;
background: rebeccapurple;
I guess you’d just call those “named colors” in CSS. 
Those aren’t the only kind of named colors there are though. Some of them …
The post System *Things appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Router: empty paths, named outlets and a fix that came with Angular 11]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-router-empty-paths-named-outlets-and-a-fix-that-came-with-angular-11-1hbl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-router-empty-paths-named-outlets-and-a-fix-that-came-with-angular-11-1hbl"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T21:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to highlight the importance of a fix that came with the 11th version of Angular Router. We will do so by examining a scenario where the lack of that fix prevents an intuitive solution from working, as well as understanding why the fix in question solves the problem.

The reader doesn't need to have more than a basic knowledge of Angular Router. Although we will make use of some advanced concepts like UrlTree, UrlSegmentGroup, they will be briefly described before being applied.  
This article has been inspired by this Stack Overflow question.
Throughout the article we will not be using the example from the aforementioned Stack Overflow question. Instead, it will be a simpler example, so that it can better illustrate the problem we are trying to solve. Before g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrei Gatej</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working around the viewport-based fluid typography bug in Safari]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343139</id>
        <link href="https://www.sarasoueidan.com/blog/safari-fluid-typography-bug-fix/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T21:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sara digs into a bug I happened to have mentioned back in 2012 where fluid type didn’t resize when the browser window resized. Back then, it affected Chrome 20 and Safari 6, but the bug still persists today in Safari …
The post Working around the viewport-based fluid typography bug in Safari appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Securely Access Secret API keys using Netlify Functions in a React App]]></title>
        <id>60d61acc6e1a1407b6b0bd46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-access-secret-api-keys-using-netlify-functions-in-a-react-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T21:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to securely access secret API keys using Netlify functions in a React app.  Netlify provides rich features that help you easily deploy Single Page Applications built using frameworks like React, Vue and Angular among others. This takes away the burden of coding and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Vue.js to new JavaScript frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/logrocket/comparing-vue-js-to-new-javascript-frameworks-15hn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/logrocket/comparing-vue-js-to-new-javascript-frameworks-15hn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T21:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Written by Samson Omojola ✏️
As frontend design becomes increasingly important for the success of an application, the need to work with the best frontend framework has become more of a necessity.
Finding the best framework to solve specific problems within a project provides a better frontend design and user experience, helping brands and developers attract and keep more users.
For developers working in JavaScript, Vue has become a popular and well-established framework. However, different projects require different solutions, and finding an alternative to Vue can propel a project forward with increased speed, performance, and community.
In this post, we’ll compare Vue to Svelte, Riot, Hyperapp, and Alpine, some new, lesser-known JavaScript frameworks that have cultivated a following and p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Angelosanto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIRUM (YC W15) is hiring to make access to medicine more equitable]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27668040</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27668040"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T21:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy an NLP Model with FastAPI]]></title>
        <id>60d9766b6e1a1407b6b0cb4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-an-nlp-model-with-fastapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T20:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're working with Natural Language Processing, knowing how to deploy a model is one of the most important skills you'll need to have. Model deployment is the process of integrating your model into an existing production environment. The model will receive input and predict an output for decision-making for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL v/s REST -  Conclusion]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tbaveja/graphql-v-s-rest-conclusion-2mfk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tbaveja/graphql-v-s-rest-conclusion-2mfk"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T20:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The objective of this blog is to explain and determine which among the REST and GraphQL could be a best fit depending upon your requirement and use-case. Let's start !
If you're not aware of GraphQL, I would highly recommend you to checkout one of the below:
Awesome crash course by @eveporcello
 on Linkedin Learning
GraphQL Tutorial by Net Ninja on Youtube
GraphQL and REST essentially accomplish the same task, i.e., communicate with a server and retrieve data. Here are a few similarities between the two:
Both GraphQL and REST are based on the concept of a resource, and they specify IDs for those resources.
Both GraphQL and REST rely on frameworks and libraries to handle the tiny networking details.
Both can differentiate if an API request is intended to read data or write it.
1. One Unique…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tbaveja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an IDE in Programming? An IDE Definition for Developers]]></title>
        <id>60d07b4578f45307fee80aef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-ide-in-programming-an-ide-definition-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T20:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every developer needs a good development enviroment, whether you're into mobile development or web apps or even if you're just learning your first programming language.  Just like any beginning developer, when I began to learn coding I needed some guidance on how to get started. And one of the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side Projects - how do you choose a tech stack?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/josefine/side-projects-how-do-you-choose-a-tech-stack-2ie9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/josefine/side-projects-how-do-you-choose-a-tech-stack-2ie9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T19:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To get my hands dirty and continue learning a little more holistically I have been wanting to get started on a side project for a long time. What’s been holding me back so far is the sheer abundance of options - I feel like a little kid at the candy store. Torn somewhere between frantically running around and completely paralysed. 
During the bootcamp I participated in, we created our own web app with React, Node & MongoDB and tested a little with Cypress. Deployment / Hosting was not part of the course. Now while these are probably solid options, these choices were made for me. Now I am wondering, if I am completely free to choose, how do I decide on the stack for a project? 
I get that this highly depends on the project’s requirements and personal preferences. But say I want to create a very basic portfolio page - think virtual business card, really nothing fancy as an MVP (else I will literally never even try this). 
I discussed this with colleagues and got pretty diverse (and sometimes confusing) answers. This these perspectives helped me a lot put my own research into perspective, I would love to hear from you: 
How would you choose what to work with?
Based on what you would like to learn or rather something you already know well? 
How do you determine what tech stack is best suited for what you want to do?
Do you rather try something new and shiny or do you have a ‘winning team’ you aren’t likely to change any time soon?
Literally any tip, opinion or resource is highly appreciated :) Thanks so much!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josefine Schfr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Vid2vid-Cameo Demo]]></title>
        <id>http://nvidia-research-mingyuliu.com/vid2vid-cameo/</id>
        <link href="http://nvidia-research-mingyuliu.com/vid2vid-cameo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T19:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Fuck You' Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://cedwards.xyz/the-fuck-you-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://cedwards.xyz/the-fuck-you-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T19:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge dismisses FTC antitrust complaint against Facebook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/28/judge-dismisses-ftc-antitrust-complaint-against-facebook.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/28/judge-dismisses-ftc-antitrust-complaint-against-facebook.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T19:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much JavaScript to learn before learning React?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mehulmpt/how-much-javascript-to-learn-before-learning-react-1b51</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mehulmpt/how-much-javascript-to-learn-before-learning-react-1b51"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T19:09:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much JS should I know before I start learning React - this is a very common question I get asked all the time. In this blog post, I will breakdown a few myths and also list some very important topics/things you should know before you start React, or any other similar library/framework (Angular, Vue, etc.)
Stress on the keyword "all". A very important thing is that if your aim is to become, say a frontend developer (a complete guide on it here), you don't want to spend month after month on only JavaScript preparation.
The ideal mix that worked for me is to learn "just enough" to move on to React. This absolutely does not mean that you have learned JavaScript. This only means that you don't need to. JavaScript, like any programming language, can be vast, especially with all the tooling a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehul Mohan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Functools - The Power of Higher-Order Functions in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/martinheinz/functools-the-power-of-higher-order-functions-in-python-3dg0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/martinheinz/functools-the-power-of-higher-order-functions-in-python-3dg0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T18:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python standard library includes many great modules that can help you make your code cleaner and simpler and functools is definitely one of them. This module offers many useful higher order functions that act on or return other functions, which we can leverage to implement function caching, overloading, creating decorators and in general to make our code a bit more functional, so let's take a tour of it and see all the things it has to offer...
Let's start off with the simplest yet quite powerful functions of functools module. These are caching functions (and also decorators) - lru_cache, cache and cached_property. First of them - lru_cache provides least recently used cache of function results or in other words - memoization of results:
from functools import lru_cache
import requests

@lr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Heinz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jasonette Docker Android APK Builder]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/clsource/jasonette-docker-android-apk-builder-135o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/clsource/jasonette-docker-android-apk-builder-135o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T18:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the Jasonette project. I created a simple Dockerfile and a Makefile with some commands to help building Android APK both in release and debug mode. 
It includes everything you would need like Gradle, JVM and Android SDK.
Additionally it includes Windows cmd files as an alternative to the Makefiles.
 / 
        docker
      
    
These are a bunch of scripts and docker files that will help you
developing apps with Jasonette in Android.
Table of Contents
Directory Structure
Installation

Linux/Mac
Windows
Android

Jasonette
Keystore Creation

Example build.gradle
Edit your files
Edit your settings
Commands

Installation Command
Download and unzip the android directory
Create Android Keystore
Build Android APK in Debug Mode
Build Android APK in Release Mode
License
Credits
When unzipping you can see the following directory structure:
. (root)
├── Dockerfile
├── Makefile
├── app
│   ├── build
│   ├── file
│   ├── keys
│   └── settings
├── docs
├── jasonette
└── tools
    └── windows







Installation
The only requirement is Docker Desktop at least v20.10.0. You can read the installation docs at
https://docs.docker.com/get-docker/. Be sure that is up and running before installing the Jasonelle Android Setup Tools.
Linux and Mac use the Make…
View on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camilo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you need to use React-Query in your React/React Native project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/benjamindaniel/why-you-need-to-use-react-query-in-your-react-react-native-project-2oog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/benjamindaniel/why-you-need-to-use-react-query-in-your-react-react-native-project-2oog"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T18:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Have you had issues with managing server state? or find yourself writing long and funny looking code that just fetches data from the server? I honestly think you need to look at react-query if you fall into any of this category.
Server state is state that's actually stored on the server then is temporarily store in the client for quick-access (like user data, transaction data)
React's lack of standard data-fetching paradigm has led to the creation of several state management libraries. However, these libraries do not fully support handling async data(server state) properly. Async data is typically handled at the component level where each state associated to it is usually tracked i.e loading, error, data, refreshing e.t.c. as the number of server states tracked increases, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Daniel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Closure Tutorial – How Closures and Lexical Scope Work in JS]]></title>
        <id>60d675ac6e1a1407b6b0bea1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-closure-lexical-scope/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T18:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, people often confuse closures with lexical scope. Lexical scope is an important part of closures, but it is not a closure by itself. Closures are an advanced concept that is also a frequent topic of technical interviews. You should have a foundational understanding of functions before attempting to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Art Generator Neoplasticism]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/andronov04/mondrian-art</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/andronov04/mondrian-art"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T18:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An announcement about the comment section]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.sciencemag.org/pipeline/archives/2021/06/28/an-announcement-about-the-comment-section</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.sciencemag.org/pipeline/archives/2021/06/28/an-announcement-about-the-comment-section"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T18:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SafeDollar ‘stablecoin’ drops to $0 following DeFi exploit on Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptoslate.com/safedollar-stablecoin-drops-to-0-following-248000-defi-exploit-on-polygon/</id>
        <link href="https://cryptoslate.com/safedollar-stablecoin-drops-to-0-following-248000-defi-exploit-on-polygon/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T17:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon is using algorithms with little human intervention to fire Flex workers]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2021/06/amazon-is-firing-flex-workers-using-algorithms-with-little-human-intervention/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2021/06/amazon-is-firing-flex-workers-using-algorithms-with-little-human-intervention/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T17:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: The Sample – newsletters curated for you with machine learning]]></title>
        <id>https://sample.findka.com/?ref=showhn</id>
        <link href="https://sample.findka.com/?ref=showhn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T16:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Chemical Does Not Exist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thischemicaldoesnotexist.com/</id>
        <link href="https://www.thischemicaldoesnotexist.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T15:32:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Positioning Overlay Content with CSS Grid]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342971</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/positioning-overlay-content-with-css-grid/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T14:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not news to any web developer in 2021: CSS Grid is an incredibly powerful tool for creating complex, distinct two-dimensional modern web layouts.
Recently, I have been experimenting with CSS Grid and alignment properties to create component layouts that …
The post Positioning Overlay Content with CSS Grid appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Mulligan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Optery – See the private info data brokers are posting about you online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.optery.com/introducing-optery-remove-yourself-from-150-people-search-sites-like-truthfinder-mylife-radaris-socialcatfish-spokeo-whitepages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.optery.com/introducing-optery-remove-yourself-from-150-people-search-sites-like-truthfinder-mylife-radaris-socialcatfish-spokeo-whitepages/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T14:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Create a Design System in Figma]]></title>
        <id>60d4d3d86e1a1407b6b0bb25</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-create-a-design-system-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T13:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A design system is a set of standards, reusable components, and patterns used to create visual consistency throughout different projects and pages. Figma is a vector graphics editor and prototyping tool. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org channel that will teach you how to build a design]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Learn Data Analytics]]></title>
        <id>60d4ea756e1a1407b6b0bb71</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-should-learn-data-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T13:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ok. I'm not suggesting that everyone needs to become a fully-credentialed data scientist. But these days, learning core data skills may provide as much value as basic financial literacy or knowledge of a simple coding language. This isn't just about your career: data has grown far beyond the world of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Organizations Should Consider Building a Website Backed by a CRM Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343072</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/scaling-organizations-should-consider-building-a-website-backed-by-a-crm-platform/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T13:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To make some terminology clear here:
CMS = Content Management System
CRM = Customer Relationship Management
Both are essentially database-backed systems for managing data. HubSpot is both, and much more. Where a CMS might be very focused on content and …
The post Scaling Organizations Should Consider Building a Website Backed by a CRM Platform appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temporal: Getting started with JavaScript's new date time API]]></title>
        <id>https://2ality.com/2021/06/temporal-api.html</id>
        <link href="https://2ality.com/2021/06/temporal-api.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T13:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biohackers take aim at big pharma’s stranglehold on insulin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freethink.com/shows/just-might-work/how-to-make-insulin</id>
        <link href="https://www.freethink.com/shows/just-might-work/how-to-make-insulin"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T13:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Plea for Lean Software (1995) [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.frantovo.cz/s/1576/Niklaus%20Wirth%20-%20A%20Plea%20for%20Lean%20Software%20-%20OCR.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.frantovo.cz/s/1576/Niklaus%20Wirth%20-%20A%20Plea%20for%20Lean%20Software%20-%20OCR.pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T13:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subdomains for IPFS]]></title>
        <id>https://ipds.io/</id>
        <link href="https://ipds.io/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T10:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China releases videos of its Zhurong Mars rover]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-57628653</id>
        <link href="https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-57628653"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T10:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Custom Emmet Snippets In VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Manuel explains why Emmet is one of his favorite productivity tools for writing HTML and CSS, and how you can create custom Emmet snippets in Visual Studio Code to help you improve your front-end workflows even more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Minimal versioned log structured relational DB in Common Lisp]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/codr7/whirlog</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/codr7/whirlog"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T01:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-counting the cognitive history of numerals]]></title>
        <id>https://thereader.mitpress.mit.edu/recounting-cognitive-history-of-numerals/</id>
        <link href="https://thereader.mitpress.mit.edu/recounting-cognitive-history-of-numerals/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T00:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Groundbreaking new bridge design could transform rail crossings across the UK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.railadvent.co.uk/2021/06/groundbreaking-new-bridge-design-could-transform-rail-crossings-across-the-uk.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.railadvent.co.uk/2021/06/groundbreaking-new-bridge-design-could-transform-rail-crossings-across-the-uk.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T07:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Security and the Internet: Tools and Jewels]]></title>
        <id>https://people.scs.carleton.ca/~paulv/toolsjewels.html</id>
        <link href="https://people.scs.carleton.ca/~paulv/toolsjewels.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T05:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sears Tele-Games Pinball Breakaway]]></title>
        <id>https://nicole.express/2021/pinball-in-your-house.html</id>
        <link href="https://nicole.express/2021/pinball-in-your-house.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T22:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (June 26th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19349</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/26/science-and-technology-links-june-26th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T16:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reportedly, half of us own a smartphone. It is often reported that women or visible minority earn less money. However, ugly people are doing comparatively even more poorly. We have highly efficient and cheap solar panels. However, we must also quickly dispose of them after a few years which leads to trash. Handling an increasing … Continue reading Science and Technology links (June 26th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nullfs: A virtual black hole file system that behaves like /dev/null]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/abbbi/nullfsvfs</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/abbbi/nullfsvfs"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T11:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The slow rise of robots in the data center]]></title>
        <id>https://www.datacenterdynamics.com/en/analysis/caves-of-steel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.datacenterdynamics.com/en/analysis/caves-of-steel/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T11:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A little-known Soviet mission to rescue a dead space station (2014)]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/science/2014/09/the-little-known-soviet-mission-to-rescue-a-dead-space-station/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2014/09/the-little-known-soviet-mission-to-rescue-a-dead-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T05:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watermark: Along the California Aqueduct (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://placesjournal.org/article/watermark-along-the-california-aqueduct/</id>
        <link href="https://placesjournal.org/article/watermark-along-the-california-aqueduct/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T23:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom Property Brain Twisters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342718</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/custom-property-brain-twisters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T18:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am part of that 82% that got the answer to Lea Verou's quiz wrong. Stephen Shaw posted a similar quiz as well and it's a fun exercise sharpen your CSS chops.
The post Custom Property Brain Twisters appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Cancel Pending API Requests to Show Correct Data]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342911</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-cancel-pending-api-requests-to-show-correct-data/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T14:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently had to create a widget in React that fetches data from multiple API endpoints. As the user clicks around, new data is fetched and marshalled into the UI. But it caused some problems.
One problem quickly became evident: …
The post How to Cancel Pending API Requests to Show Correct Data appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgi Nikoloff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intimacy And Desire Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6454</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/intimacy-and-desire-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=intimacy-and-desire-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T12:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Intimacy And Desire uses case studies of couples in therapy to show how partners can turn their normal sexual struggles and issues with sexual desire into a journey of personal, spiritual, and psychological growth that leads to a stronger bond and deeper, healthier desires for each other. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post Intimacy And Desire Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Multi-Author Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how we can connect different types of content in a Next.js application. With this technique, we can add any kind of one-to-one, one-to-many, or even many-to-many relationship to our projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dom Habersack)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run A UX Audit For A Major EdTech Platform (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a case study of how a UX audit affects a UI. It explains how a famous educational platform can be analyzed edX against Jakob Nielsen’s usability guidelines. To get started, Mark Lankmiller shares all of the criteria and metrics he used for his UX audit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mark Lankmilier)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Common React Mistakes You Might Be Making – And How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>60d3ee396e1a1407b6b0b6ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/common-react-mistakes-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go over the most common mistakes you might be making in your React code right now, plus how to fix them. If you want to create amazing React applications, it's essential to avoid many common errors along the way. In this article, we'll not only cover how to fix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use OpenTelemetry to Understand Software Performance]]></title>
        <id>60d4b5e96e1a1407b6b0bac4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opentelemetry/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want good performance in your application, you need to collect data to figure out where to make improvements. That's where OpenTelemetry comes in. OpenTelemetry offers a single set of APIs and libraries that standardize how you collect and transfer telemetry data. OpenTelemetry provides a specification for instrumentation so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chapter 9: Community]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/chapter-9-community/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April of 2009, Yahoo! shut down GeoCities. Practically overnight, the once beloved service had its signup page replaced with a vague message announcing its closure.
We have decided to discontinue the process of allowing new customers to sign up 
…
The post Chapter 9: Community appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Hoffmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doesn’t Hurt To Ask Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6453</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/doesnt-hurt-to-ask-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=doesnt-hurt-to-ask-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T12:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Doesn’t Hurt To Ask explains how to become a master of persuasion by asking all of the right questions and teaches how intentional questions are the key to sharing your ideas, connecting with your audience, and convincing people of your way of thinking whether you’re in the office or at home. Read in: 4 […]
The post Doesn’t Hurt To Ask Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Analysis? How to Visualize Data with Python, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib &amp; Seaborn Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>605abca5687d62084bf6b7cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploratory-data-analysis-with-numpy-pandas-matplotlib-seaborn/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T00:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis is the process of exploring, investigating, and gathering insights from data using statistical measures and visualizations.  The objective of data analysis is to develop an understanding of data by uncovering trends, relationships, and patterns. Data analysis is both a science and an art. On the one hand it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices Architecture – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>6072ffd4d5756f080ba98b27</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microservices-architecture-for-humans/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few years, microservices have gone from an overhyped buzzword to something you should understand as a software engineer.  According to an O'Reilly developer survey in 2020:  61% of companies have been using microservices in the last year29% say at least half of their company systems are built]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343076</id>
        <link href="https://www.bram.us/2021/06/21/tablesng-improvements-to-table-rendering-in-chromium/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I blogged “Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier” recently, I mentioned that the “stickiness” improvement was just one of the features that got better for <table>s in Chrome as part of the TablesNG upgrade…
The post TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342750</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-performant-next-gen-images-in-css-with-image-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS image-set() function has been supported in Chromium-based browsers since 2012 and in Safari since version 6. Support recently landed in Firefox 88. Let’s dive in and see what we can and can’t do today with image-set().…
The post Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Weak declaration”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342669</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/weak-declaration/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T14:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PPK looks at aspect-ratio, a CSS property for layout that, for the most part, does exactly what you would think it does. It’s getting more interesting as it’s behind a flag in Firefox and Safari now, so we’ll have …
The post “Weak declaration” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6450</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/open-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=open-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T12:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Open is the autobiography of world-famous tennis player Andre Agassi in which he details his struggles and successes on the way to self-awareness and balance while he was also trying to handle the constant pressures and difficulties that came from being one of the best tennis players in the world. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post Open Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: support an experimental template for YouTube feed 📺 Demo | Source

Aggregate content from any YouTube channel rss url https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=<replace_with_channel_id>
Videos are embedded via iframe and loading accelerated by youtube-lite-embed
Ads are reduced thanks to YouTube's policy for embedded videos 🙃
Works on mobile devices with butter smooth horizontal scroll.
Caveat: the template works only with YouTube content. You cannot mix textual RSS feed or other video sources such as Vimeo.
Changed: Default HTML template meta tag adjusted to match convention
Changed: sources in template data is now ordered by last update timestamp (as opposed to alphabetical)
Thank you @PiyushLosalka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[inherit, initial, unset, revert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342930</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inherit-initial-unset-revert/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are four keywords that are valid values for any CSS property (see the title). Of those, day to day, I’d say I see the inherit used the most. Perhaps because it’s been around the longest (I think?) but also …
The post inherit, initial, unset, revert appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Custom Elements in Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-custom-elements-in-svelte/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte fully supports custom elements (e.g. <my-component>) without any custom configuration or wrapper components and has a perfect score on Custom Elements Everywhere. However, there are still a few quirks you need to watch out for, especially around …
The post Using Custom Elements in Svelte appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Rich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342925</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/if-were-gonna-criticize-utility-class-frameworks-lets-be-fair-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not here to raise a shield protecting CSS utility frameworks. I don’t even particularly like the approach, myself, and nothing is above fair criticism. But fair is a key word there. I can’t tell you how many times I’ve …
The post If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyper-learning Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6432</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/hyper-learning-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hyper-learning-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Hyper-learning shows how people and companies can adapt in the rapidly changing world we live in today, explaining how a growth mindset, collaboration, and losing your ego will build your confidence that you can stay relevant and competitive as the world around you accelerates. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: If […]
The post Hyper-learning Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342887</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/new-responsive/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una is calling it the new responsive. A nod to the era we were most certainly in, the era of responsive design. Where responsive design was fluid grids, flexible media, and media queries, the new responsive is those things …
The post Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342448</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-css-charts-with-interesting-shapes-glyphs-and-emoji/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s forego the usual circles and bars we typically see used in charts for more eccentric shapes. With online presentations more and more common today, a quick way to spruce up your web slides and make them stand out is …
The post How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billion Dollar Whale Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6397</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/billion-dollar-whale-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=billion-dollar-whale-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T12:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Billion Dollar Whale tells the incredible story of Jho Low, a Malaysian man who committed one of the biggest heists of the century by defrauding a national investment fund. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Wharton Business School is one of America’s highest-ranked business schools, and prospective students can expect an […]
The post Billion Dollar Whale Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Be A Leader Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6396</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-be-a-leader-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-be-a-leader-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T12:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Be A Leader is Greek philosopher Plutarch’s guide to leadership and uses practical ideas, historical narratives, political events, and more to outline the qualities of the best leaders, including serving for the right reasons, speaking persuasively, and following more experienced leaders. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Ancient Roman […]
The post How To Be A Leader Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Towers Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6395</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/dark-towers-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dark-towers-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Dark Towers dives into the dirty inner workings and the rise and fall of Deutsche Bank, which contributed to many notable but not always beneficial events of the past 150 years, including the American railroad system, the Nazi regime, funding Russian oligarchs, and even the election of Donald Trump. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite […]
The post Dark Towers Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Order Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6394</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/beyond-order-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=beyond-order-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Beyond Order is the follow-up to Jordan Peterson’s bestselling book 12 Rules for Life and identifies another 12 rules to live by that help us live with and even embrace the chaos that we struggle with every day, identifying that too much order can be a problem just as much as too much disorder. […]
The post Beyond Order Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Escape Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6393</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-great-escape-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-great-escape-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Great Escape challenges the idea that the world is on fire by declaring that things have never been better in many ways, although the advancements we’ve made and the ways they have improved many lives haven’t reached everyone equally. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: If you were born in […]
The post The Great Escape Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long should you work on a problem ?]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19336</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/14/how-long-should-you-work-on-a-problem/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T21:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lev Reyzin says that working too long on a problem might be unproductive: I, personally, have diminishing (or negative?) returns to my creative work as I explicitly work on a problem past some amount of time. I often have insights coming to me out of nowhere while I’m relaxing or enjoying hobbies on nights or … Continue reading How long should you work on a problem ?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperfocus Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6392</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/hyperfocus-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hyperfocus-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Hyperfocus teaches you how to become more efficient and improve your concentration by deciding on one thing to work on, focusing only on that task, learning to understand when your mind has wandered and redirecting your attention back to your work, and thinking creatively when you’re not working. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post Hyperfocus Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (June 12th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19326</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/12/science-and-technology-links-june-12th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T16:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We completed the sequencing of the human genome. AstraZeneca’s drug Lynparza cut combined risk of recurrence of breast cancer or death by 42% among women in study. Glycine and N-acetylcysteine supplementation improves muscle strength and cognition. We found Egypt’s ancient capital. It has been lost of 3,400 years. It is unclear why it was abandoned. … Continue reading Science and Technology links (June 12th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19312</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/03/computing-the-number-of-digits-of-an-integer-even-faster/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I my previous blog post, I documented how one might proceed to compute the number of digits of an integer quickly. E.g., given the integer 999, you want 3 but given the integer 1000, you want 4. It is effectively the integer logarithm in base 10. On computers, you can quickly compute the integer logarithm … Continue reading Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>