<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-06T01:02:35.691Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-06T01:02:35.691Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haskell for the Elm Enthusiast]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.noredink.com/post/658510851000713216/haskell-for-the-elm-enthusiast</id>
        <link href="https://blog.noredink.com/post/658510851000713216/haskell-for-the-elm-enthusiast"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T00:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boy with a beard explains Web components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/boywithabeard/boy-with-a-beard-explains-web-components-1jhm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/boywithabeard/boy-with-a-beard-explains-web-components-1jhm"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T00:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Web Components?


Web component is a term used for four web standards that help us make custom, reusable and encapsulated html tags that can be used in web pages and applications.
1. <template> elements: With the <template> elements, we encapsulate html, and then render it using javascript.
So what happens is that template elements break apart html. Whatever is contained inside the template tag doesn't get rendered at load-time. Instead javascript renders when the function is called. So a page would load very quickly, since we have part of html that doesn't load at load-time. We can also reuse these elements, so we save a lot of time.

2. Custom elements: With custom elements, we create a javascript class, and then link it to a custom html element.
An html document already ships d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>boywithabeard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to display content in multiple columns using CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kritikapattalam/how-to-display-content-in-multiple-columns-using-css-3cfa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kritikapattalam/how-to-display-content-in-multiple-columns-using-css-3cfa"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T00:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to see how or when  orphans or widows property in CSS can be used in showing content as multiple columns. 
[P.S : Refer the codepen given below to see visually how each property behaves]
Consider that you have a list of paragraphs and you want to show it in 3 or 4 columns and also decide where or how the content can break. Let's see the first step on how you can split the content in a simple way.
Create a div with multiple paragraph tags or a ul with multiple li tags
Add the below code snippet
columns: 3 //  should be a positive integer. Here the paragraph will be split into 3 columns.
.split-3-columns {
  display: block;
  columns: 3; // value based on how many columns you want the content to split
  height: 250px; // height of the div as per your need
}

In …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kritika Pattalam Bharathkumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LÖVR – An open source framework for rapidly building immersive 3D experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://lovr.org</id>
        <link href="https://lovr.org"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T00:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivermectin Systematic Study: Inconclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cochranelibrary.com/cdsr/doi/10.1002/14651858.CD015017.pub2/full</id>
        <link href="https://www.cochranelibrary.com/cdsr/doi/10.1002/14651858.CD015017.pub2/full"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T23:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Bad Coding Habits You Should Leave Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/unitybuddy/7-bad-coding-habits-you-should-leave-right-now-2hjn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/unitybuddy/7-bad-coding-habits-you-should-leave-right-now-2hjn"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T23:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, buddies! Bad habits are hard to break and even harder if you don't realize that what you're doing is undermining your work. If you know but don't care—that would be the worst. You lucky buddy, you are in the right article. Here are the 7 coding habits you might have and if you have them,   drop it right now.

Instead of learning different languages, one should focus on mastering one language.

Knowing everything is okay. But it doesn’t mean that you won’t make any mistakes. When you are dealing with a big project, it may possible that there is a little syntax error. Being overconfident on what you know will lead you to make little mistakes.

While working in team projects, asking help from your team members will help you in interacting with them. You will able to know the abilities of your team members.
In this article, @Ayodele Samuel Adebayo shows you 10 reasons why you should ask questions! 




So here are the 7 bad(worst) habits you should drop right now. Happy Coding!
Originally published on Hahshnode]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mr. Unity Buddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Tips to be SUCCESSFUL at DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/3-tips-to-be-successful-at-devops-5f8h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/3-tips-to-be-successful-at-devops-5f8h"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T23:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I have for you 3 tips that will help you be more successful in your DevOps career, and they apply to every type of DevOps Role.
I have been working "in DevOps and with DevOps" for the most part of the last 14 years. I've covered many different roles, and worked with big and small clients. And today I wanna share with you how you can be more successful at DevOps. As I've mentioned I have 3 tips that will help you in your DevOps Career. Actually, I also have a bonus one at the end so I guess that makes it 4 tips.
In short, those are the tips. But check the video below 👇🏻 for the whole explanation on each of those:
Think out of the box, be a problem solver, be the person others look to when they need a solution
Find a way to automate more
Always experiment



The Bonus tip? Check the video below for it 🎬
Here you have the video with the whole explanation about the 3 tips and also the bonus tip.
Enjoy the watch 😉




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/A-NeIPCLSRU
Let me know in the comment section below what you think about those 3+1 tips. Do you agree with me? Or do you have anything else you can share that made YOU successful at DevOps?
Like, share and follow me 🚀 for more content:
📽 YouTube
Buy me a coffee
Patreon
CoderDave.io Website
Merch
Facebook page
GitHub
Twitter
LinkedIn
Podcast]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide 'CoderDave' Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stanford AIMI Releases Its Free Open-Source Repository of Medical Datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://hai.stanford.edu/news/open-source-movement-comes-medical-datasets</id>
        <link href="https://hai.stanford.edu/news/open-source-movement-comes-medical-datasets"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T23:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Readable vs Workable Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kspeakman/readable-vs-workable-code-2mla</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kspeakman/readable-vs-workable-code-2mla"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T22:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Balancing some code to be readable yet workable.
Today I was coding and decided to refactor some older code. In particular, this code is handling navigation updates in a Fable Elmish app in F#.
let routeToPage routeOpt =
    match routeOpt with
    | None ->
        let page, effects = OpsUser.Search.init None
        OpsUserSearch page, effects
    | Some route ->
        match route with
        | ToOpsUserSearch searchOpt ->
            let page, effects = OpsUser.Search.init searchOpt
            OpsUserSearch page, effects
        | ToOpsUserAdd ->
            let page, effects = OpsUser.Add.init ()
            OpsUserAdd page, effects

This function has many route cases but only two are shown here.
First I started to remove duplication. Starting at the innermost duplication, notice h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasey Speakman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST’s Quantum Crystal Could Be a New Dark Matter Sensor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2021/08/nists-quantum-crystal-could-be-new-dark-matter-sensor</id>
        <link href="https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2021/08/nists-quantum-crystal-could-be-new-dark-matter-sensor"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T22:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PWA: set manifest.json name & icon dynamically; client-side. Jabbadabbadoo!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pablo_74/pwa-set-manifest-json-name-icon-dynamically-client-side-jabbadabbadoo-10h7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pablo_74/pwa-set-manifest-json-name-icon-dynamically-client-side-jabbadabbadoo-10h7"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T22:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is my 1st write up on dev.to site. Source code included as link. I use VueJS, but you can use vanilla JS too.
PWA app needs manifest.json to be installable. We usually have index.html with the link to the manifest.json file, the separate one, where all items are defined. This file is static, the only way to change it is to edit it's source code (as you are developer, NOT user). Suppose we serve static files, not dynamically created by node.js or similar server side technology.
Today I will show you a practical example how to change some manifest's items dynamically on client side, i.e. as user.
I need to say my work is not my invention, it is based on excellent work, ideas and researches of other developers.
alshakero, his post How to Setup Your Web App Manifest Dynamically Using Java…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavel Kříž</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting a CLI Finance Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cesd/starting-a-cli-finance-tool-5acf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cesd/starting-a-cli-finance-tool-5acf"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T22:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motivation


This is a finance tool project based heavily on beancount but with less features and way less complexity. After reviewing the beancount repo and documentation, I noticed that there are many more features available that I will use. In an attempt to create a new project with a new language, C#, this project was born.
This is a console application. As of right now the only major dependency is the System.CommandLine package. The commands code is written in namespace Controllers.Commands and the parsing and formatting of entries is written in namespace Controllers.VaultAccess.
Here is an example of one of my commands.
using System;
using System.CommandLine;
using System.CommandLine.Invocation;
using Controllers.VaultAccess;
using Config;

namespace Controllers.Commands
{

    publi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ces-D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&lt;pre&gt; Tag in HTML – Example Code]]></title>
        <id>610be0ea3306a507d1bfe4b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pre-tag-in-html-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T21:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HTML <pre> tag defines a preformatted block of text. It comes in handy when you want to display text where the typographical formatting affects the meaning of the content, such as code snippets and poems.  By default, browsers ignore white space of any kind – extra text space,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/2: The Sequel is Always Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://portswigger.net/research/http2</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/research/http2"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T21:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev log for Wonder Wanderer 2: Day 4/5 #LOWREZJAM]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/michaelprimo/dev-log-for-wonder-wanderer-2-day-4-5-lowrezjam-4765</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/michaelprimo/dev-log-for-wonder-wanderer-2-day-4-5-lowrezjam-4765"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T21:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I tried to make collisions, but I didn't manage to do it and I spent the whole day doing this task unsuccessfully."
I made collisions on the map and also very rudimental jumps and gravity, but the controls are not very good now, so I'll improve them the next day.

The results of the hard work of two days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Primo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promises and async functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/manlycoffee/promises-and-async-functions-45m5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/manlycoffee/promises-and-async-functions-45m5"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T21:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With JavaScript, some operations are asynchronous, and many of these asynchronous operations are signalled via promises.
For instance, fetching data from an API is an asynchronous operation; you need to wait until data from the API has been fully downloaded. So, invoking fetch doesn't give you the data. Instead, it gives you a promise, from which you will need to have another function be called to receive said value, as the first parameter of that function.
With a promise, to get the result the instance that is available, you invoke the then method, and pass in said function as the first parameter.
Here's an example:
const fetchPromise = fetch('http://example.com/some-api/');


fetchPromise.then(response => {
  // Do something with `response` here.
  //
  // Note: the `response` object doe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sal Rahman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the inbuilt Node.js profiler]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/logrocket/using-the-inbuilt-node-js-profiler-390n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/logrocket/using-the-inbuilt-node-js-profiler-390n"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T21:07:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Written by Chimezie Enyinnaya ✏️
Starting as a software developer, it's recommended to follow a more pragmatic approach to developing software.
As time goes on, when you start building more complex software that serves thousands or millions of users, it becomes crucial to be more concerned with concepts such as architecture, system design, testing, security, deployment, and most especially performance. Furthermore, on performance, it is common practice to follow key performance metrics such as average response time, traffic rate, and CPU usage of your application and the server.
The main issue now stems from acquiring the best profiler tool that measures your Node.js application performance based on these metrics and doesn’t affect the software responsiveness.

N.B., CPU profiling and CPU …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Angelosanto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BuildZoom (better way to build custom homes) is hiring engineers]]></title>
        <id>https://jobs.lever.co/buildzoom</id>
        <link href="https://jobs.lever.co/buildzoom"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T21:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Your Own React Router]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/create-your-own-react-router-53ng</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/create-your-own-react-router-53ng"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T20:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was one of my current curiosities, however the purpose of this article is not to say that I think it is necessary to create your own router. If you have the same interest as I had this article is for you, but if you find it interesting you can read on.
According to the research I did, most of the articles I read had solutions that used a lot of hooks, some use a lot of regular expressions, and some use a mixture of both.
However in today's example I'm just going to use the hooks we are all familiar with (useEffect() and useState()). And another little thing that in a few seconds I'll explain.
So we're going to create two super popular components, Route and Link. The Route will be in charge of registering our route and rendering its component. The Link will be used to navigate between …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Mendes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Operating Systems: Timeline and Family Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://eylenburg.github.io/os_familytree.htm</id>
        <link href="https://eylenburg.github.io/os_familytree.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T20:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apophenia: How the Internet Transforms the Individual into a Conspiracy of One]]></title>
        <id>https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/conspiracy-pt2</id>
        <link href="https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/conspiracy-pt2"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T20:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript Interface vs Class With Practical Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/raj_sekhar/typescript-interface-vs-class-5f6l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/raj_sekhar/typescript-interface-vs-class-5f6l"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T20:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript, oh I love it. Take stackoverflow survey, or ask any developer, most of them do. All major UI libraries/frameworks are (following Angular way) adding Typescript support now. Need to write a little extra boilerplate (use json to ts extension), but the benefits of type checking, intellisense and instant visual feedback outweigh the extra work.
I had this confusion where both interface and class gets the work done, but which one to use and when?
Use interface, avoid class unless there is any special requirement that cannot be done with interface.
Classes add to js file size, after compiling .ts to .js, while interfaces do not
Lets take scenario, where we want to give structure to a pizza object. I can use interface or an object. 
pizza-interface.ts
interface Pizza {
    variant: st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raj Sekhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Your Audience?]]></title>
        <id>https://leejo.github.io/2021/08/01/who-is-your-audience/</id>
        <link href="https://leejo.github.io/2021/08/01/who-is-your-audience/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T20:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's plan to “think different” about encryption opens a backdoor to your life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/08/apples-plan-think-different-about-encryption-opens-backdoor-your-private-life</id>
        <link href="https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/08/apples-plan-think-different-about-encryption-opens-backdoor-your-private-life"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T20:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse Engineering the M1 [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://i.blackhat.com/USA21/Wednesday-Handouts/us-21-Reverse-Engineering-The-M1.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://i.blackhat.com/USA21/Wednesday-Handouts/us-21-Reverse-Engineering-The-M1.pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T20:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox: Performance in Progress]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/performance/2021/08/05/performance-in-progress/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/performance/2021/08/05/performance-in-progress/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T19:27:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build your own SPARC workstation]]></title>
        <id>https://learn.adafruit.com/build-your-own-sparc-with-qemu-and-solaris</id>
        <link href="https://learn.adafruit.com/build-your-own-sparc-with-qemu-and-solaris"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T18:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical? Common Lisp on the JVM: A quick intro to ABCL for modern web apps]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.eatonphil.com/practical-common-lisp-on-the-jvm.html</id>
        <link href="https://notes.eatonphil.com/practical-common-lisp-on-the-jvm.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T18:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yann LeCun on his start in AI and recent self-supervised learning research]]></title>
        <id>https://thegradientpub.substack.com/p/yann-lecun-on-his-start-in-research</id>
        <link href="https://thegradientpub.substack.com/p/yann-lecun-on-his-start-in-research"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T17:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Security – How to Use Dynamic Admission Control to Secure Your Container Supply Chain]]></title>
        <id>6108233d3306a507d1bfc731</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kubernetes-security-dynamic-admission-control/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T16:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers have exploded in popularity in recent years. And as more developers are using these containers, they need more tools to manage them and their interactions with them effectively.  To help manage all this, many devs use Kubernetes. And it has become the de facto standard for container orchestration. While]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How PostgreSQL aggregation works and how it inspired our hyperfunctions’ design]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.timescale.com/blog/how-postgresql-aggregation-works-and-how-it-inspired-our-hyperfunctions-design-2/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.timescale.com/blog/how-postgresql-aggregation-works-and-how-it-inspired-our-hyperfunctions-design-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T16:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mathematicians Solve Decades-Old Classification Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/mathematicians-solve-decades-old-classification-problem-20210805/</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/mathematicians-solve-decades-old-classification-problem-20210805/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T15:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Visualizing a Codebase]]></title>
        <id>https://octo.github.com/projects/repo-visualization</id>
        <link href="https://octo.github.com/projects/repo-visualization"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T15:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giraffes are as socially complex as elephants]]></title>
        <id>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/08/04/africa/giraffes-complex-behavior-scn/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://edition.cnn.com/2021/08/04/africa/giraffes-complex-behavior-scn/index.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T15:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Buggy React Code Examples and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345418</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/three-buggy-react-code-examples-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T14:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s usually more than one way to code a thing in React. And while it’s possible to create the same thing different ways, there may be one or two approaches that technically work “better” than others. I actually run into …
The post Three Buggy React Code Examples and How to Fix Them appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hugh Haworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>60db390127f80207bcdbb455</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T14:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML is used to create web pages.  This article will teach you the basics of HTML. I also created a 45-minute video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches you HTML in the context of creating an actual web page. If you are just learning HTML, I recommend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Years of fighting every wildfire helped fuel the Western megafires of today]]></title>
        <id>https://theconversation.com/how-years-of-fighting-every-wildfire-helped-fuel-the-western-megafires-of-today-163165</id>
        <link href="https://theconversation.com/how-years-of-fighting-every-wildfire-helped-fuel-the-western-megafires-of-today-163165"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T14:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch YC S21: Meet the Batch, Thread #4]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28073548</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28073548"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T13:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Disabled Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we make disabled buttons more inclusive? When do they work well, and when do they fail on us? And finally, when do we actually need them, and how can we avoid them? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kid Pix as a JavaScript App]]></title>
        <id>https://kidpix.app/</id>
        <link href="https://kidpix.app/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T13:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Common Voice Adds 16 New Languages and 4,600 New Hours of Speech]]></title>
        <id>https://foundation.mozilla.org/en/blog/mozilla-common-voice-adds-16-new-languages-and-4600-new-hours-of-speech/</id>
        <link href="https://foundation.mozilla.org/en/blog/mozilla-common-voice-adds-16-new-languages-and-4600-new-hours-of-speech/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T12:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal Computing on an Amiga in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://thedorkweb.substack.com/p/personal-computing-on-an-amiga-in-2021</id>
        <link href="https://thedorkweb.substack.com/p/personal-computing-on-an-amiga-in-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T12:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full-Stack Mobile Application With Flutter, Fauna, and GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345552</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-build-a-full-stack-mobile-application-with-flutter-fauna-and-graphql/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Flutter is Google’s UI framework used to create flexible, expressive cross-platform mobile applications. It is one of the fastest-growing frameworks for mobile app development. On the other hand, Fauna is a transactional, developer-friendly serverless …
The post How to Build a Full-Stack Mobile Application With Flutter, Fauna, and GraphQL appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fauna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web Workers In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345866</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T23:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You gotta appreciate the tenacity of Surma. He’s been advocating for Web Workers as a path forward to better-feeling websites for a lot of years now. He’s at it again making sure we all understand the landscape:
[…] regardless 
…
The post The State Of Web Workers In 2021 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Border – Style and HTML Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>610afe863306a507d1bfdf1e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-border-style-and-html-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T23:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In CSS, everything is a box. And each box – whether it's text, an image, a div, a span, or any other element – has a border that separates its edges from other boxes around it.  The CSS border property allows us to do several things with the border of individual boxes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Padding – CSS Padding Order]]></title>
        <id>6106575b3306a507d1bfc104</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-padding-css-padding-order/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T21:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to learn about CSS padding properties, the shorthand property, and how padding differs from margin.  What is padding in CSS?CSS padding creates space around the element's content. This space is within the element's border and margin.  Let's take a look at the CSS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAML Is Insecure by Design]]></title>
        <id>https://joonas.fi/2021/08/saml-is-insecure-by-design/</id>
        <link href="https://joonas.fi/2021/08/saml-is-insecure-by-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T19:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Where – Clause Examples]]></title>
        <id>6106638c3306a507d1bfc15c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-where-clause-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T15:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when you're working with SQL, you don't need to operate on an entire range of records. Or it would be really bad if you accidentally changed or deleted everything. In these cases, you'll need to select only the part of the records on which you want to work, those]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Vertical Align – How to Center a Div, Text, or an Image [Example Code]]]></title>
        <id>610a56153306a507d1bfd5f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-vertical-align-how-to-center-a-div-text-or-an-image-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T15:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even with helpful tools like CSS Grid and Flexbox, centering elements in CSS remains notoriously challenging.  It's been the subject of many jokes and memes, and when you successfully center something, you'll want to brag about it.  Why is Centering CSS Elements So Hard? CSS can be tricky to work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Background Color – How to Change the Background Color in HTML]]></title>
        <id>610641743306a507d1bfbfd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-background-color-how-to-change-the-background-color-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T14:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have started creating your HTML page, and you want to give it some color – maybe change the color of the text or set a nice background. So how do you do that? In this article I'll show you how you can change the background color of a page in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using CSS Shapes for Interesting User Controls and Navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345274</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-css-shapes-for-interesting-user-controls-and-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T14:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Straight across or down, that’s the proverbial order for user controls on a screen. Like a list of menu items. But what if we change that to a more fluid layout with bends, curves, and nooks? We can pull it …
The post Using CSS Shapes for Interesting User Controls and Navigation appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Children And Iteration Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll discuss and learn about the use case of iterating over React `children` and the ways to do it. In particular, we will deep dive into one of the utility methods, `React.Children.toArray`, that React gives us, which helps to iterate over the children in a way which ensures performance and determinism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arihant Verma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17th-century botanists filled their gardens with plants from around the world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.laphamsquarterly.org/roundtable/contribute-either-usefulness-or-delight</id>
        <link href="https://www.laphamsquarterly.org/roundtable/contribute-either-usefulness-or-delight"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T05:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graph Algorithms for Technical Interviews]]></title>
        <id>6109eca73306a507d1bfd3d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/graph-algorithms-for-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T01:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During technical interviews it is common for your interviewer to ask you to solve coding challenges. And you should have a good understanding of graph algorithms if you want to do well on these challenges. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React and Material UI Course – Code a Dictionary]]></title>
        <id>6109e5233306a507d1bfd3ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-dictionary-with-react-and-material-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T01:03:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React continues to be a popular front-end JavaScript library. And you can improve your skills by building a dictionary project. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a dictionary app with React and Material UI. You will learn to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of the Hollywood Memoir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.newyorker.com/books/page-turner/celebrity-memoirs-book-reviews</id>
        <link href="https://www.newyorker.com/books/page-turner/celebrity-memoirs-book-reviews"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T23:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Functions as Proxies]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345744</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/serverless-functions-as-proxies/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T20:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time cloud functions / serverless functions clicked for me was when I saw and tried Auth0’s (now defunct) Webtask. It was a little CodePen-like IDE but you didn’t really see anything aside from code and logs. The …
The post Serverless Functions as Proxies appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic Daily GitHub Backups, Restored in Seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345807</id>
        <link href="https://srv.buysellads.com/ads/long/x/TCZHURZTTTTTTT3IJZ7NTTTTTTTVINFLKTTTTTTTADBXPYTTTTTTTIDNVJR6YWS22M4647ZVKMPW454EQMNWVWPMPABT"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T20:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Any company that uses GitHub for critical applications needs a backup that can be restored quickly when needed. Cyberattacks, human errors, or a forced push are just some of the scenarios that can result …
The post Automatic Daily GitHub Backups, Restored in Seconds appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rewind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How fast can you pipe a large file to a C++ program?]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19429</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/08/03/how-fast-can-you-pipe-a-large-file-to-a-c-program/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T17:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under many operating systems, you can send data from from one process to another using ‘pipes’. The term ‘pipe’ is probably used by analogy with plumbing and we often use the the symbol ‘|‘ to represent a pipe (it looks like a vertical pipe). Thus, for example, you can sort a file and send it … Continue reading How fast can you pipe a large file to a C++ program?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive on Skipping to Content]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345154</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-deep-dive-on-skipping-to-content/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T14:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most people browsing the web on a computer use a mouse, many rely on their keyboard instead. Theoretically, using a web page with the keyboard should not be a problem — press the TAB key to move the keyboard …
The post A Deep Dive on Skipping to Content appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Ratcliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs' org-mode gets citation support]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.tecosaur.com/tmio/2021-07-31-citations.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.tecosaur.com/tmio/2021-07-31-citations.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T13:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Resilient JavaScript UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resilience is intrinsic to the web and therefore us, web developers. This article explores how graceful degradation, defensive coding, observability, and a healthy attitude towards failures better equips us before, during, and after an error occurs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Callum Hart)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leap Smear]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.google.com/time/smear</id>
        <link href="https://developers.google.com/time/smear"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T10:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Modules (The Native Ones)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345756</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-modules-the-native-ones/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T18:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They are actually called “CSS Module Scripts” and are a native browser feature, as opposed to the popular open-source project that essentially does scoped styles by creating unique class name identifiers in both HTML and CSS. 
Native CSS Modules are …
The post CSS Modules (The Native Ones) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a Playable Synth Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345178</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-code-a-playable-synth-keyboard/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T14:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a little knowledge of music theory, we can use regular HTML, CSS and JavaScript — without any libraries or audio samples — to create a simple digital instrument. Let’s put that into practice and explore one method for creating …
The post How to Code a Playable Synth Keyboard appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bret Cameron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goals! Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6694</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/goals-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=goals-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T12:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Goals! By Brian Tracy shows you how to unleash the power of goal setting to help you get or become whatever you want, identifying ways to set goals that lead you to success by being specific, challenging yourself, thinking positively, preparing, adjusting your timelines on big goals, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite […]
The post Goals! Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Strategy, Regression Testing And Maintenance (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a deep dive into the refactoring process itself, and cover incremental refactoring strategy, visual regression testing, and maintaining the refactored codebase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19419</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/31/science-and-technology-links-july-31st-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T19:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers built a microscope that might be 10 times better than the best available microscopes. Subsidizing college education can lower earnings due to lower job experience: The Post 9/11 GI Bill (PGIB) is among the largest and most generous college subsidies enacted thus far in the U.S. (…) the introduction of the PGIB raised college … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes In August (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2021. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Shared ESLint Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345628</id>
        <link href="https://katydecorah.com/code/eslint-config/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T20:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like it was almost 9 years ago when Airbnb first published their JavaScript Style Guide. 112k stars on GitHub later, it seems like the de facto preset for Babel / ES Lint. But it’s not the only company …
The post A Shared ESLint Configuration appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conjuring Generative Blobs With The CSS Paint API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345256</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/conjuring-generative-blobs-with-the-css-paint-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T14:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Paint API (part of the magical Houdini family) opens the door to an exciting new world of design in CSS. Using the Paint API, we can create custom shapes, intricate patterns, and beautiful animations — all with a …
The post Conjuring Generative Blobs With The CSS Paint API appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Francis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6687</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/now-discover-your-strengths-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=now-discover-your-strengths-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Now, Discover Your Strengths shows you how to find your top five strengths by outlining what strengths are, how you get them, why they’re important to reaching your full potential, and how to discover your own through analyzing the times when your behavior is the most natural or instinctive and why. Read in: 4 […]
The post Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An E-Commerce Site With Angular 11, Commerce Layer And Paypal]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having an e-commerce store is crucial for any store owner as more and more customers are turning to online shopping. In this tutorial, we shall go through how to create an e-commerce site with Angular 11. The site will use the Commerce Layer as a headless e-commerce API and use Paypal to process payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19408</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/29/measuring-memory-usage-virtual-versus-real-memory/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T21:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developers are often concerned with the memory usage of their applications, and rightly so. Software that uses too much memory can fail, or be slow. Memory allocation will not work the same way under all systems. However, at a high level, most modern operating systems have virtual memory and physical memory (RAM). When you write … Continue reading Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Explains the Open Graph Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345518</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-06-22-framework-building-open-graph-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T19:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An explanation of those new GitHub social media images:
[…] our custom Open Graph image service is a little Node.js app that uses the GitHub GraphQL API to collect data, generates some HTML from a template, and pipes it to 
…
The post GitHub Explains the Open Graph Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So you want to self-publish books and courses on programming]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344993</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-you-want-to-self-publish-books-and-courses-on-programming/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Resig and I recently self-published our book on GraphQL. There are tons of how-tos for self-publishing a book, or even online classes, but very little in the way of why you would want to, or whether it’s even worth …
The post So you want to self-publish books and courses on programming appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Loren Sands-Ramshaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer-Friendly Passwordless Auth]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345260</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/developer-friendly-passwordless-auth/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T14:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
I’d wager to say that most websites that are business-minded have accounts. A way to log into them. Social media sites, eCommerce sites, CMS systems, you name it, having accounts people log into is …
The post Developer-Friendly Passwordless Auth appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Such Thing As A CSS Absolute Unit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are absolute units? What are the differences between relative and absolute units, and how do we create accurate sizes on the web? In this article, Elad Shechter explains why CSS absolute units aren’t so absolute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elad Shechter)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari 15 Opinions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345404</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/safari-15-opinions/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T20:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was interesting that when Safari 15 was dropping at this last WWDC, in my circles at least, I mostly heard enthusiasm. Like the colors-in-the-browser-controls stuff was a neat trick and fun to play with. And there were other …
The post Safari 15 Opinions appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Democracies Die Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6683</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-democracies-die-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-democracies-die-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How Democracies Die explores the foundational ideas of democracy by looking at historical events, especially in Latin America, that show how democracies have failed, whether it can happen again, and how to protect democracy from threats like mutual toleration, inequality, and political parties. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: When Donald […]
The post How Democracies Die Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating An Accessible Dialog From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dialogs are everywhere in modern interface design (for good or for bad), and yet many of them are not accessible to assistive technologies. In this article, we will dig into how to create a short script to create accessible dialogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kitty Giraudel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global vs. Local Styling In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has strong opinions about how to organize JavaScript but not CSS. How can we develop patterns that encourage best CSS practices while also following the framework’s logic? The answer is surprisingly simple — to write well-structured CSS that balances global and local styling concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Dubovoy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kindness Method Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6677</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-kindness-method-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-kindness-method-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T12:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Kindness Method by Shahroo Izadi teaches how self-compassion and understanding make forming habits easier than being hard on yourself, using the personal experiences of the author and what she’s learned as an addiction recovery therapist to show how self-esteem is the true key to behavior change. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post The Kindness Method Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Serverless Functions And The International Space Station]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby recently announced the launch of “functions”. In this article, Paul Scanlon explains how to get the current location of the International Space Station (ISS) as it orbits the Earth in real-time using [Gatsby Functions](https://www.gatsbyjs.com/docs/reference/functions/) and then display it on a 3D interactive globe using [React Three Fibre](https://github.com/pmndrs/react-three-fiber).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soundtracks Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6665</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/soundtracks-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=soundtracks-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T12:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Soundtracks is New York Times bestselling author Jon Acuff’s 2021 book that teaches you how to beat overthinking by challenging whether your thoughts are true, retiring unhelpful and unkind ideas, adopting thought-boosting mantras from others, using symbols to reinforce positive thoughts, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Is there […]
The post Soundtracks Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Attracting Clients To Your Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many web design agencies consider it a badge of honor that they win work exclusively through word-of-mouth recommendations. In this article, Paul Boag explains why that is entirely the wrong attitude and what to do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Time To Your Schedule As A Professional]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you running a business and have too many things going on at once? Meetings, bugs, customer feedback, new clients in addition to your already tight deadlines? Let’s face it, time management is hard, and it becomes even more difficult in the trying times we are in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[75 Hard Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6657</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/75-hard-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=75-hard-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: 75 Hard is a fitness challenge and book that teaches mental toughness by making you commit to five daily critical tasks for 75 days straight, including drinking a gallon of water, reading 10 pages of a non-fiction book, doing two 45-minute workouts, taking a progress picture, and following a diet. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post 75 Hard Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? We’ve collected some useful color tools and resources that we’ve discovered lately — to help you get the most out of your creativity. We’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [accessible front-end components](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/complete-guide-accessible-front-end-components/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fail Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6656</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-fail-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-fail-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T12:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Fail shows the surprising benefits of going through a difficult time through the experiences of the author, Elizabeth Day, including the failures in her life that she’s grateful for and how they’ve helped her grow, uncovering why we shouldn’t be so afraid of failure but instead embrace it. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post How To Fail Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From WordPress To A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at when it makes sense to migrate from a monolithic project to a headless setup and the benefits that come with it. In addition to a step-by-step guide on how to migrate WordPress to Storyblok Headless CMS, the problems that will arise during the process and how to deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Change Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6655</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-change-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-change-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T06:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Change by Katy Milkman identifies the stumbling blocks that are in your way of reaching your goals and improving yourself and the research-backed ways to get over them, including how to beat some of the worst productivity and life problems like procrastination, laziness, and much more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post How To Change Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Stopping Time Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6638</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-art-of-stopping-time-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-art-of-stopping-time-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T12:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Art of Stopping Time teaches a framework of mindfulness, philosophy, and time-management you can use to achieve Time Prosperity, which is having plenty of time to reach your dreams without overwhelm, tumult, or constriction. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: What would you say if I asked you what the […]
The post The Art Of Stopping Time Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining End-To-End Quality With Visual Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding visual elements to your tests, you can gain more options to add meaningful ways in maintaining a high level of quality for your app. Colby Fayock explains how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Colby Fayock)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Insights I Gained While Researching Vue.js Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web app accessibility appears difficult because it seems that there is little information on the subject available online. Let’s take a closer look at the accessible use of framework features, concrete Vue.js traits, as well as community initiatives and vetted patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are You Doing With Your Life Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6595</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/what-are-you-doing-with-your-life-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=what-are-you-doing-with-your-life-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: What Are You Doing With Your Life is a book by the great philosopher and teacher Jiddu Krishnamurti, who turns traditional ideas about happiness and the purpose of life on its head by diving into the details of life’s most important questions so you can live with intention and joy more consistently. Read in: […]
The post What Are You Doing With Your Life Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISR vs DPR: Big Words, Quick Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two strategies for incrementally building websites that are growing in popularity: Incremental Static Regeneration and Distributed Persistent Rendering. What’s the difference? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cassidy Williams)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Do That With A JavaScript Data Grid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll get to see some pretty groundbreaking things you can achieve with modern JavaScript grids and discover new ways to augment a data grid to make it engaging, responsive, and accessible. All this will be illustrated using Kendo UI Data Grids and their features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19380</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/14/faster-sorted-array-unions-by-reducing-branches/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing an index, a database or a search engine, you frequently need to compute the union of two sorted sets. When I am not using fancy low-level instructions, I have most commonly computed the union of two sorted sets using the following approach: v1 = first value in input 1 v2 = first value … Continue reading Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Broken Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Too often dealing with filters can be frustrating. Let’s get them right. That means never freeze the UI on a single input, provide text input fallback and never auto-scroll users on a single input. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Dynamic Header With Intersection Observer]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, attaching an event listener to constantly fire a callback on scroll can be performance-intensive. But there is a better way with Intersection Observer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From jQuery To Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’re taking a closer look at different approaches and strategies on how we can migrate a web application that uses jQuery framework, and start using one of the coolest React frameworks in the market: Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Introduction (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS refactoring is not an easy task — it needs to be done in a way that doesn't create problems. First we need to analyze the existing codebase, audit CSS codebase health, discover weaknesses, agree on the approach, and convince management to invest time and resources into the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19369</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/10/science-and-technology-links-july-10th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use CRISPR, a state-of-the-art gene editing technique, to edit the genes of live human patients in a clinical trials. A clinical trial has begun regarding an HIV vaccine. If you choose to forgo meat to fight climate change, you may lower your individual’s lifetime warming contribution by 2 to 4%. Age-related testosterone loss may … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making A Strong Case For Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility is often overlooked or bolted on to the end of a project. Let’s figure out how to implement and advocate for accessibility from the inception of a project to the release or handoff and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Todd Libby)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools And Practices To Speed Up The Vue.js Development Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though Vue.js claims to have an approachable minimalist framework that can be incrementally adaptable, it can be a little bit overwhelming when starting as a Vue.js newbie. In this article, we’re looking at ways to make writing Vue.js a breeze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Uma Victor)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>