<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-11T00:59:44.070Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-11T00:59:44.070Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Intentional Remote Collaboration - Like GitLab]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linearb/build-intentional-remote-collaboration-like-gitlab-4dli</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linearb/build-intentional-remote-collaboration-like-gitlab-4dli"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T00:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The office of the 20th century is a testament to design. A great deal of thought goes into the layout of a building. How are the offices laid out? Where are the elevators located? Where will teams meet? But the focus on co-located office space is quickly becoming a relic of the past. To meet the challenges of the 21st century GitLab’s Head of Remote Darren Murph is pushing organizations to put just as much thought into their remote work structure as they would an office building.
For many companies, the transition to this mindset comes with difficulty. They’ve shifted into remote work as a necessity, but maintain the 20th-century ‘office-first’ mindset. While this is passable and **can **work, it’s not ultimately taking advantage of the key benefits of a virtual atmosphere.
To take advanta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Bronsdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding HTML Anchor Tag <a>]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/understanding-html-anchor-tag-a-1i44</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/understanding-html-anchor-tag-a-1i44"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T00:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The <a> HTML element (or anchor element), with its href attribute, creates a hyperlink to web pages, files, email addresses, locations on the same page, or anything else a URL can address. Content within each <a> should indicate the link's destination.
www.developer.mozilla.org
When To use anchor tags?
<a href="www.example.com>text</a>
Example:





  
  
  Relative URLs


<a href="/about-me">about me</a>
<a href="mailto:example@gmail.com">text</a>
Example:





  
  
  Phone Number


<a href="tel:+12345678910>text</a>
Example:





  
  
  a section or a part of your page


<a href="#section-id">text</a>
Example:





  
  
  Image as a link





<a href="link">
    <img src="img link" />
</a>

Example:





  
  
  Javascript Code


<a href="javascript:codeblock">text</a>





  
  
  References



www.developer.mozilla.org
www.w3schools.com
To Contact Me:
email: developer.aya.b@gmail.com
telegram: Aya Bouchiha
Have a great day!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Bouchiha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Megafires Are Solvable]]></title>
        <id>https://gabekleinman.medium.com/california-megafires-are-solvable-b3e01af873dd</id>
        <link href="https://gabekleinman.medium.com/california-megafires-are-solvable-b3e01af873dd"/>
        <updated>2021-08-11T00:09:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Siberia’s wildfires are bigger than all the world’s other blazes combined]]></title>
        <id>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2021/08/11/siberia-fires-russia-climate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2021/08/11/siberia-fires-russia-climate/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T22:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: YouTube Musical Spectrum – visualizer for YouTube with musical notes]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/mfcc64/youtube-musical-spectrum</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/mfcc64/youtube-musical-spectrum"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T22:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Destructuring and the Spread Operator – Explained with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>610e151e3306a507d1bffb32</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-destructuring-and-spread-operator-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has two awesome data structures that help you write clean and efficient code. But handling them can get messy sometimes. In this blog, I am going to show you how to handle destructuring in arrays and objects in JavaScript. We'll also learn how to use the spread operator as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev log for Wonder Wanderer 2: Day 10 #LOWREZJAM 😁]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/michaelprimo/dev-log-for-wonder-wanderer-2-day-10-lowrezjam-ed7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/michaelprimo/dev-log-for-wonder-wanderer-2-day-10-lowrezjam-ed7"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What did I do today?


I finished all the hazards, so the game can be tomorrow on alpha state. Here is some tests:

You can in the game move in two ways (top down and sidescrolling), avoid spikes and holes, wrap through the screen, switch layouts, hop down to platforms, going to other rooms with their gravity. Here is an example of the reverse gravity, but I made a normal one, lighter, heavy, zero and reverse.

 Example for a gameplay with Reverse gravity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Primo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote First, Not Remote Friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linearb/remote-first-not-remote-friendly-3jhm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linearb/remote-first-not-remote-friendly-3jhm"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shweta Saraf, the Senior Director of Engineering at Equinix, has a unique remote work story: she experienced a fully remote acquisition during the pandemic.
Her former employer — Packet — was acquired by Equinix, a huge company with more than 30,000 employees and over 200 locations around the world. Suddenly, the small team at Packet who were experts at remote work found themselves in the position of trying to onboard not just themselves at a new company, but onboard an organization of 30,000+ to the principles, structure, and best practices of a fully remote work environment. Because Equinix is the largest data center company in the world, operating data centers and office hubs all over the globe, the switch to remote work had to be as seamless and efficient as possible.
One of the key ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Bronsdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View Source (on Mobile)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346392</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/view-source-on-mobile/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wished you could see the HTML source of a web page while on a mobile browser, which generally doesn’t offer that feature? If you have a desktop machine around, there are ways, but what I mean …
The post View Source (on Mobile) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Court Orders BitMEX to Pay $100M over Illegal Crypto Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8412-21</id>
        <link href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8412-21"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unity to acquire Parsec for $320M]]></title>
        <id>https://investors.unity.com/news/news-details/2021/Unity-Enters-Into-Agreement-to-Acquire-Parsec/default.aspx</id>
        <link href="https://investors.unity.com/news/news-details/2021/Unity-Enters-Into-Agreement-to-Acquire-Parsec/default.aspx"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giuseppe 'Bepi' Colombo: Grandfather of the orbital fly-by]]></title>
        <id>https://www.esa.int/About_Us/ESA_history/Giuseppe_Bepi_Colombo_Grandfather_of_the_fly-by</id>
        <link href="https://www.esa.int/About_Us/ESA_history/Giuseppe_Bepi_Colombo_Grandfather_of_the_fly-by"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 7 Featured DEV Posts from the Past Week]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/top-7-featured-dev-posts-from-the-past-week-3h2i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/top-7-featured-dev-posts-from-the-past-week-3h2i"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every Tuesday we round up the previous week's top posts based on traffic, engagement, and a hint of editorial curation. The typical week starts on Monday and ends on Sunday, but don't worry, we take into account posts that are published later in the week. 
@fanniegunton
 created this guide for future clients after a poorly-planned project wrapped to make it better the next time around. Super helpful stuff in here!
Set Yourself Up For an Easier Development Project...
Fannie E Gunton ・ Aug 6 ・ 4 min read
#webdev
        #productivity
        #career
        #contracting
      
Step 1: be aware of your attitude when working on something new. This and manny more mindset-shifting tips for tackling hard challenges via @tomeraitz
.
The Right Mindset To Solve Complex Problems
Tomer Raitz ・ Aug 7 ・…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gracie Gregory (she/her)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Web Development Basics – HTML, CSS, and JavaScript Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>610d11273306a507d1bfeffe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-css-and-javascript-explained-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are learning web development, you will come across terms like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. These are often called the building blocks of the Web.  These three tools dominate web development. Every library or tool seems to be centered around HTML, CSS, and JS. So if you want to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avenue (YC W21) Is Hiring Full-Stack Engineers in NYC (TypeScript, Node, React)]]></title>
        <id>https://useavenue.notion.site/Software-Engineer-Avenue-d68ff1ec6b064380b3afa85d5d1b3276</id>
        <link href="https://useavenue.notion.site/Software-Engineer-Avenue-d68ff1ec6b064380b3afa85d5d1b3276"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T21:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please Log in with Router's Password]]></title>
        <id>https://www.google.com/search?q=%22Please+log+in+with+router%27s+password%22</id>
        <link href="https://www.google.com/search?q=%22Please+log+in+with+router%27s+password%22"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T20:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Way to Learn Python – Python Programming Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>610642353306a507d1bfbfe4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-way-to-learn-python-python-programming-tutorial-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T20:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a great programming language to learn and you can use it in a variety of areas in software development. You can use Python for web development, data analysis, machine learning, artificial intelligence, and more.  With the vast amount of resources to choose from, sometimes it is hard to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python any() and all() Functions – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6108f8453306a507d1bfce17</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-any-and-all-functions-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T20:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When coding in Python, have you ever had to check if any item or all items in an iterable evaluate to True? The next time you need to do so, be sure to use the nifty functions any() and all(). In this tutorial, we'll learn about Python's any() and all(]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Culdesac Tempe: The first car-free neighborhood built from scratch in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://culdesac.com/</id>
        <link href="https://culdesac.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T20:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Communities You Need to Join Today!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/remotesynth/developer-communities-you-need-to-join-today-1505</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/remotesynth/developer-communities-you-need-to-join-today-1505"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding is hard. And there is so much to learn, no one person can really know it all. I think that's why developers tend to rely on the developer community so much (more than other types of jobs I think). It's why welcoming community hubs like dev.to have exploded.
In this post, I wanted to share three communities that offer the opportunity to learn from and connect with your fellow developers. They are communities that I participate in actively and have gained a lot from. Even when they cater to new or aspiring developers (as a couple of them tend to do), I've found amazing opportunities to learn, even as someone with decades of experience as a developer.
CFE.dev



I am totally biased about this one as I created it and run it, but I do that as a way to give back to the developer community…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Rinaldi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Coding? Computer Coding Definition]]></title>
        <id>61122afb72231b077cdac810</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're starting your coding journey, one of the most exciting – and at times overwhelming – things about it is just how much there is to learn.  You'll discover different languages, frameworks, libraries, inventions and conventions.  One technology often requires knowledge of another one, and everything seems to be interconnected and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons Why You Should Start Using Rust for Personal Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bexxmodd/5-reasons-why-you-should-start-using-rust-for-personal-projects-49pb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bexxmodd/5-reasons-why-you-should-start-using-rust-for-personal-projects-49pb"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Importance of Personal Projects
contract theory.






    Signaling is the way how one party (namely agent) dispatches the information about itself to another acting party (namely principal). In the job market, this can be seen as an attempt by the potential candidate to showcase their ability to the potential employer. For example, your bachelor's degree (if you have one) is a form of signaling. It shows that for at least four years you worked hard, managed to pass the required class, and hopefully attained knowledge.





    Side projects or portfolio projects are also a form of signaling. They convey a message to the potential hiring managers that you can show initiative. You can take ownership of the project and work on it independently. It also demonstrates that you have a genuine i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beka Modebadze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JWT with RSA Signature]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tayfunakgc/jwt-with-rsa-signature-1jd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tayfunakgc/jwt-with-rsa-signature-1jd"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone!
In this article we will learn how to sign JSON Web Token with RSA key.
Let’s start!
First of all, I'm gonna create the project folder. Then install jsonwebtoken package.
cd path/to/your/workspace
# Create project folder
mkdir jwt-rsa
# Change directory
cd jwt-rsa
npm init -y
# Install JWT
npm install --save jsonwebtoken

Now let's generate public and private key. If you increase the key length, token length will be increase too. This means HTTP request body size will be increase. But also it depends what kind of payload we we'll sign.
# Create a folder named keys
mkdir keys
# Minimum RSA key length is 1024 bits
# Maximum RSA key length is 16384 bits 
# Don't add passphrase
ssh-keygen -t rsa -b 1024 -m PEM -f keys/rsa.key
# Write public key to keys/rsa.key.pub file
openssl r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tayfun Akgüç</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips for better programming in distributed teams 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chispitaos/tips-for-better-programming-in-distributed-teams-3ipk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chispitaos/tips-for-better-programming-in-distributed-teams-3ipk"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:22:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been working remote and freelance for the last 18 years, and my experience told me that working remotely with a distributed team is easier if you set a standard, using some basic and simple rules. 🤓 Remember that you have to work with different people that have different ways of coding.
Code can always work, but can you maintain it across the years?
This is the important part for me: maintain the development and release new features without rewriting it.
Those are simple tips, for best practices, in long term developments with distributed teams:
Always comment on your code, even if you think that you understand it. Because tomorrow you're not available and some  colleague has to continue it.
Try to set a standard for variable names, don't let your team use any names. Please, I beg yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vero O</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🤔 Any YouTuber Make HTML/CSS Video Tutorials? 😍]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/frontendor/any-youtuber-make-html-css-video-tutorials-2aj1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/frontendor/any-youtuber-make-html-css-video-tutorials-2aj1"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello 👋,
In July 2020, Me & my friend released Frontendor UI Library that lets developers construct gorgeous landing pages quickly and easily by Copy-Paste method. 
We are looking for creators who can make a video tutorials showcase Frontendor and in return we offer 40% For Every Customer ( ≈ $23 / Sale ).
** Of course, before all this we can give you a full access to give it a try then decide **
If you believe that we can Make More Success Together 🙌. Please contact us in the live chat.
https://frontendor.com
Thanks for reading 😎 You are awesome.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frontendor Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok overtakes Facebook as most downloaded app]]></title>
        <id>https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/TikTok-overtakes-Facebook-as-world-s-most-downloaded-app</id>
        <link href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/TikTok-overtakes-Facebook-as-world-s-most-downloaded-app"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publish your Markdown docs on GitHub Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ar2pi/publish-your-markdown-docs-on-github-pages-6pe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ar2pi/publish-your-markdown-docs-on-github-pages-6pe"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer you've most likely switched machines, even OS several times. Or maybe you've performed a specific set of operations that you might have to repeat in the future? want to remember some commands? share code snippets? capture online course notes? 
For all of the reasons above, and many more, having a personal documentation website is ideal. It lets you organize and synthesize all the information that is relevant to YOU in your own personal way, with the added benefit of being easily sharable. 
A project containing all your Markdown files, hosted on Github Pages.
Requirements
Python 3 (tested with version 3.9.5+)
Git
Make 
mkdocs


We'll use mkdocs as static site generator, so let's install it:
pip install mkdocs

Now create the basic project structure, in your projects folder:
m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Picerna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[👋 Virtual Timekeeper]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/asombachinonso/virtual-timekeeper-389l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/asombachinonso/virtual-timekeeper-389l"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T19:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An easy to use online timekeeper buddy built in JavaScript.
I managed a virtual competition where I poorly allocated time and could not properly allocate time to each competing team, and this was the inspiration for this project.
Like, Follow, and let's collaborate.
https://codepen.io/asombachinonso/full/PomXvge]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asomba Emmanuel Chinonso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interstellar nuclear-powered transport (FJ Dyson) (1968) [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://people.eecs.berkeley.edu/~pister/publications/FamousPapers/DysonInterstellarOrion.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://people.eecs.berkeley.edu/~pister/publications/FamousPapers/DysonInterstellarOrion.pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T18:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 VS Code Extensions to Increase Your Productivity]]></title>
        <id>610ef4fc3306a507d1c00257</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/10-vscode-extensions-to-increase-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T18:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best things about VS Code is the rich library of extensions you can use to speed up your coding and make your life easier.  Some of these extensions are paid, but there are tons of quality options that are available for free in the VS Code Marketplace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPL's Plan for the Next Mars Helicopter]]></title>
        <id>https://spectrum.ieee.org/the-next-mars-helicopter</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/the-next-mars-helicopter"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T18:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Web Scraping Tutorial – How to Scrape Data From Any Website with Python]]></title>
        <id>610ce4f83306a507d1bfeba5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-scrape-websites-with-python-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T17:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping is the process of extracting specific data from the internet automatically. It has many use cases, like getting data for a machine learning project, creating a price comparison tool, or any other innovative idea that requires an immense amount of data. While you can theoretically do data extraction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Against DDoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>5fff3e3798be260817e495df</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/protect-against-ddos-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T17:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attacks aim to take an organization or service offline and originate from multiple, distributed hosts.  The difficult part of defending against DDoS attacks is that the hosts are distributed – if it were a single host or small group, you could easily block the traffic with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Codex]]></title>
        <id>https://openai.com/blog/openai-codex/</id>
        <link href="https://openai.com/blog/openai-codex/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T17:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$600M taken in largest DeFi hack to date]]></title>
        <id>https://blockworks.co/hackers-steal-over-600m-biggest-in-defi-history/</id>
        <link href="https://blockworks.co/hackers-steal-over-600m-biggest-in-defi-history/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T17:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomical Engineering: A Strategy for Modifying Planetary Orbits (2001)]]></title>
        <id>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001Ap%26SS.275..349K/abstract</id>
        <link href="https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001Ap%26SS.275..349K/abstract"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T17:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format a String in Python]]></title>
        <id>60f7aef31d2b080797b80a01</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-format-a-string-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formatting a string is something you'll do all the time when you're coding in Python. For every variable, tuple, and dictionary and the logic that we define, we eventually have to either print or display it in some form.  And each of these, without exception, require us to format the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elementary OS 6 Odin]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.elementary.io/elementary-os-6-odin-released/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.elementary.io/elementary-os-6-odin-released/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T16:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crows have been shown to understand the concept of zero]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/animals-can-count-and-use-zero-how-far-does-their-number-sense-go-20210809/</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/animals-can-count-and-use-zero-how-far-does-their-number-sense-go-20210809/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T15:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible Markdown in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345861</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsible-markdown-in-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown truly is a great format. It’s close enough to plain text so that anyone can quickly learn it, and it’s structured enough that it can be parsed and eventually converted to you name it.
That being said: parsing, processing, …
The post Responsible Markdown in Next.js appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kitty Giraudel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WooCommerce With Apple Pay and Google Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345799</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/woocommerce-with-apple-pay-and-google-pay/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Got a WooCommerce store? It behooves you to offer a variety of payment methods. Just anecdotally, I’m sure both you and me have been annoyed and even abandoned purchases when a merchant, online or …
The post WooCommerce With Apple Pay and Google Pay appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Nesting, specificity, and you]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346355</id>
        <link href="https://kilianvalkhof.com/2021/css-html/css-nesting-specificity-and-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Kilian Valkhof on CSS nesting which isn’t available in browsers yet, but will be soon. There are a few differences he notes between CSS nesting and nesting in Sass or Less though. Take, for example, the following code:
div 
…
The post CSS Nesting, specificity, and you appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Write universally accessible SQL, not library-specific ORM wrapper APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/craigmichaelmartin/pure-orm</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/craigmichaelmartin/pure-orm"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust in Production: Qovery]]></title>
        <id>https://serokell.io/blog/rust-in-production-qovery</id>
        <link href="https://serokell.io/blog/rust-in-production-qovery"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 91 introduces enhanced cookie clearing]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/security/2021/08/10/firefox-91-introduces-enhanced-cookie-clearing/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/security/2021/08/10/firefox-91-introduces-enhanced-cookie-clearing/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch YC S21: Meet the Batch, Thread #5]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28128957</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28128957"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T14:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MinIO: A Bare Metal Drop-In for AWS S3]]></title>
        <id>https://tech.marksblogg.com/minio-aws-s3-hdfs.html</id>
        <link href="https://tech.marksblogg.com/minio-aws-s3-hdfs.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T13:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Big O Notation]]></title>
        <id>610abfc03306a507d1bfde47</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-big-o-notation/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T13:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big O notation is an important tools for computer scientists to analyze the cost of an algorithm. Most software engineers should have an understanding of it. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you understand Big O Notation. Georgio Tunson, aka selikapro, created]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World’s Biggest Tire Graveyard in Kuwait Is on Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://scoopempire.com/kuwait-tire-graveyards/</id>
        <link href="https://scoopempire.com/kuwait-tire-graveyards/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T12:51:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cookieless Alternative To Embed HTML, CSS And JS Code Snippets]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/cookieless-alternative-embed-html-css-js-code-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/cookieless-alternative-embed-html-css-js-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embedding code examples with third-party scripts often leads to tracking or cookies. We always wanted to have a simple website with a good UX, so setting cookies for no reason wasn’t an option for us. Now, with Indiepen, we are proud to introduce a privacy-friendly alternative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Henrik Fricke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Hack APIs in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://labs.detectify.com/2021/08/10/how-to-hack-apis-in-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://labs.detectify.com/2021/08/10/how-to-hack-apis-in-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T10:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anatomy of a Program in Memory (2009)]]></title>
        <id>http://duartes.org/gustavo/blog/post/anatomy-of-a-program-in-memory/</id>
        <link href="http://duartes.org/gustavo/blog/post/anatomy-of-a-program-in-memory/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T09:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 41 With Eva PenzeyMoog: Designing For Safety]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/smashing-podcast-episode-41/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/smashing-podcast-episode-41/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about designing for safety. What does it mean to consider vulnerable users in our designs? Drew McLellan talks to expert Eva PenzeyMoog to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>https://fgiesen.wordpress.com/2017/04/11/memory-bandwidth/</id>
        <link href="https://fgiesen.wordpress.com/2017/04/11/memory-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-10T01:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Essence – An Operating System]]></title>
        <id>https://gitlab.com/nakst/essence</id>
        <link href="https://gitlab.com/nakst/essence"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T23:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choice Words about the Upcoming Deprecation of JavaScript Dialogs]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346368</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/choice-words-about-the-upcoming-deprecation-of-javascript-dialogs/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T21:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It might be the very first thing a lot of people learn in JavaScript:
alert("Hello, World");
One day at CodePen, we woke up to a ton of customer support tickets about their Pens being broken, which ultimately boiled down to …
The post Choice Words about the Upcoming Deprecation of JavaScript Dialogs appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Large, Small, and Dynamic Viewports]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346316</id>
        <link href="https://www.bram.us/2021/07/08/the-large-small-and-dynamic-viewports/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T20:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got viewport units (e.g. vw, vh, vmin, vmax), and they are mostly pretty great. It’s cool to always have a unit available that is relative to the entire screen. But when you ask people what …
The post The Large, Small, and Dynamic Viewports appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Usefulness of Useless Knowledge (1939) [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ias.edu/sites/default/files/library/UsefulnessHarpers.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://www.ias.edu/sites/default/files/library/UsefulnessHarpers.pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T19:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the CSS Paint API: Image Fragmentation Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345642</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/exploring-the-css-paint-api-image-fragmentation-effect/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T14:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous article, I created a fragmentation effect using CSS mask and custom properties. It was a neat effect but it has one drawback: it uses a lot of CSS code (generated using Sass). This time I am …
The post Exploring the CSS Paint API: Image Fragmentation Effect appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly designed 'smart' insulin could improve type 1 diabetes treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-new-kind-of-smart-insulin-could-help-diabetics-avoid-the-risks-of-low-blood-sugar-levels</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-new-kind-of-smart-insulin-could-help-diabetics-avoid-the-risks-of-low-blood-sugar-levels"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T12:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kaizen Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6712</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/kaizen-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=kaizen-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T12:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Kaizen is Japanese for “change for the better” or “continuous improvement,” and is also the title of a book by Sarah Harvey which explains this business philosophy that has expanded into the personal growth arena to give a clear pathway to reaching your goals through consistent incremental changes. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post Kaizen Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/3 From A To Z: Core Concepts (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-core-concepts-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/http3-core-concepts-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What exactly is HTTP/3? Why was it needed so soon after HTTP/2 (which was only finalized in 2015)? How can or should you use it? And especially, how does this improve web performance? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robin Marx)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does this medieval fresco show a hallucinogenic mushroom in the Garden of Eden?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.atlasobscura.com/articles/muscaria-hallucinogenic-mushroom-fresco</id>
        <link href="https://www.atlasobscura.com/articles/muscaria-hallucinogenic-mushroom-fresco"/>
        <updated>2021-08-09T05:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Gobbler]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346259</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-gobbler/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T19:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great little project from Ross Moody: 
SVG Gobbler is a browser extension that finds the vector content on the page you’re viewing and gives you the option to download, optimize, copy, view the code, or export it as an image.
…
The post SVG Gobbler appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Nuxt Features past v2.10]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=346290</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/new-nuxt-features-past-v2-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T15:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nuxt offers an incredible developer experience, with a lot of performance and application setup best practices baked in. In recent releases, they’ve been working on taking this developer experience to the next level, with some newer features that speed up …
The post New Nuxt Features past v2.10 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Drasner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Infinite Utility Helpers Using Inline CSS Custom Properties and calc()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345467</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/efficient-infinite-utility-helpers-using-inline-css-custom-properties-and-calc/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T14:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently wrote a very basic Sass loop that outputs several padding and margin utility classes. Nothing fancy, really, just a Sass map with 11 spacing values, looped over to create classes for both padding and margin on each side. …
The post Efficient Infinite Utility Helpers Using Inline CSS Custom Properties and calc() appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Ford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gridless.design]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345878</id>
        <link href="https://gridless.design/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T14:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donnie D’Amato built a whole site around the thesis that “digital designers still expect to use the grid while experienced layout engineers have moved beyond it.” The idea isn’t that we should never literally use display: grid; but rather that …
The post gridless.design appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bounce Back Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6708</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/bounce-back-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=bounce-back-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Bounce Back is a book by Susan Kahn, a business coach who will teach you the psychology of resilience from the perspectives of Greek philosophy, Sigmund Freud, and modern neuroscience, so you can recover quickly from professional blunders of all kinds by changing your thinking. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: […]
The post Bounce Back Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Useful VSCode Extensions For Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/useful-vscode-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code can be supercharged wuth hundreds of [VS Code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/). In this article, Leonardo shares four useful extensions that help him in his daily work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Buggy React Code Examples and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345418</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/three-buggy-react-code-examples-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T14:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s usually more than one way to code a thing in React. And while it’s possible to create the same thing different ways, there may be one or two approaches that technically work “better” than others. I actually run into …
The post Three Buggy React Code Examples and How to Fix Them appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hugh Haworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Disabled Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/frustrating-design-patterns-disabled-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we make disabled buttons more inclusive? When do they work well, and when do they fail on us? And finally, when do we actually need them, and how can we avoid them? Let’s find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full-Stack Mobile Application With Flutter, Fauna, and GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345552</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-build-a-full-stack-mobile-application-with-flutter-fauna-and-graphql/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-05T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Flutter is Google’s UI framework used to create flexible, expressive cross-platform mobile applications. It is one of the fastest-growing frameworks for mobile app development. On the other hand, Fauna is a transactional, developer-friendly serverless …
The post How to Build a Full-Stack Mobile Application With Flutter, Fauna, and GraphQL appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shadid Haque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web Workers In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345866</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T23:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You gotta appreciate the tenacity of Surma. He’s been advocating for Web Workers as a path forward to better-feeling websites for a lot of years now. He’s at it again making sure we all understand the landscape:
[…] regardless 
…
The post The State Of Web Workers In 2021 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using CSS Shapes for Interesting User Controls and Navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345274</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-css-shapes-for-interesting-user-controls-and-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T14:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Straight across or down, that’s the proverbial order for user controls on a screen. Like a list of menu items. But what if we change that to a more fluid layout with bends, curves, and nooks? We can pull it …
The post Using CSS Shapes for Interesting User Controls and Navigation appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Socialism Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6696</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/socialism-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=socialism-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Socialism by Michael Newman outlines the history of the governmental theory that everything should be owned and controlled by the community as a whole, including how this idea has impacted the world in the last 200 years, how its original aims have been lost, and ways we might use it in the future. Read in: […]
The post Socialism Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Children And Iteration Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/react-children-iteration-methods/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-04T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll discuss and learn about the use case of iterating over React `children` and the ways to do it. In particular, we will deep dive into one of the utility methods, `React.Children.toArray`, that React gives us, which helps to iterate over the children in a way which ensures performance and determinism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arihant Verma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How fast can you pipe a large file to a C++ program?]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19429</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/08/03/how-fast-can-you-pipe-a-large-file-to-a-c-program/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T17:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under many operating systems, you can send data from from one process to another using ‘pipes’. The term ‘pipe’ is probably used by analogy with plumbing and we often use the the symbol ‘|‘ to represent a pipe (it looks like a vertical pipe). Thus, for example, you can sort a file and send it … Continue reading How fast can you pipe a large file to a C++ program?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Resilient JavaScript UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/build-resilient-javascript-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resilience is intrinsic to the web and therefore us, web developers. This article explores how graceful degradation, defensive coding, observability, and a healthy attitude towards failures better equips us before, during, and after an error occurs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Callum Hart)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goals! Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6694</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/goals-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=goals-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T12:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Goals! By Brian Tracy shows you how to unleash the power of goal setting to help you get or become whatever you want, identifying ways to set goals that lead you to success by being specific, challenging yourself, thinking positively, preparing, adjusting your timelines on big goals, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite […]
The post Goals! Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Strategy, Regression Testing And Maintenance (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-strategy-regression-testing-maintenance-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a deep dive into the refactoring process itself, and cover incremental refactoring strategy, visual regression testing, and maintaining the refactored codebase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19419</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/31/science-and-technology-links-july-31st-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T19:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers built a microscope that might be 10 times better than the best available microscopes. Subsidizing college education can lower earnings due to lower job experience: The Post 9/11 GI Bill (PGIB) is among the largest and most generous college subsidies enacted thus far in the U.S. (…) the introduction of the PGIB raised college … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes In August (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2021. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6687</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/now-discover-your-strengths-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=now-discover-your-strengths-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Now, Discover Your Strengths shows you how to find your top five strengths by outlining what strengths are, how you get them, why they’re important to reaching your full potential, and how to discover your own through analyzing the times when your behavior is the most natural or instinctive and why. Read in: 4 […]
The post Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An E-Commerce Site With Angular 11, Commerce Layer And Paypal]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having an e-commerce store is crucial for any store owner as more and more customers are turning to online shopping. In this tutorial, we shall go through how to create an e-commerce site with Angular 11. The site will use the Commerce Layer as a headless e-commerce API and use Paypal to process payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19408</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/29/measuring-memory-usage-virtual-versus-real-memory/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T21:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developers are often concerned with the memory usage of their applications, and rightly so. Software that uses too much memory can fail, or be slow. Memory allocation will not work the same way under all systems. However, at a high level, most modern operating systems have virtual memory and physical memory (RAM). When you write … Continue reading Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Such Thing As A CSS Absolute Unit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are absolute units? What are the differences between relative and absolute units, and how do we create accurate sizes on the web? In this article, Elad Shechter explains why CSS absolute units aren’t so absolute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elad Shechter)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Democracies Die Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6683</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-democracies-die-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-democracies-die-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How Democracies Die explores the foundational ideas of democracy by looking at historical events, especially in Latin America, that show how democracies have failed, whether it can happen again, and how to protect democracy from threats like mutual toleration, inequality, and political parties. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: When Donald […]
The post How Democracies Die Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating An Accessible Dialog From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dialogs are everywhere in modern interface design (for good or for bad), and yet many of them are not accessible to assistive technologies. In this article, we will dig into how to create a short script to create accessible dialogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kitty Giraudel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global vs. Local Styling In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has strong opinions about how to organize JavaScript but not CSS. How can we develop patterns that encourage best CSS practices while also following the framework’s logic? The answer is surprisingly simple — to write well-structured CSS that balances global and local styling concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Dubovoy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kindness Method Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6677</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-kindness-method-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-kindness-method-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T12:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Kindness Method by Shahroo Izadi teaches how self-compassion and understanding make forming habits easier than being hard on yourself, using the personal experiences of the author and what she’s learned as an addiction recovery therapist to show how self-esteem is the true key to behavior change. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post The Kindness Method Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Serverless Functions And The International Space Station]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby recently announced the launch of “functions”. In this article, Paul Scanlon explains how to get the current location of the International Space Station (ISS) as it orbits the Earth in real-time using [Gatsby Functions](https://www.gatsbyjs.com/docs/reference/functions/) and then display it on a 3D interactive globe using [React Three Fibre](https://github.com/pmndrs/react-three-fiber).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soundtracks Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6665</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/soundtracks-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=soundtracks-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T12:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Soundtracks is New York Times bestselling author Jon Acuff’s 2021 book that teaches you how to beat overthinking by challenging whether your thoughts are true, retiring unhelpful and unkind ideas, adopting thought-boosting mantras from others, using symbols to reinforce positive thoughts, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Is there […]
The post Soundtracks Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Attracting Clients To Your Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many web design agencies consider it a badge of honor that they win work exclusively through word-of-mouth recommendations. In this article, Paul Boag explains why that is entirely the wrong attitude and what to do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Time To Your Schedule As A Professional]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you running a business and have too many things going on at once? Meetings, bugs, customer feedback, new clients in addition to your already tight deadlines? Let’s face it, time management is hard, and it becomes even more difficult in the trying times we are in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[75 Hard Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6657</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/75-hard-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=75-hard-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: 75 Hard is a fitness challenge and book that teaches mental toughness by making you commit to five daily critical tasks for 75 days straight, including drinking a gallon of water, reading 10 pages of a non-fiction book, doing two 45-minute workouts, taking a progress picture, and following a diet. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post 75 Hard Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? We’ve collected some useful color tools and resources that we’ve discovered lately — to help you get the most out of your creativity. We’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [accessible front-end components](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/complete-guide-accessible-front-end-components/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fail Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6656</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-fail-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-fail-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T12:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Fail shows the surprising benefits of going through a difficult time through the experiences of the author, Elizabeth Day, including the failures in her life that she’s grateful for and how they’ve helped her grow, uncovering why we shouldn’t be so afraid of failure but instead embrace it. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post How To Fail Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From WordPress To A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at when it makes sense to migrate from a monolithic project to a headless setup and the benefits that come with it. In addition to a step-by-step guide on how to migrate WordPress to Storyblok Headless CMS, the problems that will arise during the process and how to deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining End-To-End Quality With Visual Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding visual elements to your tests, you can gain more options to add meaningful ways in maintaining a high level of quality for your app. Colby Fayock explains how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Colby Fayock)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Insights I Gained While Researching Vue.js Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web app accessibility appears difficult because it seems that there is little information on the subject available online. Let’s take a closer look at the accessible use of framework features, concrete Vue.js traits, as well as community initiatives and vetted patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISR vs DPR: Big Words, Quick Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two strategies for incrementally building websites that are growing in popularity: Incremental Static Regeneration and Distributed Persistent Rendering. What’s the difference? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cassidy Williams)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Do That With A JavaScript Data Grid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll get to see some pretty groundbreaking things you can achieve with modern JavaScript grids and discover new ways to augment a data grid to make it engaging, responsive, and accessible. All this will be illustrated using Kendo UI Data Grids and their features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19380</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/14/faster-sorted-array-unions-by-reducing-branches/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing an index, a database or a search engine, you frequently need to compute the union of two sorted sets. When I am not using fancy low-level instructions, I have most commonly computed the union of two sorted sets using the following approach: v1 = first value in input 1 v2 = first value … Continue reading Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Broken Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Too often dealing with filters can be frustrating. Let’s get them right. That means never freeze the UI on a single input, provide text input fallback and never auto-scroll users on a single input. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Dynamic Header With Intersection Observer]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, attaching an event listener to constantly fire a callback on scroll can be performance-intensive. But there is a better way with Intersection Observer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From jQuery To Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’re taking a closer look at different approaches and strategies on how we can migrate a web application that uses jQuery framework, and start using one of the coolest React frameworks in the market: Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Introduction (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS refactoring is not an easy task — it needs to be done in a way that doesn't create problems. First we need to analyze the existing codebase, audit CSS codebase health, discover weaknesses, agree on the approach, and convince management to invest time and resources into the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>