<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-11T00:57:18.665Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-11T00:57:18.665Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Cheat sheet (Updated June 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ericchapman/react-cheat-sheet-updated-may-2021-1mcd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ericchapman/react-cheat-sheet-updated-may-2021-1mcd"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T00:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't use React often and so whenever I need to do even the smallest thing in React, I have to check out the documentation, a tutorial, or post a question on a forum.
That's why I decided to do this memory aid and given that my memory is not that good I thought why not make a monstrous memory aid with all the concepts I know about React.
So I can read it from time to time and thereby strengthen my knowledge of React.
If you have ideas or recommendation do not hesitate and do so in the comments section.
React Cheat Sheet
 

Create a React App
// Create a new app
npx create-react-app my-app-name

// Run the created app
cd my-app-name
yarn start

// http://localhost:3000

First React functional Component
No need to import React from 'react' (since React 17)
Must have uppercase first letter
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Chapman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put a Background on Open Details Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342050</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/put-a-background-on-open-details-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T00:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing that can be just a smidge funky about the <details> element is that, when open, it’s not always 100% clear what is inside that element and what isn’t. I’m not saying that always matters or that it’s a …
The post Put a Background on Open Details Elements appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Crunch” Open Source Texture Compression Library vs. US Patent #20110115806]]></title>
        <id>https://richg42.blogspot.com/2012/07/the-saga-of-crunch.html</id>
        <link href="https://richg42.blogspot.com/2012/07/the-saga-of-crunch.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T00:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Container Registry: BETTER than Docker Hub?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/github/github-container-registry-better-than-docker-hub-1o9k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/github/github-container-registry-better-than-docker-hub-1o9k"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T23:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Container Registry improves how we handle containers within GitHub. Let's see what it is, how it works, and if it is better than Docker Hub.
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video with the whole explanation and demo, which to be fair is much more complete than this post.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/WjzA9dfk5w4
If you rather prefer reading, well... let's just continue :)
The GitHub Container Registry (GHCR) is a redesigned, enhanced version of GitHub Packages. It not only replaces the Packages Docker service, but also it represents a fundamental shift in how GitHub will provide packages to its customers, because Packages are now tied to organizations and accounts instead of repos. 
And in the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide 'CoderDave' Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome abandons 'simplified domain experiment' in omnibar]]></title>
        <id>https://bugs.chromium.org/p/chromium/issues/detail?id=1090393#c75</id>
        <link href="https://bugs.chromium.org/p/chromium/issues/detail?id=1090393#c75"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T23:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why we shipped a Next.js SDK, and how you can use it]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sentry/why-we-shipped-a-next-js-sdk-and-how-you-can-use-it-14jp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sentry/why-we-shipped-a-next-js-sdk-and-how-you-can-use-it-14jp"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T23:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you could probably tell from the title, we shipped an SDK for Next.js. This means you can capture errors, measure performance, manage releases, configure suspect commits, and automatically upload sourcemaps to view unminified JavaScript and TypeScript with zero(-ish) configuration.
Why was Next.js next on our list? Well, it’s one of the fastest-growing React frameworks and developers love it. Next.js provides a developer experience that helps with building features rapidly, seeing local changes quickly, and reducing build times.
"Next.js turns traditionally complex decisions into simple implementation details. Spinning up new pages with our existing React components and Material UI went from days to hours with Next." 
– Sean Parmelee, Applications Architect, Care.com
To monitor Next.js …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Chhabria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chime has detected 535 fast radio bursts, quadrupling the known tally]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-021-01560-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-021-01560-4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T22:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDA approves drug to treat smallpox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fda.gov/drugs/drug-safety-and-availability/fda-approves-drug-treat-smallpox</id>
        <link href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/drug-safety-and-availability/fda-approves-drug-treat-smallpox"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T22:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Frankfurt Status: Engineers are still not able to enter the affected part]]></title>
        <id>https://status.aws.amazon.com/#EU_block</id>
        <link href="https://status.aws.amazon.com/#EU_block"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T22:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding CORS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/useanvil/understanding-cors-5gm5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/useanvil/understanding-cors-5gm5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T22:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CORS, or Cross-Origin Resource Sharing, is one thing that can bite a developer
For example, CORS can help prevent a malicious case where a website executes an
XMLHttpRequest) to a different
Let’s take a look at how that would work in a world without CORS:
A user just visited "https://mybank.example", one of the most popular
banking websites, to complete a few transactions.
The user, maybe on another tab, visits "http://not-suspicious.example".
Unknown to the user, not-suspicious.example contains a script that
sends requests to a list of endpoints from very popular banking sites. This
is all done in the background.
If a response comes back containing user session data or other sensitive
user data, the malicious site now has the means to impersonate the user.
Now the same example, but on a b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anvil Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My TPRCiC 2021 review]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thibaultduponchelle/tprcic-2021-review-56k3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thibaultduponchelle/tprcic-2021-review-56k3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T22:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I wrote a (poignant?) review of TPRCiC as one of my first blog posts.
Once again this year, I attended The Perl and Raku Conference in the Cloud (and I even talked 😱 🙊), so here we go again for the review!
Brad Lhotsky came with a very solid talk... 👍
With a live demo (he's mad). That worked! (he's lucky good 😁) 
And the overall was very nice to listen (he's maybe experimented at this exercise - EDIT: yes he is).

I enjoyed the topic (ElasticSearch), the comparisons and expertise about this technology and other related ones.
And... Yes... A working live demo... What else?
OpenFoodFacts well deserved his lightning talk. 
Stephane Giganded presented this project (does it really need to be introduced?) discussed about GSOC (or similar) and sent a call to volunteers!

I love when…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tib</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds: Get vaccinated. Stop believing the anti-vax lies]]></title>
        <id>https://lkml.org/lkml/2021/6/10/957</id>
        <link href="https://lkml.org/lkml/2021/6/10/957"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T21:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[E2E Sandbox with Test-containers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mvillarrealb/e2e-sandbox-with-test-containers-1b01</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mvillarrealb/e2e-sandbox-with-test-containers-1b01"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T21:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[End to End tests can be cumbersome the mayority of the times, we need to wire up a lot of services (cache servers, database engines, message brokers etc) resulting in a big ball of stuff to do in order to run a simple test.
These tests are the most expensive ones in the test pyramid, but are the ones closer to a real production scenario. 
While unit tests ensures our business logic is ok, e2e tests ensures that our platform will perform accordingly with no surprises.
In this article we are going to put hands up with testcontainers to create an e2e sandbox and run some postman assertions through newman.
Tescontainers is a java library to run containers in JUnit tests, it provides lightweight containers environment to create infraestructure service and test real case scenarios(Database conne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Villarreal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May: Forem Twitch Events Roundup 👾]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/may-forem-twitch-events-roundup-h78</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/may-forem-twitch-events-roundup-h78"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T21:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May, Nick Taylor and I had the privilege to speak with 4 awesome guests. This is a round up of all the wonderful guests who joined us and a special pair programming episode where Nick and I talk about GitHub and contributing to open source projects.



Nick Taylor and Jerome Hardaway discussed Vets Who Code, job hunting during the pandemic, habits, and more. 
Places to follow Jerome:
Personal Twitter
Vets Who Code



Nick and I talked about the DEV community Bug Smash, Contributing to open source, and some important  features of GitHub, and Git.
A few of the links mentioned in the stream:
Talk by Nick Taylor on Getting the Most Out of Open Source
Forem Docs
GitHub CLI

  
    
Join Us For the First DEV Community Bug Smash!
Christina Gorton ・ May 4 ・ 4 min read
#devbugsmash
        #open…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christina Gorton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physicists measure the gravitational force between the smallest masses yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/physicists-measure-the-gravitational-force-between-the-smallest-masses-yet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/physicists-measure-the-gravitational-force-between-the-smallest-masses-yet/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T21:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Inheritance So You Don't Repeat Yourself & Notes.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rthefounding/using-inheritance-so-you-don-t-repeat-yourself-ba8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rthefounding/using-inheritance-so-you-don-t-repeat-yourself-ba8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T21:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a principle in programming called Don't Repeat Yourself (DRY). The reason repeated code is a problem is because any change requires fixing code in multiple places. This usually means more work for programmers and more room for errors.


Notice in the example below that the eat method is shared by Cat and Bear:




function Cat(name) {
  this.name = name;
}

Cat.prototype = {
  constructor: Cat,
  eat: function() {
    console.log("nom nom nom");
  }
};

function Bear(name) {
  this.name = name;
}

Bear.prototype = {
  constructor: Bear,
  eat: function() {
    console.log("nom nom nom");
  }
};

The eat method is repeated in two places. The code can be edited to follow the DRY principle by creating a supertype (or parent) called Animal:




function Animal() { }

Animal.prototype =…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Randy Rivera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Where an Object’s Prototype Comes From]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rthefounding/understanding-where-an-object-s-prototype-comes-from-4a64</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rthefounding/understanding-where-an-object-s-prototype-comes-from-4a64"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T21:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just like people inherit genes from their parents, an object inherits its prototype directly from the constructor function that created it. For example, here the Dog constructor creates the beagle object:




function Dog(name) {
  this.name = name;
}

let beagle = new Dog("Snoopy");

beagle inherits its prototype from the Dog constructor function. You can show this relationship with the isPrototypeOf method:




Dog.prototype.isPrototypeOf(beagle);

This would return true.
All objects in JavaScript (with a few exceptions) have a prototype. Also, an object’s prototype itself is an object.




function Dog(name) {
  this.name = name;
}

typeof Dog.prototype; // yields object

Because a prototype is an object, a prototype can have its own prototype! In this case, the prototype of Bird.prototype is Object.prototype:


How is this useful? You may recall the hasOwnProperty method from a previous post:




let beagle = new Dog("Snoopy");
beagle.hasOwnProperty("name");

The hasOwnProperty method is defined in Object.prototype, which can be accessed by Dog.prototype, which can then be accessed by beagle. This is an example of the prototype chain. In this prototype chain, Dog is the supertype for beagle, while beagle is the subtype. Object is a supertype for both Dog and beagle. Object is a supertype for all objects in JavaScript. Therefore, any object can use the hasOwnProperty method.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Randy Rivera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fermi-Pasta-Ulam-Tsingou problem: A foray into the beautifully simple]]></title>
        <id>https://3quarksdaily.com/3quarksdaily/2020/01/the-fermi-pasta-ulam-tsingou-problem-a-foray-into-the-beautifully-simple-and-the-simply-beautiful.html</id>
        <link href="https://3quarksdaily.com/3quarksdaily/2020/01/the-fermi-pasta-ulam-tsingou-problem-a-foray-into-the-beautifully-simple-and-the-simply-beautiful.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T21:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraftful (YC S19) hiring a founding engineer to build an IoT platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kraftful.com/blog/engineering-roles</id>
        <link href="https://www.kraftful.com/blog/engineering-roles"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T21:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting a React/Next.js Single Page Application Optimized for SEO]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/colbyfayock/crafting-a-react-next-js-single-page-application-optimized-for-seo-54fk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/colbyfayock/crafting-a-react-next-js-single-page-application-optimized-for-seo-54fk"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T20:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a rush? Skip to tutorial steps.
What's the first thing you do when you are looking for something?
If you're like me, you probably pull out your phone and search for it on Google. It makes optimizing websites for search engines more important than ever. And as a developer, I get it, SEO is a critical part of any business’ online presence. It's my job to be sure our tools can support that effort of being easily visible on search engine results pages. 
And since React is the most popular JavaScript framework, these tools will most likely be related to it or React frameworks like Next.js.
But, how can we be sure our React dynamic applications are SEO-friendly for our favorites robot crawlers to understand?
That's when the real work comes in. Stop googling: "SEO with react" 'cause you're are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colby Fayock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript "plain" Object]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/romeopeter/javascript-plain-object-52eh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/romeopeter/javascript-plain-object-52eh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T20:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NOTE:
The term "object" denotes two kinds of objects: the key-value data structure in JavaScript, and the popular but opinionated programming methodology: OOP . This article is about the latter type of object.
In JavaScript, [almost] everything is an object. To understand the language in-depth, you first have to know what objects are and how they work.
An object is used to store key-value data. It allows for various data and complex entities to be stored. Entities within an object are known as properties. A property is a "key-value" pair, where the key is the property name and value can be anything
To create an object, the curly braces {...} is used with a list of optional properties. It's possible to initialize an empty object.
// Empty object using "object literal" syntax
let user = {};
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Romeo Agbor Peter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using aligned word vectors for instant translations with Python and Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://instantdomainsearch.com/engineering/how-to-use-fasttext-for-instant-translations</id>
        <link href="https://instantdomainsearch.com/engineering/how-to-use-fasttext-for-instant-translations"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T20:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Github actions tweaks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/achimoraites/github-actions-tweaks-23pa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/achimoraites/github-actions-tweaks-23pa"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T19:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here there are some cool tricks you can do to improve your Github Actions.
How many times you have re-installed all of your packages in your actions even when no packages were changed?
Github actions are charged based on the time they actually run;
have a look here in case you are interested 😉
To cache our modules we will use the actions/cache@v2 action
Here is an example of caching npm dependencies for Linux/MacOS
- name: Cache node_modules 📦
  uses: actions/cache@v2
  with:
    path: ~/.npm
    key: ${{ runner.os }}-node-${{ hashFiles('**/package-lock.json') }}
    restore-keys: |
      ${{ runner.os }}-node-

Here you can see it in a Github Action used for deploying my svelte-kit powered blog to gh-pages 🚀
There are times where you need to be able to create a string based on env vari…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Achilles Moraites</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Pi WiFi to ethernet bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://willhaley.com/blog/raspberry-pi-wifi-ethernet-bridge/</id>
        <link href="https://willhaley.com/blog/raspberry-pi-wifi-ethernet-bridge/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T19:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Argo to Train Predictive Models at FlightAware]]></title>
        <id>https://flightaware.engineering/using-argo-to-train-predictive-models/</id>
        <link href="https://flightaware.engineering/using-argo-to-train-predictive-models/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T19:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy Analysis of FLoC]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/en/mozilla/privacy-analysis-of-floc/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/mozilla/privacy-analysis-of-floc/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T18:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heart inflammation cases in young men higher than expected after mRNA vaccines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/cdc-heart-inflammation-cases-ages-16-24-higher-than-expected-after-mrna-covid-19-2021-06-10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us/cdc-heart-inflammation-cases-ages-16-24-higher-than-expected-after-mrna-covid-19-2021-06-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T18:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good and Bad Elixir]]></title>
        <id>https://keathley.io/blog/good-and-bad-elixir.html</id>
        <link href="https://keathley.io/blog/good-and-bad-elixir.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T18:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software is eating the car]]></title>
        <id>https://spectrum.ieee.org/cars-that-think/transportation/advanced-cars/software-eating-car</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/cars-that-think/transportation/advanced-cars/software-eating-car"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T16:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Link shorteners: the long and short of why you shouldn’t use them]]></title>
        <id>https://gcs.civilservice.gov.uk/blog/link-shorteners-the-long-and-short-of-why-you-shouldnt-use-them/</id>
        <link href="https://gcs.civilservice.gov.uk/blog/link-shorteners-the-long-and-short-of-why-you-shouldnt-use-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T16:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A robot to replace the need for farmers to go inside the grain bin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.agweb.com/news/business/technology/robot-replace-need-farmers-go-inside-grain-bin</id>
        <link href="https://www.agweb.com/news/business/technology/robot-replace-need-farmers-go-inside-grain-bin"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My startup journey]]></title>
        <id>https://johnjianwang.medium.com/my-startup-journey-dcf86a38676d</id>
        <link href="https://johnjianwang.medium.com/my-startup-journey-dcf86a38676d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The work-from-home future is destroying bosses' brains]]></title>
        <id>https://ez.substack.com/p/the-work-from-home-future-is-destroying</id>
        <link href="https://ez.substack.com/p/the-work-from-home-future-is-destroying"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Okay (YC W20) – Analytics for engineering teams]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27461564</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27461564"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equal Columns With Flexbox: It’s More Complicated Than You Might Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341894</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/equal-columns-with-flexbox-its-more-complicated-than-you-might-think/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As awesome as flexbox is, what it’s doing under the hood is actually a little strange because, by default, it is doing two things at once. It first looks at the content size which is what we would get if by declaring width: max-content on an element. But on top of that, flex-shrink is also doing some work allowing the items to be smaller, but only if needed.
Let’s break those two down and see how they work together.
The post Equal Columns With Flexbox: It’s More Complicated Than You Might Think appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Powell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Headless CMS with Fauna and Vercel Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342182</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-headless-cms-with-fauna-and-vercel-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will learn and use headless CMS, Fauna, and Vercel functions to build a blogging platform, Blogify After that, you can easily build any web application using a headless CMS, Fauna and Vercel functions.
The post Building a Headless CMS with Fauna and Vercel Functions appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikeh Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Try APL]]></title>
        <id>https://tryapl.org</id>
        <link href="https://tryapl.org"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rqlite 6.0: the evolution of a distributed database design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.philipotoole.com/rqlite-6-0-0-building-for-the-future/</id>
        <link href="https://www.philipotoole.com/rqlite-6-0-0-building-for-the-future/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T12:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe Tax]]></title>
        <id>https://stripe.com/tax</id>
        <link href="https://stripe.com/tax"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T12:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Logo Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6390</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/no-logo-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=no-logo-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T12:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: No Logo uses four parts, including “No Space,” “No Choice,” “No Jobs,” and “No Logo,” to explain the growth of brand power since the 1980s, how the focus of companies on image rather than products has affected employees, and to identify those who fight against large corporations and their brands. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post No Logo Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Data Fundamentals Certification (DP-900) – Pass the Exam With This Free 4.5-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>60b93afaacb62507dd1d8915</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-data-fundamentals-certification-dp-900-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-4-5-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can learn everything you need to know to earn the Azure Data Fundamentals certification by completing this free 4.5 hour course. What is the Azure Data Fundamentals Certification?The Azure Data Fundamentals Certification is for those seeking a data-related role such as Data Analyst, Data Engineer, or Data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers can't fix bad management (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://iism.org/article/developers-can-t-fix-bad-management-57</id>
        <link href="https://iism.org/article/developers-can-t-fix-bad-management-57"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T09:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did I break you? Reverse dependency verification]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.soundcloud.com/blog/did-i-break-you</id>
        <link href="https://developers.soundcloud.com/blog/did-i-break-you"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T06:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All at Sea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.historytoday.com/reviews/all-sea</id>
        <link href="https://www.historytoday.com/reviews/all-sea"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T00:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Amateur Photographers of Midcentury São Paulo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theparisreview.org/blog/2021/05/21/the-amateur-photographers-of-midcentury-sao-paulo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.theparisreview.org/blog/2021/05/21/the-amateur-photographers-of-midcentury-sao-paulo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T00:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Prison Cell of Ludger Sylbaris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.atlasobscura.com/places/the-prison-cell-of-ludger-sylbaris-saint-pierre-martinique</id>
        <link href="https://www.atlasobscura.com/places/the-prison-cell-of-ludger-sylbaris-saint-pierre-martinique"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T22:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From the Slums of Mumbai to a Rented Apartment – My 30-Year Developer Journey]]></title>
        <id>60b357ad11ffb70827ef9a90</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/my-journey-into-tech-from-slums-of-mumbai-to-my-own-apartment/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T21:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I tweeted about how I was moving from a Slum where I lived for 29 years to a multi-story rented apartment.  The tech community on Twitter responded with nothing but love. Dan Wahlin posted that he would love to hear more about my story. It's not going to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Cornucopia of Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340967</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-cornucopia-of-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T20:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t know about y’all, but my feeds have been flooded with articles about CSS Container Queries these past few weeks. The buzz about container queries actually started back in December after Miriam Suzanne posted a proposal (picking up on …
The post A Cornucopia of Container Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Skills You Need to Start Freelancing as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>60c0ccbed3126007592d5781</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-skills-you-need-to-start-freelancing/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T19:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's the bottom line: you don't need much to get started as a freelance developer.  The biggest obstacle developers face when they're thinking about getting started is that they tend to overcomplicate things.  Most are intimidated by the sheer number of different paths or skills deemed necessary by various blog]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Bootstrap 5 and SASS by Building a Portfolio Website]]></title>
        <id>60c10a1dd3126007592d5988</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bootstrap-5-and-sass-by-building-a-portfolio-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T18:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bootstrap is one of the most popular CSS frameworks and Sass is one of the most popular preprocessors for CSS. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about Bootstrap 5 and Sass by building a portfolio website. Patrick Muriungi developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[target=blank]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341916</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/targetblank/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T14:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does that make your eye twitch a little bit? Like… it’s a typo. It should be target="_blank" with an underscore to start the value. As in…
<a target="_blank" href="https://codepen.io"Open CodePen in a New Tab
</a
Welp, that’s correct syntax!…
The post target=blank appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Apple Mail threaten the newsletter boom?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.platformer.news/p/will-apple-mail-end-the-newsletter</id>
        <link href="https://www.platformer.news/p/will-apple-mail-end-the-newsletter"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T14:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Myth Of The Strong Leader Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6389</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-myth-of-the-strong-leader-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-myth-of-the-strong-leader-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T12:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Myth Of The Strong Leader reveals why being a bold, charismatic leader might not be all it’s cracked up to be even though people tend to think of good leaders in this light and explains how these individuals rise to power and some of the consequences of it happening on an international scale. […]
The post The Myth Of The Strong Leader Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your freeCodeCamp Project on AWS – A Beginner&#x27;s Guide to the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>60bfa4d4d3126007592d5160</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-your-freecodecamp-project-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T23:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout this post we’ll deploy your freeCodeCamp front end project using various services on AWS like S3, ElasticBeanstalk, and Lambda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Electronics With Arduino - Full Course]]></title>
        <id>60bfd986d3126007592d53a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-your-own-electronics-with-arduino-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T21:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino is an open-source electronics platform based on easy-to-use hardware and software. Arduino boards are able to read inputs - light on a sensor, a finger on a button, or a Twitter message - and turn it into an output - activating a motor, turning on an LED, publishing something]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking at WCAG 2.5.5 for Better Target Sizes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341982</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/looking-at-wcag-2-5-5-for-better-target-sizes/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T18:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever experienced the frustration of trying to tap a button on a mobile device only to have it do nothing because the target size is just not large enough **and it’s not picking up on your press? Maybe …
The post Looking at WCAG 2.5.5 for Better Target Sizes appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Libby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pass Data and Events Between Components in React]]></title>
        <id>60b23b8911ffb70827ef954e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pass-data-between-components-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T16:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're trying to implement CRUD operations using API endpoints, you might find that it's hard to manage data across multiple components. Or maybe you have a modal, but you want to trigger it from a different component.  Wrapping your head around how to tackle these scenarios can be difficult.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complete CSS Grid Tutorial with Cheat Sheet 🎖️]]></title>
        <id>60be6a3cd3126007592d4a03</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-grid-tutorial-with-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T16:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're going to learn CSS Grid properties so that you can make your own responsive websites. I'll explain how each of Grid's properties work along with a CheatSheet that covers everything you can do with Grid. Let's go. 🎖️ Table of Contents: CSS Grid Architecture CSS Grid Chart Grid Parent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Trickz: An Experiment with Netlify’s On-Demand Builders]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341884</id>
        <link href="https://alex.party/posts/2021-05-31-css-trickz-an-experiment-with-netlify-s-on-demand-builders/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T14:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress sites have an API by default. Wanna see this site’s most recent posts, with just a specific set of data… in JSON format? Here ya go. Alex Riviere made a joke site using that.
At first, the site …
The post CSS-Trickz: An Experiment with Netlify’s On-Demand Builders appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Until Yesterday Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6381</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-world-until-yesterday-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-world-until-yesterday-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The World Until Yesterday identifies some of the most valuable lessons we can learn from societies of the past like hunter-gatherers, including how to resolve conflicts better, more effective ways to raise children, how to stay healthier for longer, and much more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Around 11,000 years […]
The post The World Until Yesterday Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Development with Next.js and Supabase – The Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>60bbd28eacb62507dd1d99fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-complete-guide-to-full-stack-development-with-supabas/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T23:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build full stack serverless apps with Supabase and Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use OpenCV and Python for Computer Vision and AI]]></title>
        <id>60be863cd3126007592d4c36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opencv-and-python-for-computer-vision-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T20:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCV is a popular Python library for real-time computer vision. We just released a new OpenCV course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course comes directly from the creators of OpenCV and is the perfect course for beginners.  You will learn how to use OpenCV for Computer Vision and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341805</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T19:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Show/Hide password accessibility and password hints tutorial — Nicolas Steenhout goes deep on <input type="password"> accessibility. For one thing, being able to toggle it to type="text" should be possible, while announcing, politely, the change. But also, put the password hints 
…
The post Links on Accessibility appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code Extensions for HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340390</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/vs-code-extensions-for-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T14:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s look at some extensions for VS Code that make writing and editing HTML (and languages that are basically HTML with extra powers) better. You may not like all of them. Maybe some of them don’t appeal to you, solve …
The post VS Code Extensions for HTML appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Arguments For Deleting Your Social Media Accounts Right Now Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6380</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/ten-arguments-for-deleting-your-social-media-accounts-right-now-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ten-arguments-for-deleting-your-social-media-accounts-right-now-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T12:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Ten Arguments For Deleting Your Social Media Accounts Right Now shows why you should quit social media because it stops joy, makes you a jerk, erodes truth, kills empathy, takes free will, keeps the world insane, destroys authenticity, blocks economic dignity, makes politics a mess, and hates you. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post Ten Arguments For Deleting Your Social Media Accounts Right Now Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Principles for user-centered front-end development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341793</id>
        <link href="https://colinoakley.medium.com/the-web-we-choose-to-build-e921510e3f1b"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T20:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colin Oakley:
• Accessible — Use semantic HTML, and make sure we meet the WCAG 2.1 AA standard as a minimum and it works with assisted technologies (this sits alongside the DWP Accessibility Manual)
• Agnostic — Build 
…
The post Principles for user-centered front-end development appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I :has()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341968</id>
        <link href="https://bkardell.com/blog/canihas.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T14:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just joked that we’re basically getting everything we want in CSS super fast (mostly referring to container queries, my gosh, can you imagine they are actually coming?). Now we might actually get parent selectors?! As in .parent:has(.child) { …
The post Can I :has() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greenlights Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6379</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/greenlights-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=greenlights-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Greenlights is the fascinating autobiography of Matthew McConaughey in which he takes us on a wild ride of his journey through a childhood of tough love, rising to fame and success in Hollywood, shifting his career, and more, guided by the green lights he saw that led him forward at each step. Read in: […]
The post Greenlights Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19312</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/03/computing-the-number-of-digits-of-an-integer-even-faster/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I my previous blog post, I documented how one might proceed to compute the number of digits of an integer quickly. E.g., given the integer 999, you want 3 but given the integer 1000, you want 4. It is effectively the integer logarithm in base 10. On computers, you can quickly compute the integer logarithm … Continue reading Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexagons and Beyond: Flexible, Responsive Grid Patterns, Sans Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341584</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/hexagons-and-beyond-flexible-responsive-grid-patterns-sans-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little while back, Chris shared this nice hexagonal grid. And true to its name, it’s using —wait for it — CSS Grid to form that layout. It’s a neat trick! Combining grid columns, grid gaps, and creative clipping …
The post Hexagons and Beyond: Flexible, Responsive Grid Patterns, Sans Media Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Lighthouse Scores and Core Web Vitals with DebugBear]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341494</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/monitoring-lighthouse-scores-and-core-web-vitals-with-debugbear/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DebugBear takes just a few seconds to start using. You literally point it at a URL you want to watch, and it’ll start watching it. You install nothing.
It’ll start running tests, and you’ve immediately got performance charts you can …
The post Monitoring Lighthouse Scores and Core Web Vitals with DebugBear appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Rules Rules Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6372</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/no-rules-rules-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=no-rules-rules-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T12:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: No Rules Rules explains the incredibly unique and efficient company culture of Netflix, including the amazing levels of freedom and responsibility it gives employees and how this innovative way of running the business is the very reason that Netflix is so successful. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: When Netflix started […]
The post No Rules Rules Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging iOS Safari]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341724</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/debugging-ios-safari/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do I debug Safari on iOS?
These are my general steps, starting with not even using iOS Safari.
1. Is this just a small-screen problem?
Lemme just use the device mode in Chrome quick.
Note that this does a …
The post Debugging iOS Safari appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Crash Course in WordPress Block Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341442</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-crash-course-in-wordpress-block-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blocks in WordPress are great. Drop some into the page, arrange them how you like, and you’ve got a pretty sweet landing page with little effort. But what if the default blocks in WordPress need a little tweaking? Like, what …
The post A Crash Course in WordPress Block Filters appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Mayorov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Standard Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6370</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-bitcoin-standard-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-bitcoin-standard-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Bitcoin Standard uses the history of money and gold to explain why Bitcoin is the way to go if the world wants to stick to having sound money and why it’s the only cryptocurrency to be focusing on right now. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Have you ever thought […]
The post The Bitcoin Standard Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Design Of Everyday Things Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6244</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-design-of-everyday-things-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-design-of-everyday-things-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Design Of Everyday Things helps you understand why your inability to use some products isn’t your fault but instead is the result of bad design and how companies can use the principles of cognitive psychology to implement better design principles that actually solve your problems without creating more of them. Read in: 4 […]
The post The Design Of Everyday Things Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Drama Of The Gifted Child Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6243</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-drama-of-the-gifted-child-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-drama-of-the-gifted-child-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T12:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Drama Of The Gifted Child is an international bestseller that will help you unearth your sad, suppressed memories from childhood that still haunt you today and teach you how to confront them so you can avoid passing them on to your children, release yourself from the pains of your past, and finally be […]
The post The Drama Of The Gifted Child Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing the number of digits of an integer quickly]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19288</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/28/computing-the-number-of-digits-of-an-integer-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T19:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose I give you an integer. How many decimal digits would you need to write it out? The number ‘100’ takes 3 digits whereas the number ’99’ requires only two. You are effectively trying to compute the integer logarithm in base 10 of the number. I say ‘integer logarithm’ because you need to round up … Continue reading Computing the number of digits of an integer quickly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Hundred Souls Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6242</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/four-hundred-souls-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=four-hundred-souls-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Four Hundred Souls tells the history of African Americans from the perspective of 90 authors who share insights on 400 years of conflict, oppression, and faith that with all the hard work of those fighting for equality, things would get better someday. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Most American students can […]
The post Four Hundred Souls Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Powerful Responsive Websites With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19274</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/26/all-models-are-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T19:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong, but some are useful is a common saying in statistics. It does not merely apply to statistics, however. It is general observation. Box (1976) wrote an  influential article on the topic. He says that you make progress by successively making models followed by experiments, followed by more models, and then more … Continue reading All models are wrong]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 22nd 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19268</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/22/science-and-technology-links-may-22nd-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T15:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most computer chips today in flagship phones and computers use a process based on a 5 nm or larger resolution. Finer resolutions usually translate into lower energy usage and lower heat production. Given that many of our systems are limited by heat or power, finer resolutions lead to higher performance. The large Taiwanese chip maker … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 22nd 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Counting the number of matching characters in two ASCII strings]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19258</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/21/counting-the-number-of-matching-characters-in-two-ascii-strings/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose that you give me two ASCII strings having the same number of characters. I wish to compute efficiently the number of matching characters (same position, same character). E.g., the strings ‘012c’ and ‘021c’ have two matching characters (‘0’ and ‘c’). The conventional approach in C would look as follow: uint64_t standard_matching_bytes(char * c1, char … Continue reading Counting the number of matching characters in two ASCII strings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Converting binary integers to ASCII characters: Apple M1 vs AMD Zen2]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19250</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/17/converting-binary-integers-to-ascii-characters-apple-m1-vs-amd-zen2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Programmers often need to write integers as characters. Thus given the 32-bit value 1234, you might need a function that writes the characters 1234. We can use the fact that the ASCII numeral characters are in sequence in the ASCII table: ‘0’+0 is ‘0’, ‘0’+1 is ‘1’ and so forth. With this optimization in mind, … Continue reading Converting binary integers to ASCII characters: Apple M1 vs AMD Zen2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 15th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19244</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/15/science-and-technology-links-may-15th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were rainforests near the south pole 90 million years ago. Though commercial exchanges are typically win-win for both the buyer and the seller, people tend to view the buyer as more likely to be taken advantage of. People with low self-esteem are more likely to blame the political system for their personal problems. Moscona … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 15th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>