<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-08-01T01:06:32.427Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-08-01T01:06:32.427Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey Epstein Got Away with It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/13/books/review/perversion-of-justice-julie-k-brown.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/13/books/review/perversion-of-justice-julie-k-brown.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-01T00:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tsParticles 1.33.2 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/matteobruni/tsparticles-1-33-2-6c2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/matteobruni/tsparticles-1-33-2-6c2"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T23:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tsParticles 1.33.2 Changelog



  
  
  New Features



Added spin movement options
Bubble color can now be mixed with the original one to have a smoother effect
Added resize observer, this will replace window.resize if available
Fixed images shape options
Fixed broken movement after 1.31
Fixed frozen frames (more than 1 second), this will fix the issue with pause on blur
Fixed svelte component
Improved Absorbers
Improved Orbits
 / 
        tsparticles
      
    

A lightweight TypeScript library for creating particles. Dependency free (*), browser ready and compatible with React, Vue, Angular, Svelte, jQuery, Preact, Inferno
         
This library is available on the two most popular CDNs and it's easy and ready to use, if you were using particles.js it's even easier.
You'll find the instructions below, with all the links you need, and don't be scared by TypeScript, it's just the source language.
The output files are just JavaScript. 🤩
CDNs and npm have all the sources you need in Javascript, a bundle browser ready (tsparticles.min.js) and all files splitted for import syntax.
If you are still interested some lines below there are some instructions for migrating from the old particles.js library.
Library installation


Hosting / CDN

Please use this hosts or your own to…
View on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matteo Bruni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Your Complete Guide To All Python List Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/this-is-your-complete-guide-to-all-python-list-methods-b4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/this-is-your-complete-guide-to-all-python-list-methods-b4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T23:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm Aya Bouchiha, today, I'm going to talk about the list of built-in objects.
A list is a mutable, iterable,  ordered collection of values. It is used to store different and multiple values in one variable.
new_list = ['hi', 1, False, {"name":"Aya"}, [10, 20], None]

print(new_list) # ['hi', 1, False, {"name":"Aya"}, [10, 20], None]
print(type(new_list)) # <class 'list'>
print(len(new_list)) # 6

append(value): this list method lets you insert an element at the end of the list.
my_list = [10, 20, 30]

my_list.append(40)

print(my_list.append(50)) # None

print(my_list) # [10, 20, 30, 40, 50]

my_list.append() # error

insert(index, value): used to add a new element at a given index
admins = ['Aya Bouchiha', 'John Doe']

admins.insert(0, 'Simon Bihao') 
print(admins)  # ['Simon Bihao',…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Bouchiha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard's reputation collapsed in just three years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pcgamer.com/how-blizzards-reputation-collapsed-in-just-3-years/</id>
        <link href="https://www.pcgamer.com/how-blizzards-reputation-collapsed-in-just-3-years/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T22:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six corporations control 90% of America media]]></title>
        <id>https://techstartups.com/2020/09/18/6-corporations-control-90-media-america-illusion-choice-objectivity-2020/</id>
        <link href="https://techstartups.com/2020/09/18/6-corporations-control-90-media-america-illusion-choice-objectivity-2020/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T22:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compose.ai (YC W21) Is Hiring a Senior Front End Engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/compose-ai/jobs/syPzbAB-senior-frontend-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/compose-ai/jobs/syPzbAB-senior-frontend-engineer"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cy384/ssheven: A modern SSH client for Mac OS 7/8/9]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/cy384/ssheven</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/cy384/ssheven"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T20:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using array map, filter and reduce in MongoDB aggregation pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cassiolacerda/using-array-map-filter-and-reduce-in-mongodb-aggregation-pipeline-1lp2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cassiolacerda/using-array-map-filter-and-reduce-in-mongodb-aggregation-pipeline-1lp2"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T20:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work with javascript, the chances of you are using array methods like map, filter and reducer today are really great. 
All simplicity offered by javascript higher-order functions makes our code more readable and concise, mainly when we work with array data transformations.
Let's remember these methods:
const numbers = [2, 8, 15];

const greaterThanFive = (num) => num > 5;
const multiplyBy2 = (num) => num * 2;
const sum = (acc, num) => acc + num;

const filtered = numbers.filter(greaterThanFive);
const mapped = numbers.map(multiplyBy2);
const reduced = numbers.reduce(sum);

console.log(filtered); // [8, 15]
console.log(mapped); // [4, 16, 30]
console.log(reduced); // 25

That's really amazing! 
However, in databases scenario, querying data with this simplicity is usually unusual, unl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cássio Lacerda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comma Three Devkit]]></title>
        <id>https://comma.ai/shop/products/three</id>
        <link href="https://comma.ai/shop/products/three"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T20:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make your React App a Progressive Web App (PWA)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arndom/how-to-make-your-react-app-a-progressive-web-app-pwa-3d05</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arndom/how-to-make-your-react-app-a-progressive-web-app-pwa-3d05"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T20:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro 💨


PWAs are great for your apps because;
Short loading times and overall better performance in poor network conditions for your users.


No need for extra development time to make product a native app(iOS and Android).


Have native features like push notifications without the hassle of  development.


Overall better user engagement



So it's a pretty handy thing to have in any react app.  
Note:


If your are just starting your project the best thing would be to run the create-react-app command with the pwa template:
npx create-react-app my-app --template cra-template-pwa

It would save you the time. If you have already progressed into your project follow along ⏬⏬⏬
Saving it as worker.js  in our public folder: public/worker.js . 
var CACHE_NAME = "app name"

var urlsToCache = [
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nabil Alamin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Let The Lies Of Imposter Syndrome Get To You]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madebyayan/don-t-let-the-lies-of-imposter-syndrome-get-to-you-749</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madebyayan/don-t-let-the-lies-of-imposter-syndrome-get-to-you-749"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T20:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a developer and coder for years, I recently realized that it's okay to use no code solutions for things I'm not as familiar with
It's NOT cheating if you use templates or easier solutions, it's just being productive
In fact it opens up a whole new area of possibilities that you never knew existed.
You'll be able to build quicker and be more productive as you'll be able to finish projects faster. And at the end of the development journey, the thing that you'll have would be the thing that YOU built
So, don't let the lies of imposter syndrome get to you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayan S</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lang Jam: create a programming language in a weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/langjam/langjam</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/langjam/langjam"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T20:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19419</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/31/science-and-technology-links-july-31st-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T19:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers built a microscope that might be 10 times better than the best available microscopes. Subsidizing college education can lower earnings due to lower job experience: The Post 9/11 GI Bill (PGIB) is among the largest and most generous college subsidies enacted thus far in the U.S. (…) the introduction of the PGIB raised college … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 31st 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Txiki.js: Tiny JavaScript runtime built with QuickJS and libuv]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/saghul/txiki.js</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/saghul/txiki.js"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T19:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Bezos loses attempt to block the Moon-landing contract NASA gave to SpaceX]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2021/07/jeff-bezos-loses-attempt-to-block-the-moon-landing-contract-nasa-gave-to-spacex/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2021/07/jeff-bezos-loses-attempt-to-block-the-moon-landing-contract-nasa-gave-to-spacex/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T19:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning the performance of the DeepRacer model]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/fine-tuning-the-performance-of-the-model-4pjo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/fine-tuning-the-performance-of-the-model-4pjo"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T19:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of the AWS DeepRacer Blog series, we saw how to create your AWS DeepRacer Model. How cool is to watch your AWS DeepRacer car navigating autonomously every corner and turn in the circuit with your Reinforcement Learning model guiding it? Now its time to fine-tune the model so that we will try to clock the best time.
We will try to dive deeper into this tutorial and discuss more on the Action Space, Reward Function and Hyper-parameter tuning. I have explained of creating and fine-tuning the model using two algorithms and action spaces. You can choose either one and ignore the rest.
We can train models using either of two RL Algorithms
Proximal Policy Optimization (PPO)
Soft Actor Critic (SAC)
The main differences between the two algorithms are



PPO
SAC




Works in both d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek0712</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Download a CSV of your Amazon purchases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.amazon.com/gp/b2b/reports</id>
        <link href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/b2b/reports"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T18:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having the rick power!!! Pt.3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/blitty/having-the-rick-power-pt-3-2f0k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/blitty/having-the-rick-power-pt-3-2f0k"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T18:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello again!!! 🙌
Here I am, I've just open vscode, and the first thing I did was styling the container of the cards, now is amazing how it is!! (Maybe you don't like it, but I DO :)
A bit of react-router
Starting with Apollo


A little explanation
Returning to the project



Then I did 'the change', I converted App.jsx into a Switch for Routes, using react-router-dom, which I have neves used, but is super simple!!
(Mini tutorial)
React Router, the first thing we have to do is install it :) of course... docs
npm install react-router-dom
Now that we have it installed, the first thing we have to do, is to say to React that we are using it!!! So we tell index.js (the one that is god, because it controls everything) to have something called BrowserRouter, which is like a Route but a bit specia…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blitty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add Social Login in Laravel With Socialite]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sureshramani/add-social-login-in-laravel-with-socialite-3gad</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sureshramani/add-social-login-in-laravel-with-socialite-3gad"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T18:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social login is now an essential part of any site which performs user authentication. It saves the users a lot of time, as they won't need to fill the whole form. They just sign up with their social account and next time they can log into the website with a single click.
Using social media accounts to sign up for websites is common nowadays and preferred by users because they don't have to remember a password every time they log in to a website. Even though social signup is easy, you can also inadvertently end up with a bunch of very confused users in an app.
Login with social accounts is a straightforward process and simultaneously enhances the user experience; nowadays, everybody knows a better user experience is the key to any digital product's success.
Laravel Socialite  is a package developed to abstract away any social authentication complexities and boilerplate code into a fluent and expressive interface.
Socialite only supports Google, Facebook, Twitter, Linked In, Github, and Bitbucket as OAuth providers. They won't be adding any others to the list, however, there's a community-driven collection called  Socialite Providers , which contains plenty of unofficial providers for Socialite.
In this tutorial, we are going to add Social Authentication to a Laravel app through  Socialite , an official Laravel package that makes adding social authentication to a Laravel app.
If you want to manage your VPS / VM Server without touching command line go and Checkout this link. ServerAvatar allows you to quickly set up WordPress or Custom PHP websites on VPS / VM in  matter of minutes.  You can host multiple websites on a single VPS / VM, configure SSL certificates, and monitor the health of your server  without ever touching the command line interface .
Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suresh Ramani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disable Page Pulling]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jfullerco/disable-page-pulling-2m4b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jfullerco/disable-page-pulling-2m4b"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T18:18:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In case anyone else finds the ability to "pull" your page down or right exposing whitespace that is not actually there...
https://developers.google.com/web/updates/2017/11/overscroll-behavior
Hope this helps someone else from having to search around for a solution!
* {
   overscroll-behavior: none;
}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jfullerco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PCI Devices in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gaurav24072002/pci-devices-in-linux-36fi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gaurav24072002/pci-devices-in-linux-36fi"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T18:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are PCI Devices ?


A PCI device is any piece of computer hardware that plugs directly into a PCI slot on a computer's motherboard. PCI, which stands for Peripheral Component Interconnect, was introduced to personal computers by the Intel Corporation in 1993. The technology to operate PCI is integrated into the motherboard of nearly every personal computer manufactured since 1995. A PCI connection on a motherboard can be identified as a long strip of raised copper connectors encased in plastic. This long strip of connectors is usually called a bus.
The PCI bus is not as fast as the system bus. Its primary purpose is to facilitate communication of hardware devices of all types such as audio, video, network or graphics with the microprocessor.
The lspci command is used to display detail…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Maheshwari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Behind The Scenes: Scope & The Scope Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bhattpawan/javascript-behind-the-scenes-scope-the-scope-chain-4de7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bhattpawan/javascript-behind-the-scenes-scope-the-scope-chain-4de7"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T17:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey fellow developers, so now that we are well verse with The Execution Context and Call Stack, its now time to dive a little deeper into JavaScript and understand what The Scope and Scope Chain is.
Scope is an environment in which a variable is accessible. It determines the visibility of a variable. We cannot access a variable outside its scope. JavaScript follows Lexical Scoping , which determines the scope of a variable by how the functions and blocks are placed in our code. Following are the different types of scopes in JavaScript:
1. Global Scope: Variables defined in global scope are defined outside any function or block. These variables can be accessed anywhere throughout the code.
2. Function Scope: Variables which are defined inside a function, have their visibility limited to ins…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pawan Bhatt 👨‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made 50+ COLOR PALETTES for you to use in your next projects and designs 🎨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/underscorecode/i-made-50-color-palettes-for-you-to-use-in-your-next-projects-and-designs-33f7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/underscorecode/i-made-50-color-palettes-for-you-to-use-in-your-next-projects-and-designs-33f7"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T17:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, everybody! 👋
Today, I bring you 50+ color palettes to use in your upcoming projects or to just get some inspiration out of them.
I've given every palette a name to make it easier to identify them (I've tried my best, promise 😅).
Let me know if you like this kind of content and if you'd like to see more articles like this in the future (about colors, gradients, fonts, design resources, etc). I'd be glad to hear from you in comments! 
And now, let's have a look at those color schemes 👇
Sunset in Arizona


Pink Fall Vibes


Desert Adventures


Chic Garden


Neon Lights


Pastel Cake


Acid Tangerine


Frozen Winter


Vibing Summer


Drops of Summer








  
  
  Package 2



 Pink Mandarin


Nomadic Dreams


Circus Acrobat


Coffee By The Sea


Strawberry Nights


Dans La Fôret


Easter Vibes


Salty Waters


Fresh Berries


Skeptical Minds








  
  
  Package 3



Dry Landscape


Dark Sunset


Antartic Sun


Velvet Fall


Water Park


Origami


Nights In The City


Vintage Vineyards


Fun & Games


Aquamarina








  
  
  Package 4



Cold Pastels


Sober Twilight


Sandy Cocoa


Tokyo Streets


Tireless Traveler 


Candy Dreams


Roses & Wood


Downtown LA


Pumpkin Spice Latte


Honey Hearts








  
  
  Package 5



Orange Muffin


Self-love


Trip to Paris


Perfect Getaway


Eclipse Solstice


Muddy Feelings


Watermelon Party


Golden Hour


Sun, Sand & Tan


Soft Skies








  
  
  Bonus



Vibrant Neon


Sweet Surrender


90s Child


Pomegranate Paradise


Brown Eyed Soul







And this is all for today! 
I hope you liked the article and see you all in the next 👋

🎉 Don't forget to follow @underscorecode
 on Instagram and Twitter for more daily webdev content 🖥🖤]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>_CODE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One-Thousand Year-Old Plants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/31/science/plant-leaves-welwitschia.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/31/science/plant-leaves-welwitschia.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T17:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Retrocomputing Archive]]></title>
        <id>http://www.retroarchive.org/</id>
        <link href="http://www.retroarchive.org/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T16:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As lockdowns lift, media firms brace for an “attention recession”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.economist.com/international/2021/07/01/as-lockdowns-lift-media-firms-brace-for-an-attention-recession</id>
        <link href="https://www.economist.com/international/2021/07/01/as-lockdowns-lift-media-firms-brace-for-an-attention-recession"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T15:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Past Performance is Not Indicative of Future Results (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://locusmag.com/2020/11/cory-doctorow-past-performance-is-not-indicative-of-future-results/</id>
        <link href="https://locusmag.com/2020/11/cory-doctorow-past-performance-is-not-indicative-of-future-results/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T15:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typos, tricks and misprints]]></title>
        <id>https://aeon.co/essays/why-is-the-english-spelling-system-so-weird-and-inconsistent</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/why-is-the-english-spelling-system-so-weird-and-inconsistent"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T14:14:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The recycling myth: A plastic waste solution littered with failure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/environment-plastic-oil-recycling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/environment-plastic-oil-recycling/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T13:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where has all the productivity gone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.johndcook.com/blog/2021/07/31/where-has-productivity-gone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.johndcook.com/blog/2021/07/31/where-has-productivity-gone/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T13:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I, Token: The untold story of the hole in Bitcoin's heart]]></title>
        <id>https://brettscott.substack.com/p/the-hole-in-bitcoins-heart</id>
        <link href="https://brettscott.substack.com/p/the-hole-in-bitcoins-heart"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T12:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TheBoard: Collaborative Whiteboard powered by matrix protocol and infrastucture]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/toger5/TheBoard</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/toger5/TheBoard"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T11:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Do you have a process or a framework to learn specific skills quickly?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28017289</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=28017289"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T11:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster CRDTs: An Adventure in Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://josephg.com/blog/crdts-go-brrr/</id>
        <link href="https://josephg.com/blog/crdts-go-brrr/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T11:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Micro HTTP server in 22 lines of C]]></title>
        <id>https://twitter.com/ilyakurdyukov/status/1421349901720510465</id>
        <link href="https://twitter.com/ilyakurdyukov/status/1421349901720510465"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T11:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[London’s Crossrail Is a $21B Test of Virtual Modeling (2016)]]></title>
        <id>https://spectrum.ieee.org/londons-crossrail-is-a-21-billion-test-of-virtual-modeling</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/londons-crossrail-is-a-21-billion-test-of-virtual-modeling"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T07:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes In August (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2021. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air – Live reload when developing with Go]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/cosmtrek/air</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/cosmtrek/air"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T06:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How hard is it to get counting right?]]></title>
        <id>https://desystemize.substack.com/p/desystemize-1</id>
        <link href="https://desystemize.substack.com/p/desystemize-1"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T05:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restaurant prices in the 19th and 20th centuries (2009)]]></title>
        <id>https://restaurant-ingthroughhistory.com/restaurant-prices/</id>
        <link href="https://restaurant-ingthroughhistory.com/restaurant-prices/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T02:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithmic Complexity of Left-Pad (2016)]]></title>
        <id>https://accidentallyquadratic.tumblr.com/post/142387131042/nodejs-left-pad</id>
        <link href="https://accidentallyquadratic.tumblr.com/post/142387131042/nodejs-left-pad"/>
        <updated>2021-07-31T00:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pleasures of Tsundoku: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Book Piles]]></title>
        <id>https://lithub.com/the-pleasures-of-tsundoku-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-book-piles/</id>
        <link href="https://lithub.com/the-pleasures-of-tsundoku-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-book-piles/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basic HTML5 Template: Use This HTML Boilerplate as a Starter for Any Web Dev Project]]></title>
        <id>6053023028094f59be257c79</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/basic-html5-template-boilerplate-code-example/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are building a new website, it is important to have a good starting foundation. In this article, I will explain what an HTML 5 boilerplate is and how to create a basic template to use in your projects.  What is an HTML 5 boilerplate?According to Wikipedia,  boilerplate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Programmer-Specified Aliasing Is a Bad Idea (2004) [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.94.140&amp;rep=rep1&amp;type=pdf</id>
        <link href="http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.94.140&amp;rep=rep1&amp;type=pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excel Text Function – How to Convert a Number to Text Format]]></title>
        <id>60f534d266c61b07d458ecf8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-text-function-how-to-convert-a-number-to-text-format/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to add a number to a text string, you can't do so directly since the format isn't maintained. Also, a number added to a text string doesn't have any formatting or all its decimal places.  The TEXT function comes in handy here, as it allows you to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Advanced Actor-Critic Methods: Reinforcement Learning Course]]></title>
        <id>610478b63306a507d1bfbb23</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-advanced-actor-critic-methods-reinforcement-learning-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actor-Critic Methods are very useful reinforcement learning techniques. Actor-critic methods are most useful for applications in robotics as they allow software to output continuous, rather than discrete actions. This enables control of electric motors to actuate movement in robotic systems, at the expense of increased computational complexity. We just released]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Hyperlink? Definition for HTML Link Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6102c9803306a507d1bfb0f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-hyperlink-definition-for-html-link-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T22:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Links are a defining featute of the Web and you'll find them everywhere.  As their name suggests, they create links, or connections, between pages. This allows us to navigate quickly and easily from one webpage to another.  You'll find many types of links on the Web.  There are links that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs Voice Typing – How to Use Speech-to-Text in a Google Doc]]></title>
        <id>60f5350266c61b07d458ed04</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-docs-voice-typing-how-to-use-speech-to-text-in-a-google-doc/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T20:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speech-to-Text is a really useful accessibility tool if typing is difficult for you. Or you can also use it if you like to think out loud and transcribe what you say. In this tutorial, I'll show you how to use speech-to-text in Google Docs. Do note, though, that this feature]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Shared ESLint Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345628</id>
        <link href="https://katydecorah.com/code/eslint-config/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T20:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like it was almost 9 years ago when Airbnb first published their JavaScript Style Guide. 112k stars on GitHub later, it seems like the de facto preset for Babel / ES Lint. But it’s not the only company …
The post A Shared ESLint Configuration appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Still Don’t Get Things Done]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wired.com/story/to-do-apps-failed-productivity-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/to-do-apps-failed-productivity-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T18:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conjuring Generative Blobs With The CSS Paint API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345256</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/conjuring-generative-blobs-with-the-css-paint-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T14:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Paint API (part of the magical Houdini family) opens the door to an exciting new world of design in CSS. Using the Paint API, we can create custom shapes, intricate patterns, and beautiful animations — all with a …
The post Conjuring Generative Blobs With The CSS Paint API appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Francis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6687</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/now-discover-your-strengths-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=now-discover-your-strengths-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Now, Discover Your Strengths shows you how to find your top five strengths by outlining what strengths are, how you get them, why they’re important to reaching your full potential, and how to discover your own through analyzing the times when your behavior is the most natural or instinctive and why. Read in: 4 […]
The post Now, Discover Your Strengths Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An E-Commerce Site With Angular 11, Commerce Layer And Paypal]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/ecommerce-angular11-headless-paypal/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having an e-commerce store is crucial for any store owner as more and more customers are turning to online shopping. In this tutorial, we shall go through how to create an e-commerce site with Angular 11. The site will use the Commerce Layer as a headless e-commerce API and use Paypal to process payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Camera2 – How to Use the Camera2 API to Take Photos and Videos]]></title>
        <id>60f0501b66c61b07d458df00</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/android-camera2-api-take-photos-and-videos/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T22:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all use the camera on our phones and we use it a l-o-t. There are even some applications that have integrated the camera as a feature.  On one end, there is a standard way of interacting with the camera. On the other, there is a way to customize your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19408</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/29/measuring-memory-usage-virtual-versus-real-memory/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T21:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developers are often concerned with the memory usage of their applications, and rightly so. Software that uses too much memory can fail, or be slow. Memory allocation will not work the same way under all systems. However, at a high level, most modern operating systems have virtual memory and physical memory (RAM). When you write … Continue reading Measuring memory usage: virtual versus real memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Explains the Open Graph Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345518</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2021-06-22-framework-building-open-graph-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T19:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An explanation of those new GitHub social media images:
[…] our custom Open Graph image service is a little Node.js app that uses the GitHub GraphQL API to collect data, generates some HTML from a template, and pipes it to 
…
The post GitHub Explains the Open Graph Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Equal Sign – How to Type the Does Not Equal Symbol]]></title>
        <id>60f534ec66c61b07d458ecfe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/not-equal-sign-how-to-type-the-does-not-equal-symbol/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T18:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The does not equal symbol, or ≠, is often not part of a standard keyboard setup – or it's well hidden. So if you need to write it, how do you do it? How to Write the Not Equal Sign on Desktop DevicesOn Windows: Use the Character MapThe Character Map is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Deploy 12 Apps to AWS, Azure, &amp; Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>6102ccd03306a507d1bfb150</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-deploy-12-apps-to-aws-azure-google-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T15:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing an app makes it simpler to deploy. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to deploy 12 apps to 3 popular hosting services. Scalable Scripts developed this course. They create courses on all sorts of languages and frameworks on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Basic Excel Tutorial – How to Automate Repetitive Tasks in a Spreadsheet]]></title>
        <id>60fc708a22b0e2078fcd0cdc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-repetitive-tasks-in-excel-with-vba/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use VBA, or Visual Basic for Applications, to automate my repetitive tasks. This saves me quite a lot of time in my day-to-day life.  Based on the fact that you're reading this tutorial, I assume that you would like to be able to do the same. So I will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python If Else Statement – Conditional Statements Explained]]></title>
        <id>61018d5c3306a507d1bfa74a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-if-else-statement-conditional-statements-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T15:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many cases where you don't want all of your code to be executed in your programs.  Instead, you might want certain code to run only when a specific condition is met, and a different set of code to run when the condition is not satisified.  That's where conditional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So you want to self-publish books and courses on programming]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344993</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-you-want-to-self-publish-books-and-courses-on-programming/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Resig and I recently self-published our book on GraphQL. There are tons of how-tos for self-publishing a book, or even online classes, but very little in the way of why you would want to, or whether it’s even worth …
The post So you want to self-publish books and courses on programming appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Loren Sands-Ramshaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer-Friendly Passwordless Auth]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345260</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/developer-friendly-passwordless-auth/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T14:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’d wager to say that most websites that are business-minded have accounts. A way to log into them. Social media sites, eCommerce sites, CMS systems, you name it, having accounts people log into is at the heart of them. So… …
The post Developer-Friendly Passwordless Auth appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Such Thing As A CSS Absolute Unit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/css-absolute-units/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are absolute units? What are the differences between relative and absolute units, and how do we create accurate sizes on the web? In this article, Elad Shechter explains why CSS absolute units aren’t so absolute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elad Shechter)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari 15 Opinions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345404</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/safari-15-opinions/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T20:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was interesting that when Safari 15 was dropping at this last WWDC, in my circles at least, I mostly heard enthusiasm. Like the colors-in-the-browser-controls stuff was a neat trick and fun to play with. And there were other …
The post Safari 15 Opinions appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Absolute Value, Sign, Rounding and Modulo in CSS Today]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=320544</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-absolute-value-sign-rounding-and-modulo-in-css-today/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T14:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For quite a while now, the CSS spec has included a lot of really useful mathematical functions, such as trigonometric functions (sin(), cos(), tan(), asin(), acos(), atan(), atan2()), exponential functions (…
The post Using Absolute Value, Sign, Rounding and Modulo in CSS Today appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Tudor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Democracies Die Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6683</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-democracies-die-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-democracies-die-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How Democracies Die explores the foundational ideas of democracy by looking at historical events, especially in Latin America, that show how democracies have failed, whether it can happen again, and how to protect democracy from threats like mutual toleration, inequality, and political parties. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: When Donald […]
The post How Democracies Die Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating An Accessible Dialog From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/accessible-dialog-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dialogs are everywhere in modern interface design (for good or for bad), and yet many of them are not accessible to assistive technologies. In this article, we will dig into how to create a short script to create accessible dialogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kitty Giraudel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learnings From a WebPageTest Session on CSS-Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345169</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/learnings-from-a-webpagetest-session-on-css-tricks/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T23:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got together with Tim Kadlec from over at WebPageTest the other day to use do a bit of performance testing on CSS-Tricks. Essentially use the tool, poke around, and identify performance pain points to work on. You can watch …
The post Learnings From a WebPageTest Session on CSS-Tricks appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ES2021 Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345400</id>
        <link href="https://h3manth.com/ES2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T23:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hemanth HM very succinctly shows off ES2021 features. Gosh it doesn’t feel like that long ago that all we could talk about is ES2015, and now that’s over a half-decade behind us. 
There are new things like “arbitrarily chuck underscores …
The post ES2021 Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Logical Properties and Values]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344815</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-logical-properties-and-values/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T15:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that cross-browser support is at a tipping point, it’s a good time to take a look at logical properties and values. If you’re creating a website in multiple languages, logical properties and values are incredibly useful. Even if you’re …
The post CSS Logical Properties and Values appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global vs. Local Styling In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/global-local-styling-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has strong opinions about how to organize JavaScript but not CSS. How can we develop patterns that encourage best CSS practices while also following the framework’s logic? The answer is surprisingly simple — to write well-structured CSS that balances global and local styling concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Dubovoy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying styled-components]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345297</id>
        <link href="https://www.joshwcomeau.com/react/demystifying-styled-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-27T00:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joshua Comeau digs into how styled-components works by re-building the basics. A fun and useful journey. 
styled-components seems like the biggest player in the CSS-in-React market. Despite being in that world, I haven’t yet been fully compelled by it. I’m …
The post Demystifying styled-components appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Built a Cross-Platform Desktop Application with Svelte, Redis, and Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344653</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-built-a-cross-platform-desktop-application-with-svelte-redis-and-rust/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T14:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Cloudflare, we have a great product called Workers KV which is a key-value storage layer that replicates globally. It can handle millions of keys, each of which is accessible from within a Worker script at exceptionally low latencies, …
The post How I Built a Cross-Platform Desktop Application with Svelte, Redis, and Rust appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slinkity]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345288</id>
        <link href="https://slinkity.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T14:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps the #1 reason I love Astro is that it brings the JavaScript component authoring experience to the Static Site Generator world with zero JavaScript (except bits you very specifically opt-in to). That HTML-first approach is also why I like …
The post Slinkity appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kindness Method Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6677</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-kindness-method-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-kindness-method-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T12:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Kindness Method by Shahroo Izadi teaches how self-compassion and understanding make forming habits easier than being hard on yourself, using the personal experiences of the author and what she’s learned as an addiction recovery therapist to show how self-esteem is the true key to behavior change. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post The Kindness Method Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Serverless Functions And The International Space Station]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/gatsby-serverless-functions-international-space-station/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-26T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby recently announced the launch of “functions”. In this article, Paul Scanlon explains how to get the current location of the International Space Station (ISS) as it orbits the Earth in real-time using [Gatsby Functions](https://www.gatsbyjs.com/docs/reference/functions/) and then display it on a 3D interactive globe using [React Three Fibre](https://github.com/pmndrs/react-three-fiber).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Features That May Not Work As You’d Expect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344019</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-features-that-may-not-work-as-youd-expect/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T15:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the web gets more and more capable, developers are able to make richer online experiences. There are times, however, where some new web capabilities may not work as you would expect in the interest of usability, security and privacy.…
The post Web Features That May Not Work As You’d Expect appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farai Gandiya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My petite-vue review]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345209</id>
        <link href="https://daverupert.com/2021/07/petite-vue-review/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T15:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave:
petite-vue is a new cut of the Vue project specifically built with progressive enhancement in mind. At 5kb, petite-vue is a lightweight Alpine (or jQuery) alternative that can be “sprinkled” over your project requiring no extra bundling steps 
…
The post My petite-vue review appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soundtracks Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6665</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/soundtracks-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=soundtracks-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T12:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Soundtracks is New York Times bestselling author Jon Acuff’s 2021 book that teaches you how to beat overthinking by challenging whether your thoughts are true, retiring unhelpful and unkind ideas, adopting thought-boosting mantras from others, using symbols to reinforce positive thoughts, and more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Is there […]
The post Soundtracks Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Attracting Clients To Your Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/guide-attracting-clients-agency/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many web design agencies consider it a badge of honor that they win work exclusively through word-of-mouth recommendations. In this article, Paul Boag explains why that is entirely the wrong attitude and what to do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Time To Your Schedule As A Professional]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/time-schedule-professional-trafft/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you running a business and have too many things going on at once? Meetings, bugs, customer feedback, new clients in addition to your already tight deadlines? Let’s face it, time management is hard, and it becomes even more difficult in the trying times we are in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[75 Hard Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6657</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/75-hard-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=75-hard-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-22T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: 75 Hard is a fitness challenge and book that teaches mental toughness by making you commit to five daily critical tasks for 75 days straight, including drinking a gallon of water, reading 10 pages of a non-fiction book, doing two 45-minute workouts, taking a progress picture, and following a diet. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post 75 Hard Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? We’ve collected some useful color tools and resources that we’ve discovered lately — to help you get the most out of your creativity. We’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [accessible front-end components](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/complete-guide-accessible-front-end-components/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fail Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6656</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-fail-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-fail-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T12:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Fail shows the surprising benefits of going through a difficult time through the experiences of the author, Elizabeth Day, including the failures in her life that she’s grateful for and how they’ve helped her grow, uncovering why we shouldn’t be so afraid of failure but instead embrace it. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post How To Fail Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From WordPress To A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at when it makes sense to migrate from a monolithic project to a headless setup and the benefits that come with it. In addition to a step-by-step guide on how to migrate WordPress to Storyblok Headless CMS, the problems that will arise during the process and how to deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Change Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6655</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-change-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-change-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T06:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Change by Katy Milkman identifies the stumbling blocks that are in your way of reaching your goals and improving yourself and the research-backed ways to get over them, including how to beat some of the worst productivity and life problems like procrastination, laziness, and much more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post How To Change Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Stopping Time Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6638</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-art-of-stopping-time-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-art-of-stopping-time-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T12:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Art of Stopping Time teaches a framework of mindfulness, philosophy, and time-management you can use to achieve Time Prosperity, which is having plenty of time to reach your dreams without overwhelm, tumult, or constriction. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: What would you say if I asked you what the […]
The post The Art Of Stopping Time Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining End-To-End Quality With Visual Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding visual elements to your tests, you can gain more options to add meaningful ways in maintaining a high level of quality for your app. Colby Fayock explains how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Colby Fayock)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Insights I Gained While Researching Vue.js Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web app accessibility appears difficult because it seems that there is little information on the subject available online. Let’s take a closer look at the accessible use of framework features, concrete Vue.js traits, as well as community initiatives and vetted patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are You Doing With Your Life Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6595</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/what-are-you-doing-with-your-life-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=what-are-you-doing-with-your-life-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: What Are You Doing With Your Life is a book by the great philosopher and teacher Jiddu Krishnamurti, who turns traditional ideas about happiness and the purpose of life on its head by diving into the details of life’s most important questions so you can live with intention and joy more consistently. Read in: […]
The post What Are You Doing With Your Life Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISR vs DPR: Big Words, Quick Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two strategies for incrementally building websites that are growing in popularity: Incremental Static Regeneration and Distributed Persistent Rendering. What’s the difference? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cassidy Williams)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Do That With A JavaScript Data Grid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll get to see some pretty groundbreaking things you can achieve with modern JavaScript grids and discover new ways to augment a data grid to make it engaging, responsive, and accessible. All this will be illustrated using Kendo UI Data Grids and their features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Way Of Integrity Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6594</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-way-of-integrity-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-way-of-integrity-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T12:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Way Of Integrity uses science, spirituality, humor, and Dante’s Divine Comedy to teach you how to find well-being, healing, a sense of purpose, and much more by rediscovering integrity, or the recently lost art of living true to yourself by what you do, think and say. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post The Way Of Integrity Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19380</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/14/faster-sorted-array-unions-by-reducing-branches/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing an index, a database or a search engine, you frequently need to compute the union of two sorted sets. When I am not using fancy low-level instructions, I have most commonly computed the union of two sorted sets using the following approach: v1 = first value in input 1 v2 = first value … Continue reading Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Broken Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Too often dealing with filters can be frustrating. Let’s get them right. That means never freeze the UI on a single input, provide text input fallback and never auto-scroll users on a single input. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Dynamic Header With Intersection Observer]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, attaching an event listener to constantly fire a callback on scroll can be performance-intensive. But there is a better way with Intersection Observer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From jQuery To Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’re taking a closer look at different approaches and strategies on how we can migrate a web application that uses jQuery framework, and start using one of the coolest React frameworks in the market: Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Introduction (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS refactoring is not an easy task — it needs to be done in a way that doesn't create problems. First we need to analyze the existing codebase, audit CSS codebase health, discover weaknesses, agree on the approach, and convince management to invest time and resources into the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19369</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/10/science-and-technology-links-july-10th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use CRISPR, a state-of-the-art gene editing technique, to edit the genes of live human patients in a clinical trials. A clinical trial has begun regarding an HIV vaccine. If you choose to forgo meat to fight climate change, you may lower your individual’s lifetime warming contribution by 2 to 4%. Age-related testosterone loss may … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making A Strong Case For Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility is often overlooked or bolted on to the end of a project. Let’s figure out how to implement and advocate for accessibility from the inception of a project to the release or handoff and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Todd Libby)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools And Practices To Speed Up The Vue.js Development Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though Vue.js claims to have an approachable minimalist framework that can be incrementally adaptable, it can be a little bit overwhelming when starting as a Vue.js newbie. In this article, we’re looking at ways to make writing Vue.js a breeze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Uma Victor)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Figma Interactive Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Components in Figma allows designers to create a component with states (hover, active, clicked, focus) and make it interactive so that every copy of the component will inherit those same interactions by default. Let’s explore how it can reduce the time and effort needed to create interactions for your mock-ups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emiliano Cicero)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an array of Headless CMSes out there. In this article, we delve into headless CMS features to satisfy your content editors, marketers and yourself as a developer. For the experience headless practitioner, this could be a checklist to see what’s new out there. For those starting out on their headless journey, this could be a guide on what to look for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emmanuel Tissera)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HSL Colors In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ahmad Shadeed explains what HSL is, how to use it, and shares some of the useful use-cases and examples that you can use right away in your current projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>