<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-28T01:47:07.741Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-28T01:47:07.741Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.9.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etleap (YC W13) Is Hiring a Technical End User Documentation Writer]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27310586</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27310586"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T01:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QUIC is now RFC 9000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fastly.com/blog/quic-is-now-rfc-9000</id>
        <link href="https://www.fastly.com/blog/quic-is-now-rfc-9000"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T00:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A six figure meme making job at a legit company]]></title>
        <id>https://twitter.com/nateliason/status/1397719837204418561</id>
        <link href="https://twitter.com/nateliason/status/1397719837204418561"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T00:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stuffed Dormouse and Fish Gut Sauce: The Flavors of Pompeii (2019)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/07/arts/design/rome-food-last-supper-in-pompeii.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/07/arts/design/rome-food-last-supper-in-pompeii.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T00:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring DEV.to API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mwrpwr/exploring-dev-to-api-45ni</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mwrpwr/exploring-dev-to-api-45ni"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T00:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You often forget that APIs exist for most of the platforms you use. While some companies lock down their APIs to only provide very limited information, DEV.to goes the extra mile to provide an extremely robust API. Let’s go over what is available!




Link to Project: https://www.josephamaurer.com/Projects/DevAPI/RecentDevPosts.html 
Link to DEV API Documentation: https://docs.forem.com/api/ 
DEV’s API allows for lots of interesting functionality. In the video above, I go over a use case where you pull the latest 100 posts, and create bootstrap cards for each. In each card I display three buttons. The first is either active or disabled if the user has a twitter account. This is useful because I like to retweet articles and tag their creators. The second button is a link to the DEV post. Finally the third button opens the API response for the article.
While my example showed articles, there are lots of different things that the API can return to you. One of the more interesting functionality is the ability to post an article completely from the API. I have no idea why you would want to do that, but it could be useful. 
All in all, it’s cool to think that this functionality exists, even if you can’t find a practical use case for it. One of the more useful use cases might just be populating your recent articles from your blog to your website. 
Let me know what you would want to do with this API!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Maurer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple GUI on Linux Using Zenity and Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ferfox1981/simple-gui-on-linux-using-zenity-and-node-js-2kei</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ferfox1981/simple-gui-on-linux-using-zenity-and-node-js-2kei"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T23:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is incredible the amount of "secret" features on Linux that are not well known until today.
My goal is to do the following:
Use Node.js to access financial data related to Brazilian Treasury Bonds (Tesouro Direto in Brazil);
Create a mechanism to sistematically check instant treasury rates;
Use Zenity to pop-up a notification to user;
Tesouro Direto Rates can be found here. In addition, if you press F12 and check Network Tab, you'll see that the following json is received by the browser:  https://www.tesourodireto.com.br/json/br/com/b3/tesourodireto/service/api/treasurybondsinfo.json 
const axios = require('axios');
const { exec } = require("child_process");
const https = require('https');



const instance = axios.create({
  httpsAgent: new https.Agent({
    rejectUnauthorized: false
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Raposo da Camara Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to send web push notifications in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcushellberg/how-to-send-web-push-notifications-in-java-21lo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcushellberg/how-to-send-web-push-notifications-in-java-21lo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T23:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web push notifications are a way of informing your app users when something important has happened. 
Users can receive web push notifications even when they are not actively using your application, for instance, if the app is open in a background tab or even if it's not open. 

Push notifications are widely supported by all browsers except for Safari: 78% of web users use a browser that supports them.
In this tutorial, I'll show you how to subscribe to notifications in the browser and how to send notifications from a Java server. 





  
  
  A bit of background: how web push notifications work


Web push notifications rely on two web standards: Notification API and Push API (which in turn uses ServiceWorker). They require HTTPS to work. 
The server shares its public key with the browser
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcus Hellberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Microservices in Go: REST APIs - HTTP Handlers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mariocarrion/building-microservices-in-go-rest-apis-http-handlers-578g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mariocarrion/building-microservices-in-go-rest-apis-http-handlers-578g"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T23:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building Microservices the de facto way to do it is to use both HTTP, as the protocol, and REST, as the way to represent resources. HTTP is literally the foundation of the World Wide Web and it is supported by multiple programmings in one way or another, so using HTTP is a no brainer because it could be used by any Frontend and Backend code with few to no external dependencies.
REST is an acronym for REpresentational State Transfer coined by Roy Fielding and introduced in his doctoral dissertation, it is an architectural style that defines guidelines when building web services, it's not a standard but it does use standards like HTTP (and its verbs to represent actions) and payload/message formats (like JSON or XML), to mention a few.
This is the first of a series of posts covering ste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Carrion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oh My ZSH! Deixando seu terminal mais interessante]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/computandoarte/oh-my-zsh-deixando-seu-terminal-mais-interessante-2ci7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/computandoarte/oh-my-zsh-deixando-seu-terminal-mais-interessante-2ci7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T23:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover photo by Cookie the Pom on Unsplash
Neste pequeno tutorial, vou mostrar como instalar o Oh My ZSH! e deixar seu terminal um pouco mais limpo, interessante e com as informações que importam para você.
Atenção: Estou utilizando o MacOS Big Sur e o iTerm2 (versão 3.4.3). Para versões do Ubuntu 16+, o ZSH precisa estar instalado.
Qualquer dúvida, pode mandar abaixo que responderei assim que for possível.
Instale o Oh My ZSH!




sh -c "$(curl -fsSL https://raw.github.com/robbyrussell/oh-my-zsh/master/tools/install.sh)"

Feche e abra novamente o terminal
Abra o .zshrc para mudar o tema




vim ~/.zshrc

Mude o valor da variável de /ZSH_THEM="robbyrussell" para ZSH_THEME="kolo" (ou outro tema de sua preferência). Salve a modificação pressionando ESC e em seguida digite :wq

Carregue o tema…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Bertan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upload videos on GitHub (now GA!)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/upload-videos-on-github-now-ga-2en0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/upload-videos-on-github-now-ga-2en0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T23:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we talk about uploading and using videos in GitHub.
As developers, the ability to collaborate through videos (for example, pair programming, demos, etc.) is an extremely important part of a software workflow, especially for communities and teams that are distributed.
GitHub video support is now finally GA, so let's see how it works
Let's quickly see how to upload a video in GitHub, and then let's explore few scenarios where this can be very helpful:




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/h6fOErvWIGI
As you have seen, uploading a video in GitHub Issues, Pull Requests and Discussions is super straight forward. I wanna share 3 scenarios in which uploading a video can be helpful.
Bugs are something that every developer deals with, but sometimes words aren’t enough to help someone else r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Next.js 10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fayvik/what-s-new-in-next-js-10-2-n34</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fayvik/what-s-new-in-next-js-10-2-n34"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T23:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js is a framework for building React web applications, super-fast static websites, and single-page JavaScript applications. It was designed to help solve common problems associated with React development, including production optimizations such as code splitting, code bundlers (webpack), and code compilers (Babel).
Next.js is also gaining popularity for its superior developer experience and many built-in features, notably automatic code splitting for faster page loading and client-side routing with optimized prefetching. 
On 28 April 2021, the Next.js team announced the release of Next.js 10.2 with even more attractive new features. The new release enables developers to build hybrid applications containing both server-rendered and statically generated pages.
In this guide, we’ll take …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>favour vivian woka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Tutorial: Learn Git Branching in 5 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/educative/git-tutorial-learn-git-branching-in-5-minutes-1f8p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/educative/git-tutorial-learn-git-branching-in-5-minutes-1f8p"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T22:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is one of the most widely used version control systems and is an important tool for every developer to know. One of the greatest benefits of Git is its branching capabilities. Git branching is a fundamental aspect of your version control workflow. Today, we’ll discuss how to create, delete, merge, and rebase Git branches. Afterward, we’ll cover the next steps you can take to further your Git knowledge.
We'll cover:
What is branching?
Creating branches
Deleting branches
Merging branches
Rebasing branches
Git concepts to learn next

Imagine you’re working on a project with your team, and you’re creating a new feature that requires a lot of changes to the codebase. In the process, you discover a bug that needs to be fixed. This bug is related to your new feature, and you don’t want to aff…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Schaffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Golden Age of Developer Advocacy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stripe/welcome-to-the-golden-age-of-developer-advocacy-51fe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stripe/welcome-to-the-golden-age-of-developer-advocacy-51fe"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T22:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary: The displacement of in-person developer events has vaulted Developer Advocacy forward by years. The momentum of self-forming communities, better streaming capabilities, and the rise of scaled developer experiences are a peek into the direction of our field of work.
A quick google search for Developer Advocate will present over 42 million results with the top results clearly showing a trend:
"What the heck is a Developer Advocate?"
"What is Developer Advocacy?"
"What exactly is the job of a developer advocate?"
At the end of this search, you will discover there's no singular answer. The shape of work depends on the organization's goals, the product offering, and existing expectations the community. For many Advocates, the answer comes into focus through the context of an individual…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Traganos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O Ciclo de Vida do Request no Phoenix]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maiquitome/o-ciclo-de-vida-do-request-no-phoenix-53e7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maiquitome/o-ciclo-de-vida-do-request-no-phoenix-53e7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T22:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O objetivo deste artigo é falar sobre o Ciclo de Vida do Request no framework web para a Linguagem de Programação Elixir chamado Phoenix. Esse assunto é introdutório para começarmos a aprender o framework, onde criaremos duas páginas ao longo do nosso projeto.
Como base para este guia, foram retirados alguns trechos da documentação oficial do Phoenix, e de algumas ideias do bootcamp da Rocketseat.
Primeiramente, vamos criar o projeto rodando o comando abaixo:
$ mix phx.new hello_phoenix --no-ecto

Note que usamos um underline para separar o nome hello_phoenix. Essa separação chamada de snake case é uma convenção da comunidade Elixir, usada bastante também para nomear arquivos. Com o underline, nossa aplicação vai conseguir converter o nome hello_phoenix para HelloPhoenix em nomes de módulo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maiqui Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Platform.sh VueJS platform.sh gridsome  application deployment template]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/leamsigc/platform-sh-vuejs-platform-sh-gridsome-application-deployment-template-45h2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/leamsigc/platform-sh-vuejs-platform-sh-gridsome-application-deployment-template-45h2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T22:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently I need to deploy my application to  platform.sh but could find a good example for the template for a vue - grid some application so here it is:


The application that I'm currently using for this test is this
mendozaRoofing
Mendoza roofing Wilmington NC <- Host in Netlify currently
For the .platform.app.yaml file I have the fallowing configuration
# .platform.app.yaml

# The name of this application, which must be unique within a project.
name: "vuejs"

# The type key specifies the language and version for your application.
type: "nodejs:14"

build:
  flavor: none

# Build dependencies.
dependencies:
  nodejs:
    "@gridsome/cli": "*"

# The hooks that will be triggered when the package is deployed.
hooks:
  # Build hooks can modify the application files on disk but not access any services like databases.
  build: |
    npm i
    gridsome build
# The size of the persistent disk of the application (in MB).
disk: 5120

# The configuration of the application when it is exposed to the web.
web:
  locations:
    "/":
      # The public directory of the application relative to its root.
      root: "dist" #The build directory if you have a custom output directory then you should change it
      index: ["index.html"]
      scripts: false
      allow: true


.platform folder


For the router.yaml file that should go in the .platform directory
# Each route describes how an incoming URL is going to be processed by Platform.sh.
"https://www.{default}/":
  type: upstream
  upstream: "vuejs:http"
#Remember the the name in the .platform.app.yaml  should be the same for the name before the :http

"https://{default}/":
  type: redirect
  to: "https://www.{default}/"


For the services.yaml file that should go in the .platform directory
Currently, I have this file empty because is just a static site.
The site link from the platform.sh 
Deploy Site]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ismael garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[awesome Css Loader in 2 min!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mohammedelmredi/awesome-css-loader-in-2-min-2kb6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mohammedelmredi/awesome-css-loader-in-2-min-2kb6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T22:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello


If you have been working with CSS before you may have trouble with animation,transitions,etc...
Create index.html file




<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<title>Loader!</title>
</head>
<body>
<div class="loader" >
<span></span>
<span></span>
<span></span>
<span></span>
<span></span>
<span></span>
</div>
</body>
</html>

<style type="text/css">
body {
background:#000;
}

.loader {
position:absolute;
width:100px;
height:100px;
transform:translate(-50%, -50%);
top:50%;
left:50%;
border-radius:50%;
animation:rotate 1.3s ease infinite;
}




.loader span {
position:absolute;
top:50%;
left:50%;
transform:translate(-50%, -50%);
width:100%;
animation:rotate 1.7s ease infinite;
}

.loader span::before {
content:"";
position:absolute;
top:50%;
left:100%;
transform:translate(-50%, -50%);
width:4px;
border-radius:50%;
height:15px;
background:#38f860;
}

.loader span:nth-child(1) {
animation-delay:0.1s;
}
.loader span:nth-child(2) {
animation-delay:0.2s;
}
.loader span:nth-child(3) {
animation-delay:0.3s;
}
.loader span:nth-child(4) {
animation-delay:0.4s;
}
.loader span:nth-child(5) {
animation-delay:0.5s;
}

@keyframes rotate {

0%{
transform:translate(-50%, -50%) rotate(0deg);
filter:hue-rotate(0deg);
}
50% {
filter:hue-rotate(120deg);
}
100%{
transform:translate(-50%, -50%) rotate(360deg);
filter:hue-rotate(0deg);
}
}







</style>







  
  
  And that's it run the HTML file in the browser to see an awesome Loader]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammed-elmredi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second-guessing the modern web (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2020/05/10/spa-fatigue.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2020/05/10/spa-fatigue.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T21:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Intuition for Lisp Syntax]]></title>
        <id>https://stopa.io/post/265?repost=true</id>
        <link href="https://stopa.io/post/265?repost=true"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T19:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The media's lab leak fiasco]]></title>
        <id>https://www.slowboring.com/p/the-medias-lab-leak-fiasco</id>
        <link href="https://www.slowboring.com/p/the-medias-lab-leak-fiasco"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T19:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To $ or Not to $: Displaying Terminal Code Snippets]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341298</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/to-or-not-to-displaying-terminal-code-snippets/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T18:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s very popular to put a $ on lines that are intended to be a command in code documentation that involves the terminal (i.e. the command line).
Like this:
$ brew install somepackage
The point of that is that it …
The post To $ or Not to $: Displaying Terminal Code Snippets appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JsonLogic]]></title>
        <id>https://jsonlogic.com/</id>
        <link href="https://jsonlogic.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T18:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Machine Learning Model Performance by Combining Categorical Features]]></title>
        <id>60af931811ffb70827ef85d3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-machine-learning-model-performance-by-combining-categorical-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T17:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're training a machine learning model, you can have some features in your dataset that represent categorical values. Categorical features are types of data that you can divide into groups. There are three common categorical data types: Ordinal – a set of values in ascending or descending order. Example: rating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New dark matter map reveals cosmic mystery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-57244708</id>
        <link href="https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-57244708"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T17:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stacked Git – manage commits as a stack of patches]]></title>
        <id>https://stacked-git.github.io/</id>
        <link href="https://stacked-git.github.io/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T17:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manifest v3 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/addons/2021/05/27/manifest-v3-update/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/addons/2021/05/27/manifest-v3-update/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T16:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Egyptian Circumnavigation of Africa ~600 BC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.livius.org/sources/content/herodotus/herodotus-on-the-first-circumnavigation-of-africa/</id>
        <link href="https://www.livius.org/sources/content/herodotus/herodotus-on-the-first-circumnavigation-of-africa/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T16:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[V8 Sparkplug – A non-optimizing JavaScript compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://v8.dev/blog/sparkplug</id>
        <link href="https://v8.dev/blog/sparkplug"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T16:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Bouncing Basketball in Unity with Materials and Textures 🏀]]></title>
        <id>60a325c6906c5207e3a7da25</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-basketball-in-unity-with-materials-and-textures/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T15:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll teach you how to make a basketball using materials and textures in Unity. You can extend this micro-concept to create any kind of ball like a football, tennis ball, or snooker balls.  That said, these techniques aren't just limited to creating round 3D objects like balls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phil's Old Radios]]></title>
        <id>https://antiqueradio.org/welcome.htm</id>
        <link href="https://antiqueradio.org/welcome.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: NocoDB – The Open Source Airtable Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/nocodb/nocodb</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/nocodb/nocodb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Convect – Instant Serverless Deployment of ML Models]]></title>
        <id>https://convect.ml</id>
        <link href="https://convect.ml"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Show Images on Click]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341020</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-show-images-on-click/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most images on the web are superfluous. If I might be a jerk for a bit, 99% of them aren’t even that helpful at all (although there are rare exceptions). That’s because images don’t often complement the text they’re …
The post How to Show Images on Click appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Postgres in a Post-Server World]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340910</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/rethinking-postgres-in-a-post-server-world/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architectures have brought engineering teams a great number of benefits. We get simpler deployments, automatic and infinite scale, better concurrency, and a stateless API surface. It’s hard to imagine going back to the world of managed services, broken local …
The post Rethinking Postgres in a Post-Server World appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Rispoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marvell Announces First PCIe 5.0 NVMe SSD Controllers: Up to 14 GB/S]]></title>
        <id>https://www.anandtech.com/show/16703/marvell-announces-first-pcie-50-nvme-ssd-controllers</id>
        <link href="https://www.anandtech.com/show/16703/marvell-announces-first-pcie-50-nvme-ssd-controllers"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDN Plus]]></title>
        <id>https://developer.mozilla.org/en/plus</id>
        <link href="https://developer.mozilla.org/en/plus"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Favorite Blogs by Individuals?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27302195</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27302195"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T12:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I, as someone who is visually impaired, use my iPhone (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://twitter.com/Kristy_Viers/status/1287189581926981634</id>
        <link href="https://twitter.com/Kristy_Viers/status/1287189581926981634"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T12:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Emperor Of All Maladies Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6241</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-emperor-of-all-maladies-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-emperor-of-all-maladies-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T12:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Emperor Of All Maladies details the beginnings and progress in our understanding of cancer, including how we first started learning about it, began developing ways to treat it and discovered ways to prevent it, and the biological effect that it has on us. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Virtually […]
The post The Emperor Of All Maladies Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I made a free blogging/bookmarking platform with discussions/discovery]]></title>
        <id>http://wndr.xyz</id>
        <link href="http://wndr.xyz"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Klarna users are being signed in to random accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://twitter.com/esraefe/status/1397842160607711232</id>
        <link href="https://twitter.com/esraefe/status/1397842160607711232"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T10:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Responsive Websites Faster With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roots of 'Program' Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2021/4/251342-roots-of-program-revisited/fulltext</id>
        <link href="https://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2021/4/251342-roots-of-program-revisited/fulltext"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog about what you've struggled with]]></title>
        <id>https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/05/24/blog-about-what-you-ve-struggled-with/</id>
        <link href="https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/05/24/blog-about-what-you-ve-struggled-with/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T08:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mathematicians Find Long-Sought Building Blocks for Special Polynomials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/mathematicians-find-polynomial-building-blocks-hilbert-sought-20210525</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/mathematicians-find-polynomial-building-blocks-hilbert-sought-20210525"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T05:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Carle has died]]></title>
        <id>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/obituaries/eric-carle-dead/2021/05/26/cbb39414-2234-11e4-8593-da634b334390_story.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/obituaries/eric-carle-dead/2021/05/26/cbb39414-2234-11e4-8593-da634b334390_story.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T03:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giphy API Tutorial – How to Generate Animated Text GIFs with ReactJS]]></title>
        <id>60a44b9f906c5207e3a7e098</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/giphy-api-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T21:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial you will create an app that generates dynamic animated text using Giphy's API with ReactJS. After that I'll go over some of the other API features Giphy provides that you can use to make other interesting projects. You can find the code for the tutorial here. Video]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19274</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/26/all-models-are-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T19:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong, but some are useful is a common saying in statistics. It does not merely apply to statistics, however. It is general observation. Box (1976) wrote an  influential article on the topic. He says that you make progress by successively making models followed by experiments, followed by more models, and then more … Continue reading All models are wrong]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open Source  Projects – A Beginner&#x27;s Guide]]></title>
        <id>60abe7fb11ffb70827ef63a6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-projects-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a developer, you've probably come across the term "open source." If you've ever wondered what it's all about and how to contribute, you are in exactly the right place.  I put aside all my fears about how and what to contribute during Hacktoberfest 2020, and made]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Basic Terraform Syntax in 20 minutes]]></title>
        <id>606f4f5fd5756f080ba96b65</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/terraform-syntax-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T18:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll give you a brief overview of the configuration syntax of Terraform.  Terraform's docs provide the most comprehensive look at its syntax. But this article should serve as a condensed quick start introduction that'll give new users a simplified overview. We'll focus on the basic structures without]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome Standalone (Web Components)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339759</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/awesome-standalone-web-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T17:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his last An Event Apart talk, Dave made a point that it’s really only just about right now that Web Components are becoming a practical choice for production web development. For example, it has only been about a year …
The post Awesome Standalone (Web Components) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Web Components]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340901</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-web-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T17:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How we use Web Components at GitHub — Kristján Oddsson talks about how GitHub is using web components. I remember they were very early adopters, and it says here they released a <relative-time> component in 2014! Now they’ve got a 
…
The post Links on Web Components appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a GraphQL API Using Laravel]]></title>
        <id>60abc59d11ffb70827ef6304</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-graphql-api-using-laravel/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T16:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll walk you through how to set up your own GraphQL API using PHP and Laravel. Two years ago, I started working professionally as a backend developer. And I was very intimidated by all the technology I didn't yet know. Words like Docker, Kubernetes, and GraphQL seemed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever hurt yourself from your own code?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nikitas.link/have-you-ever-hurt-yourself-from-your-own-code</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nikitas.link/have-you-ever-hurt-yourself-from-your-own-code"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T16:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Super Mario Bros, Zelda, and Space Invaders with Kaboom.js]]></title>
        <id>60aced0011ffb70827ef6d96</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-mario-zelda-and-space-invaders-with-kaboom-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T14:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video course I show you how to build three popular games using the latest game development library for JavaScript called Kaboom.js. This course is exciting for two reasons: First of all, I am going to be introducing a new technology designed especially for game development in JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Thorough Analysis of CSS-in-JS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340705</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-thorough-analysis-of-css-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T14:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering what’s even more challenging than choosing a JavaScript framework? You guessed it: choosing a CSS-in-JS solution. Why? Because there are more than 50 libraries out there, each of them offering a unique set of features.
We tested 10 different …
The post A Thorough Analysis of CSS-in-JS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrei Pfeiffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptoassets Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6240</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/cryptoassets-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cryptoassets-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T12:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Cryptoassets is your guide to understanding this revolutionary new digital asset class and explains the history of Bitcoin, how to invest in it and other cryptocurrencies, and how the blockchain technology behind it all works. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Have you ever heard of Bitcoin? Of course, you have; […]
The post Cryptoassets Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Tasmanian Devils born in the wild of Australia mainland in 3k years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/first-tasmanian-devils-born-wild-australia-mainland-3000-years-2021-05-26/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/first-tasmanian-devils-born-wild-australia-mainland-3000-years-2021-05-26/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T11:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battlefield of the Cold War: Nevada Test Site 1951 - 1963 [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.osti.gov/opennet/servlets/purl/969352.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://www.osti.gov/opennet/servlets/purl/969352.pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persian legends and their Western counterparts (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tor.com/2020/07/06/5-persian-legends-and-their-western-counterparts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.tor.com/2020/07/06/5-persian-legends-and-their-western-counterparts/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T02:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Calm and Hack The Box – Valentine]]></title>
        <id>60ac3a2711ffb70827ef6aec</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keep-calm-and-hack-the-box-valentine/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T22:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walkthrough for Hack The Box Valentine machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chakra UI and React-Hook-Form –How to Build Beautiful Forms]]></title>
        <id>60a93b0011ffb70827ef5b0d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-hook-form-with-chakra-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T20:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, it’s the default behavior for forms to redirect to a new page whenever they're submitted. So in order to provide dynamic functionality, React uses a strategy called controlled components. If you have recently gone through a React course, you probably didn't like this part, because there are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Portfolio-Worthy Work – Web Design Best Practices for New Developers]]></title>
        <id>608706aedd38b9088c2c012c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-design-best-practices-for-new-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a beginner developer, it can be difficult to find ways to use your limited knowledge to support yourself. And at the same time, you won't be able to hone your skills if you aren't using them full time.  It's a precarious spot that I remember being in when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340759</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-i-learned-building-a-word-game-app-with-nuxt-on-google-play/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I fell in love with coding the moment I created my first CSS :hover effect. Years later, that initial bite into interactivity on the web led me to a new goal: making a game.
Table of contents
What’s the game 
…
The post What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of Power Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6239</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-end-of-power-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-end-of-power-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The End Of Power explains why the old positions of power aren’t as powerful as they used to be due to recent changes in society and technology and how this shift has put more influence in the hands of everyday citizens like you and what it might mean for the future of our governments […]
The post The End Of Power Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Powerful Websites with Serverless-Driven CMS Development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341383</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-powerful-websites-with-serverless-driven-cms-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing the right tools to build a website for your organization is essential, but it can be tough to find the right fit. Simple site builders like Wix and Squarespace are easy for marketers to use, but severely limit developers …
The post Creating Powerful Websites with Serverless-Driven CMS Development appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Bouchefra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340808</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-performance/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T22:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making GitHub’s new homepage fast and performant — Tobias Ahlin describes how the scrolling effects are done more performantly thanks to IntersectionObserver and the fact that it avoids the use of methods that trigger reflows, like getBoundingClientRect. Also, 
…
The post Links on Performance appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[proxy-www]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341153</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/justjavac/proxy-www"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like a good trick. What if… a URL was…  a promise… that fetched said URL?
www.codepen.io.then((response) ={
  console.log(response);
});
That’s what @justjavac did with JavaScript Proxys. A clever trick, that. Don’t @ me about the practicality. Trick…
The post proxy-www appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrangling Control Over PDFs with the Adobe PDF Embed API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340626</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wrangling-control-over-pdfs-with-the-adobe-pdf-embed-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T13:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By our last estimate, there are now more PDFs in the world than atoms in the universe (not verified by outside sources) so chances are, from time to time, you’re going to run into a PDF document or two. Browsers …
The post Wrangling Control Over PDFs with the Adobe PDF Embed API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raymond Camden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spark Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6238</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/spark-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=spark-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Spark teaches you how to become an influential, un-fireable asset to your team at work by taking on the role of a leader regardless of your position, utilizing the power of creative thinking to make better decisions, and learning how to be more self-aware and humble. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the […]
The post Spark Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 22nd 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19268</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/22/science-and-technology-links-may-22nd-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T15:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most computer chips today in flagship phones and computers use a process based on a 5 nm or larger resolution. Finer resolutions usually translate into lower energy usage and lower heat production. Given that many of our systems are limited by heat or power, finer resolutions lead to higher performance. The large Taiwanese chip maker … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 22nd 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340991</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/should-devtools-teach-the-css-cascade/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T23:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Judis, two days before I mouthed off about using (X, X, X, X) for talking about specificity, has a great blog post not only using that format, but advocating that browser DevTools should show us that value by …
The post Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte for the Experienced React Dev]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340825</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svelte-for-the-experienced-react-dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is an accelerated introduction to Svelte from the point of view of someone with solid experience with React. I’ll provide a quick introduction, and then shift focus to things like state management and DOM interoperability, among other things. …
The post Svelte for the Experienced React Dev appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340919</id>
        <link href="https://csshell.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collection of common CSS mistakes, and how to fix them
From Stefánia Péter. 
Clever idea for a site! Some of them are little mind-twisters that could bite you, and some of them are honing in on best practices that …
The post CSS Hell appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Counting the number of matching characters in two ASCII strings]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19258</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/21/counting-the-number-of-matching-characters-in-two-ascii-strings/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose that you give me two ASCII strings having the same number of characters. I wish to compute efficiently the number of matching characters (same position, same character). E.g., the strings ‘012c’ and ‘021c’ have two matching characters (‘0’ and ‘c’). The conventional approach in C would look as follow: uint64_t standard_matching_bytes(char * c1, char … Continue reading Counting the number of matching characters in two ASCII strings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gift Of Fear Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6237</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-gift-of-fear-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-gift-of-fear-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T12:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Gift Of Fear is a guide to understanding how your fear and instincts about other people can protect you by showing you how to recognize and understand the warning signs that criminals and violent people exhibit before they strike. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Michael Cantrell is a police […]
The post The Gift Of Fear Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG) From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSON in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/json-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Neal tweeted a heck of a little CSS trick the other day, putting JSON inside CSS and plucking it out with JavaScript. Valid values for custom properties are quite liberal! So this looks for a CSS rule (e.g. a …
The post JSON in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Double Helix Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6236</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-double-helix-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-double-helix-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T12:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Double Helix tells the story of the discovery of DNA, which is one of the most significant scientific findings in all of history, by explaining the rivalries, struggles of the prideful scientific community to work together, and other roadblocks that James Watson had on the way to making the breakthrough of a lifetime […]
The post The Double Helix Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Think Again Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6235</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/think-again-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=think-again-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T12:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Think Again will make you more intelligent, persuasive, and self-aware by identifying the power of being humble about what you don’t know, how to recognize blind spots in your thinking before they start causing you problems, and what you can do to become more effective at convincing others of your way of thinking. Read […]
The post Think Again Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dark Net Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6234</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-dark-net-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-dark-net-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Dark Net dives into the details of the wildest and most dangerous parts of the digital world, including self-harmers, cryptocurrency programmers, computer scientists, hackers, extremists, pornographers, vigilantes, and much more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: The internet has completely revolutionized pretty much everything we do in today’s world. It […]
The post The Dark Net Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Converting binary integers to ASCII characters: Apple M1 vs AMD Zen2]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19250</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/17/converting-binary-integers-to-ascii-characters-apple-m1-vs-amd-zen2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Programmers often need to write integers as characters. Thus given the 32-bit value 1234, you might need a function that writes the characters 1234. We can use the fact that the ASCII numeral characters are in sequence in the ASCII table: ‘0’+0 is ‘0’, ‘0’+1 is ‘1’ and so forth. With this optimization in mind, … Continue reading Converting binary integers to ASCII characters: Apple M1 vs AMD Zen2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forgiving What You Can’t Forget Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6233</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/forgiving-what-you-cant-forget-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=forgiving-what-you-cant-forget-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Forgiving What You Can’t Forget teaches you how to heal from past traumas that still haunt you today by going through the lessons that author Lysa TerKeurst learned from childhood abuse and an unfaithful spouse, which have helped her find peace even in tough situations by forgiving those who have wronged her. Read in: […]
The post Forgiving What You Can’t Forget Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 15th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19244</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/15/science-and-technology-links-may-15th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were rainforests near the south pole 90 million years ago. Though commercial exchanges are typically win-win for both the buyer and the seller, people tend to view the buyer as more likely to be taken advantage of. People with low self-esteem are more likely to blame the political system for their personal problems. Moscona … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 15th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caste Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6232</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/caste-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=caste-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T12:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Caste unveils the hidden cultural and societal rules of our class system, including where it comes from, why it’s so deeply entrenched in society, and how we can dismantle it forever and finally allow all people to have the equality they deserve.  Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Imagine you inherited […]
The post Caste Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constructing arrays of Boolean values in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19236</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/05/constructing-arrays-of-boolean-values-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not uncommon that we need to represent an array of Boolean (true or false) values. There are multiple ways to do it. The most natural way could be to construct an array of booleans (the native Java type). It is likely that when stored in an array, Java uses a byte per value. … Continue reading Constructing arrays of Boolean values in Java]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (May 1st 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19227</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/01/science-and-technology-links-may-1st-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-01T16:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing your own food could lower your carbon footprint by 3-5%. In recent years, we have acquired the ability to measure biological age: your chronological age does not necessarily match your biological since some people age faster. We measure biological aging with gene expression. Researchers found that an eight-week program of diet, exercise, and meditation … Continue reading Science and Technology links (May 1st 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ideal divisors: when a division compiles down to just a multiplication]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19218</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/04/28/ideal-divisors-when-a-division-compiles-down-to-just-a-multiplication/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T16:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The division instruction is one of the most expensive instruction in your CPU. Thus optimizing compilers often compile divisions by known constants down to a multiplication followed by a shift. However, in some lucky cases, the compiler does not even need a shift. I call the corresponding divisors ideal. For the math. geeks, they are … Continue reading Ideal divisors: when a division compiles down to just a multiplication]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>