<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-25T01:02:54.302Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-25T01:02:54.302Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JWT Tokens are NOT safe]]></title>
        <id>https://redislabs.com/blog/json-web-tokens-jwt-are-dangerous-for-user-sessions/</id>
        <link href="https://redislabs.com/blog/json-web-tokens-jwt-are-dangerous-for-user-sessions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T00:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EvalAI: An Open-Source Alternative to Kaggle]]></title>
        <id>https://eval.ai/</id>
        <link href="https://eval.ai/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T00:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Password with Argon2 Algorithm, the Winner of the Password Hashing Competition]]></title>
        <id>https://argon2.online/</id>
        <link href="https://argon2.online/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T23:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Las 15 mejores extensiones para VSCode (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gdcodev/las-15-mejores-extensiones-para-vscode-2021-430n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gdcodev/las-15-mejores-extensiones-para-vscode-2021-430n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T23:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[En esta ocasión te mostraré las 15 extensiones que debes instalar en Visual Studio Code para sacarle el máximo  provecho y así facilitar tu trabajo día a día como desarrollador.
PRETTIER
Auto Close Tag
Auto Rename Tag
Material Icon Theme
Bracket Pair Colorizer
Better Comments
LIVE SERVER
LIVE SHARE
GITLENS
SNAPCODE
Settings Sync
Code Spell Checker
Import Cost
Markdown All in One
Path Intellisense
PRETTIER 


Formatea tu código de manera automática.





Auto Close Tag 


Tiene soporte de etiqueta cerrada para archivos.





Auto Rename Tag 


Cambia automáticamente el nombre de una etiqueta. Ahorra tiempo al renombrar una etiqueta.





Material Icon Theme 


Con este tema tendrás un entorno limpio, minimalista y atractivo.





Bracket Pair Colorizer 


Permite identificar los corchetes correspondientes con colores.
 
Better Comments 


 Podrás darle color a tus comentarios.





LIVE SERVER 


Server local en tiempo real de nuestra pagina.





LIVE SHARE 


Trabaja en tiempo real en el mismo código.





GITLENS 


Historial de quien ha editado un fragmento de código en GIT.





SNAPCODE 


Capturas de pantalla profesional.





Settings Sync 


Permite sincronizar el estado de su VSCode entre varias instancias.





Code Spell Checker 


Nos ayuda a detectar errores ortográficos.





Import Cost 


Ayuda con la productividad al mostrar el tamaño estimado de un paquete de importación.





Markdown All in One 


Es una extensión muy útil para todo lo relacionado con Markdown.





Path Intellisense 


Esta extensión le ayuda a completar automáticamente la ruta de las importaciones.









Repositorio de Git: https://github.com/gdcodev/extensiones-vscode
Facebook | LinkedIn | GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gastón Danielsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🧑‍💻 How I developed my portfolio for a month 🗓 + Demo 🍿]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kerthin/how-i-developed-my-portfolio-for-a-month-demo-3ee7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kerthin/how-i-developed-my-portfolio-for-a-month-demo-3ee7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T23:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Link to the DEMO at the end
And why spend so much time developing a portfolio at all?      After all, you just need to create a small one-page website and add all the information about yourself and your works there. And here I definitely agree with you that if you are developing a business card website, then this is quite a working option. You don't even have to spend a few days developing such a site. Such a site can be developed in 4-6 hours.
But I set myself a different task. I wanted to create a portfolio that would show with its appearance what kind of developer I am and what I am capable of. I wanted to use animations, build complex objects using HTML and CSS, make smooth transitions between pages, choose bright colors for the site.  But at the same time, of course, I di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do I Need To Know About React Native Coming From React JS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/coleflournoy/what-do-i-need-to-know-about-react-native-coming-from-react-js-2kp0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/coleflournoy/what-do-i-need-to-know-about-react-native-coming-from-react-js-2kp0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T22:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is for the people who are interested in React Native because they have experience with React JS. People who know that being able to develop for mobile and web helps their job prospects but who also want to know how easy it's going to be before they sink in too much time wading through the documentation (which is actually really good, you should check it out).
Getting React Native set up is incredibly easy, so definitely don't let that stop you. In less than five minutes you can be building out an app that you can see displayed on your own phone. 

We'll be using Expo CLI to get rolling quickly (more on the differences between the two here and the limitations of using Expo here). As long as you're on Node 12+, you can install using npm, and create a new project.
npm install -g exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cole-flournoy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Accelerate Your Career During Uncertain Times]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/krowser/how-to-accelerate-your-career-during-uncertain-times-50dn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/krowser/how-to-accelerate-your-career-during-uncertain-times-50dn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T22:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does the current situation have you wondering whether your career has come grinding to a halt? According to experts, growing professionally during a pandemic can be challenging but not impossible. 
View career paths as fluid
Focus on stretching yourself
Leverage your network
Keep pushing forward
Self-isolation and social distancing can make professional advancement more difficult. Yet, despite these challenges, you can still accelerate your career. All it takes is a bit of creativity, initiative and the willingness to believe it’s possible. Focus on these strategies now, and you'll be ahead of the curve when things inevitably take a turn for the better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krowser Web Services</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WD My Book users wake up to find their data deleted]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/06/mass-data-wipe-in-my-book-devices-prompts-warning-from-western-digital/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/06/mass-data-wipe-in-my-book-devices-prompts-warning-from-western-digital/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T22:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Laravel Observers.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abdallhsamy/introducing-laravel-observers-4a45</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abdallhsamy/introducing-laravel-observers-4a45"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T22:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laravel framework comes with lots of awesome features, the outstanding one for me is the model  observers.
According to the Laravel framework’s documentation:
If you are listening for many events on a given model, you may use observers to group all of your listeners into a single class. Observers classes have method names which reflect the Eloquent events you wish to listen for. Each of these methods receives the model as their only argument. The  make:observer  Artisan command is the easiest way to create a new observer class.
The observers helps me to declutter my controller of clean-up codes that I might have to run before or after making a model event, and also gives me a way to plug into the model’s event’s lifecycle and run any logic I might see fit.
The model events that can be obse…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdallah Samy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tiny Acquisitions]]></title>
        <id>https://tinyacquisitions.com</id>
        <link href="https://tinyacquisitions.com"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T22:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Blog with React, Strapi & GraphQL - Create Post & Display it in Frontend]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/semirteskeredzic/building-a-blog-with-react-strapi-graphql-create-post-display-it-in-frontend-3e19</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/semirteskeredzic/building-a-blog-with-react-strapi-graphql-create-post-display-it-in-frontend-3e19"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T21:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there, this is the second part of the mini series in Building an app with React, Strapi, and GraphQL. In the first part that you can find here, we went through first steps in prepping the backend and frontend for our app.
First of all, spin up your Strapi environment with the command in the terminal from the directory that houses Strapi:
$ yarn develop

This will start the Strapi server so you can now navigate to http://localhost:1337/admin/, once you are there enter the login data for the admin user. 
Content-Types Builder and this will bring you to the list of your content type so click Create Content Type.
BlogPost and press Continue, next you will be prompted to select a field for our content type:

For a proper Blog post we need following fields:
Title (Text - Short text)
Body (Te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semir Teskeredzic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile NixOS]]></title>
        <id>https://mobile.nixos.org/</id>
        <link href="https://mobile.nixos.org/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T21:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Absolute beginner's guide to Docker: What is a container?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/educative/absolute-beginner-s-guide-to-docker-what-is-a-container-lck</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/educative/absolute-beginner-s-guide-to-docker-what-is-a-container-lck"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T21:29:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is an open-source software platform that helps you simplify the process of creating, managing, running, and distributing your applications. With Docker, you can package your application along with all its dependencies into a container. Containers allow your applications to be deployed easily and uniformly.
Today, we’ll dive deeper into Docker and discuss containers, modules, key terms, and more.
We'll cover:
What is Docker?
Docker vs Kubernetes
Docker vocabulary guide
Installing Docker
What to learn next





Docker is an open-source software that runs on Linux and Windows. With Docker, you can package your application and its dependencies together into containers. Docker allows you to separate your applications from your infrastructure. 
The company started as a platform as a servi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Schaffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regular Expression in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thewebguyy/regular-expression-in-javascript-172k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thewebguyy/regular-expression-in-javascript-172k"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T21:27:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A regular expression is an object that describes a pattern of characters. Regular expressions are often abbreviated "regex" or "regexp".
The JavaScript RegExp class represents regular expressions, and both strings and RegExp define methods that use regular expressions to perform powerful pattern matching and search-and-replace functions on the text.
In simpler terms, a regular expression is a sequence of characters that forms a search pattern.
When you search for data in a text, you can use this search pattern to describe what you are searching for.
A regular expression can be a single character, or a more complicated pattern.
A regular expression can be defined as:
var pattern = new RegExp(pattern,attributes);
OR
var pattern = /pattern/attributes;

Using String Methods
In JavaScript, regu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AtoB (YC S20) – Stripe for Transportation – hiring early engineers and operators]]></title>
        <id>https://careers.atob.com/</id>
        <link href="https://careers.atob.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T21:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twilio, Asana to List on Long Term Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/articles/twilio-asana-to-list-on-long-term-stock-exchange-as-esg-push-continues-11624565701</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/twilio-asana-to-list-on-long-term-stock-exchange-as-esg-push-continues-11624565701"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T20:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use SOLID Principles To Become Better Automation Tester]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gusdmoreira/use-solid-principles-to-become-better-automation-tester-3kg9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gusdmoreira/use-solid-principles-to-become-better-automation-tester-3kg9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T20:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you using most recommended and fundamental SOLID principles in your automation?
Like any development work, automation also needs to be planned, designed, developed, maintained and extended over time. Your automation code or automation framework is an application which is testing your actual application. That’s why SOLID principles are highly recommend for your automation to make it easy to understand, use, maintain and extend over time. When SOLID principles are not applied, your automation might become fragile, hard to maintain and hard to extend very soon.
Even if you are using different programming language like C#, Python or automation tool like HP UFT/QTP for automation, you should definitely consider applying SOLID principles to make your automation tester life easy. Please note …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gusdmoreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick sort algorithm]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/quick-sort-algorithm-1k72</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/quick-sort-algorithm-1k72"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T20:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Definition of quicksort


Quicksort is a type of  Divide and Conquer algorithm like merge sort, it works by choosing an element as a pivot from the giving array, and appending the greater elements to the selected pivot, and shifting the smaller elements before it.
The space complexity of quicksort is O(log n)



best-case
average case
worst-case




O(n log n)
O(n log n)
O(n^2) when the list is already sorted, or the pivot is min or max value of the giving list




def QuickSortAlgorithm(arr: list) -> list:
    """
        [ name ] => Quick Sort
        [ type ] => Sorting algorithms
        [ time complexity ] => (
            1. best case:  O(n log n)
            2. average case: O(n log n)
            3. worst case: O(n^2) { when the pivot is the (min or max) value of the giving list, o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Bouchiha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop using your work laptop or phone for personal stuff, because I know you are]]></title>
        <id>https://www.zdnet.com/article/stop-using-your-work-laptop-or-phone-for-personal-stuff-because-i-know-you-are/</id>
        <link href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/stop-using-your-work-laptop-or-phone-for-personal-stuff-because-i-know-you-are/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T19:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I built my app in React, React Native and NextJS. Lessons learned.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ash_grover/i-built-my-app-in-react-react-native-and-nextjs-lessons-learned-3f38</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ash_grover/i-built-my-app-in-react-react-native-and-nextjs-lessons-learned-3f38"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T19:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I developed an offline-first personal Kanban app called Brisqi and launched it for 5 different platforms. I started this project with 2 purposes - to learn React and to build my own offline Kanban app as I always wanted one. I've been working on Brisqi since June last year.
ReactJS + BlueprintJS + custom styling for desktop app.
React Native + React Native elements + custom styling for Android/iOS App.
NextJS + BulmaCSS for the website.
Firebase Auth for authentication + Firestore for the database.
Google cloud functions - to handle backend operations.
Electron framework was the obvious choice to make it cross-platform as it has good eco-system around it so I went ahead with it as the underlying framework.
Start with Context API for state management if your app is small, learn how it works…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ash G</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crazy Clock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tindie.com/products/nsayer/crazy-clock/</id>
        <link href="https://www.tindie.com/products/nsayer/crazy-clock/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T19:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best React UI Component Libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mvmilanjain/best-react-ui-component-libraries-25ah</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mvmilanjain/best-react-ui-component-libraries-25ah"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T19:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Material UI


Material UI is a set of react components built based on the Material Design guidelines of Google.
Material UI consists of many accessible and configurable UI widgets.
The components are self-supporting and only inject the styles they need to display, which could lead to performance enhancements in your application.
Material UI has an active set of maintainers and a strong community behind it. It currently has over 69k stars on GitHub, making it one of the most popular component libraries out there.
If you’re looking to build a beautiful, consistent, and light interface quickly without sacrificing accessibility and performance, the material design will help you achieve that.
Chakra UI is a simple, modular and accessible component library that gives you the building blocks you …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Milan Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google turned me into a serial killer]]></title>
        <id>https://hristo-georgiev.com/google-turned-me-into-a-serial-killer</id>
        <link href="https://hristo-georgiev.com/google-turned-me-into-a-serial-killer"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T18:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fun and dystopia with AI-based code generation using GPT-J-6B]]></title>
        <id>https://minimaxir.com/2021/06/gpt-j-6b/</id>
        <link href="https://minimaxir.com/2021/06/gpt-j-6b/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:36:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cl-bodge: a cross-platform Common Lisp game and application framework]]></title>
        <id>https://borodust.org/projects/cl-bodge/</id>
        <link href="https://borodust.org/projects/cl-bodge/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Common React Mistakes You Might Be Making – And How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>60d3ee396e1a1407b6b0b6ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/common-react-mistakes-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go over the most common mistakes you might be making in your React code right now, plus how to fix them. If you want to create amazing React applications, it's essential to avoid many common errors along the way. In this article, we'll not only cover how to fix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quad9 and Sony Music: German Injunction Status]]></title>
        <id>https://quad9.net/news/blog/quad9-and-sony-music-german-injunction-status/</id>
        <link href="https://quad9.net/news/blog/quad9-and-sony-music-german-injunction-status/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Banning of Joyce's Ulysses]]></title>
        <id>https://crimereads.com/banned-books-ulysses-joyce-morris-ernst/</id>
        <link href="https://crimereads.com/banned-books-ulysses-joyce-morris-ernst/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use OpenTelemetry to Understand Software Performance]]></title>
        <id>60d4b5e96e1a1407b6b0bac4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opentelemetry/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want good performance in your application, you need to collect data to figure out where to make improvements. That's where OpenTelemetry comes in. OpenTelemetry offers a single set of APIs and libraries that standardize how you collect and transfer telemetry data. OpenTelemetry provides a specification for instrumentation so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing Games on Linux: An Interview with Little Red Dog Games]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.system76.com/post/654884924769370112/developing-games-on-linux-an-interview-with</id>
        <link href="https://blog.system76.com/post/654884924769370112/developing-games-on-linux-an-interview-with"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Backblaze Storage Pod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.backblaze.com/blog/next-backblaze-storage-pod/</id>
        <link href="https://www.backblaze.com/blog/next-backblaze-storage-pod/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is bringing Android apps to Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/24/22548428/microsoft-windows-11-android-apps-support-amazon-store</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/24/22548428/microsoft-windows-11-android-apps-support-amazon-store"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Micro APIs for Everyday Use]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.m3o.com/2021/06/24/micro-apis-for-everyday-use.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.m3o.com/2021/06/24/micro-apis-for-everyday-use.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/24/22546791/microsoft-windows-11-announcement-features-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/24/22546791/microsoft-windows-11-announcement-features-updates"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chapter 9: Community]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/chapter-9-community/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April of 2009, Yahoo! shut down GeoCities. Practically overnight, the once beloved service had its signup page replaced with a vague message announcing its closure.
We have decided to discontinue the process of allowing new customers to sign up 
…
The post Chapter 9: Community appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Hoffmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada: Hundreds of unmarked graves found at residential school]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-57592243</id>
        <link href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-57592243"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA can't figure out what's causing computer issues on the Hubble telescope]]></title>
        <id>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/23/1009567351/hubble-trouble-nasa-cant-figure-out-whats-causing-computer-issues-on-the-telesco</id>
        <link href="https://www.npr.org/2021/06/23/1009567351/hubble-trouble-nasa-cant-figure-out-whats-causing-computer-issues-on-the-telesco"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T13:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doesn’t Hurt To Ask Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6453</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/doesnt-hurt-to-ask-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=doesnt-hurt-to-ask-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T12:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Doesn’t Hurt To Ask explains how to become a master of persuasion by asking all of the right questions and teaches how intentional questions are the key to sharing your ideas, connecting with your audience, and convincing people of your way of thinking whether you’re in the office or at home. Read in: 4 […]
The post Doesn’t Hurt To Ask Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Thiel turned a Roth IRA into a $5B tax-free piggy bank]]></title>
        <id>https://www.propublica.org/article/lord-of-the-roths-how-tech-mogul-peter-thiel-turned-a-retirement-account-for-the-middle-class-into-a-5-billion-dollar-tax-free-piggy-bank</id>
        <link href="https://www.propublica.org/article/lord-of-the-roths-how-tech-mogul-peter-thiel-turned-a-retirement-account-for-the-middle-class-into-a-5-billion-dollar-tax-free-piggy-bank"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T11:20:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hospitals are selling troves of medical data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/23/22547397/medical-records-health-data-hospitals-research</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/23/22547397/medical-records-health-data-hospitals-research"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T10:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: 3dasd – open-source DIY room-scale 3D scanner]]></title>
        <id>https://3dasd.com/</id>
        <link href="https://3dasd.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T07:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Analysis? How to Visualize Data with Python, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib &amp; Seaborn Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>605abca5687d62084bf6b7cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploratory-data-analysis-with-numpy-pandas-matplotlib-seaborn/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T00:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis is the process of exploring, investigating, and gathering insights from data using statistical measures and visualizations.  The objective of data analysis is to develop an understanding of data by uncovering trends, relationships, and patterns. Data analysis is both a science and an art. On the one hand it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices Architecture – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>6072ffd4d5756f080ba98b27</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microservices-architecture-for-humans/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few years, microservices have gone from an overhyped buzzword to something you should understand as a software engineer.  According to an O'Reilly developer survey in 2020:  61% of companies have been using microservices in the last year29% say at least half of their company systems are built]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343076</id>
        <link href="https://www.bram.us/2021/06/21/tablesng-improvements-to-table-rendering-in-chromium/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I blogged “Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier” recently, I mentioned that the “stickiness” improvement was just one of the features that got better for <table>s in Chrome as part of the TablesNG upgrade…
The post TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342750</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-performant-next-gen-images-in-css-with-image-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS image-set() function has been supported in Chromium-based browsers since 2012 and in Safari since version 6. Support recently landed in Firefox 88. Let’s dive in and see what we can and can’t do today with image-set().…
The post Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a REST API with .NET 5 and  C#]]></title>
        <id>60d36eb66e1a1407b6b0b16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-rest-api-with-dot-net-5-and-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.NET is a popular software framework developed by Microsoft. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a REST API end-to-end from scratch using the latest .NET 5 innovations and Visual Studio Code. The course uses the C# programming language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Great Technical Course]]></title>
        <id>60a406bd906c5207e3a7dfcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-great-technical-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you will learn how to create a great technical video course. I run the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel where we post technical courses from a variety of contributors. Video courses that follow the guidelines in this article are often a good fit for freeCodeCamp's channel. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Weak declaration”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342669</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/weak-declaration/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T14:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PPK looks at aspect-ratio, a CSS property for layout that, for the most part, does exactly what you would think it does. It’s getting more interesting as it’s behind a flag in Firefox and Safari now, so we’ll have …
The post “Weak declaration” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parentheses Are Just Typechecking]]></title>
        <id>https://adam.nels.onl/blog/parentheses-are-just-typechecking/</id>
        <link href="https://adam.nels.onl/blog/parentheses-are-just-typechecking/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T12:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6450</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/open-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=open-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T12:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Open is the autobiography of world-famous tennis player Andre Agassi in which he details his struggles and successes on the way to self-awareness and balance while he was also trying to handle the constant pressures and difficulties that came from being one of the best tennis players in the world. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post Open Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The rich, weird, and frustrating world of Depression-era travel guides]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/06/new-deal-american-guides-federal-writers-project/619255/</id>
        <link href="https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/06/new-deal-american-guides-federal-writers-project/619255/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T11:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: support an experimental template for YouTube feed 📺 Demo | Source

Aggregate content from any YouTube channel rss url https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=<replace_with_channel_id>
Videos are embedded via iframe and loading accelerated by youtube-lite-embed
Ads are reduced thanks to YouTube's policy for embedded videos 🙃
Works on mobile devices with butter smooth horizontal scroll.
Caveat: the template works only with YouTube content. You cannot mix textual RSS feed or other video sources such as Vimeo.
Changed: Default HTML template meta tag adjusted to match convention
Changed: sources in template data is now ordered by last update timestamp (as opposed to alphabetical)
Thank you @PiyushLosalka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Don't Know, But Let's Try It]]></title>
        <id>http://bostonreview.net/class-inequality-politics-philosophy-religion/simon-torracinta-we-dont-know-lets-try-it</id>
        <link href="http://bostonreview.net/class-inequality-politics-philosophy-religion/simon-torracinta-we-dont-know-lets-try-it"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T04:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logical Fallacies – Definition and Fallacy Examples]]></title>
        <id>607f5fafdd38b9088c2bd0c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logical-fallacies-definition-fallacy-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T04:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're debating someone, you want to use all the resources at your disposal to convince them you're right. And that's great – but you should be careful that you don't end up using a logical fallacy to help you make your point. What is a Logical Fallacy?A logical fallacy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[inherit, initial, unset, revert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342930</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inherit-initial-unset-revert/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are four keywords that are valid values for any CSS property (see the title). Of those, day to day, I’d say I see the inherit used the most. Perhaps because it’s been around the longest (I think?) but also …
The post inherit, initial, unset, revert appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping with PHP – How to Crawl Web Pages Using Open Source Tools]]></title>
        <id>60d2323d6e1a1407b6b0ac4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-with-php-crawl-web-pages/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping lets you collect data from web pages across the internet. It's also called web crawling or web data extraction.  PHP is a widely used back-end scripting language for creating dynamic websites and web applications. And you can implement a web scraper using plain PHP code.  But since we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Async/Await to Write Better JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>60cac8ff4dc1a607ed7b4592</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-async-await-write-better-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a special syntax you can use in JavaScript that makes working with promises easier. It's called “async/await", and it’s surprisingly straightforward to understand and use.  In this article, we'll discuss:  What are asynchronus functions? How promises work in JavaScript Async/Await basics How to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript and MongoDB to Build a 100 Days of Code Discord Bot]]></title>
        <id>60c13e71d3126007592d5be2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-100-days-of-code-bot-for-discord-using-typescript-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 100 Days of Code challenge is very popular among new coders and developers looking to level up their skills. It's so popular that our Discord server has an entire channel dedicated to it.  By popular demand, we recently built a Discord bot that helps people track their progress in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Custom Elements in Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-custom-elements-in-svelte/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte fully supports custom elements (e.g. <my-component>) without any custom configuration or wrapper components and has a perfect score on Custom Elements Everywhere. However, there are still a few quirks you need to watch out for, especially around …
The post Using Custom Elements in Svelte appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Rich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342925</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/if-were-gonna-criticize-utility-class-frameworks-lets-be-fair-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not here to raise a shield protecting CSS utility frameworks. I don’t even particularly like the approach, myself, and nothing is above fair criticism. But fair is a key word there. I can’t tell you how many times I’ve …
The post If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyper-learning Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6432</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/hyper-learning-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hyper-learning-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Hyper-learning shows how people and companies can adapt in the rapidly changing world we live in today, explaining how a growth mindset, collaboration, and losing your ego will build your confidence that you can stay relevant and competitive as the world around you accelerates. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: If […]
The post Hyper-learning Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cupcake - A Rust library for lattice-based additive homomorphic encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/facebookresearch/Cupcake</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/facebookresearch/Cupcake"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T07:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smoothstep Integral]]></title>
        <id>https://iquilezles.org/www/articles/smoothstepintegral/smoothstepintegral.htm</id>
        <link href="https://iquilezles.org/www/articles/smoothstepintegral/smoothstepintegral.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T07:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342887</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/new-responsive/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una is calling it the new responsive. A nod to the era we were most certainly in, the era of responsive design. Where responsive design was fluid grids, flexible media, and media queries, the new responsive is those things …
The post Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342448</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-css-charts-with-interesting-shapes-glyphs-and-emoji/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s forego the usual circles and bars we typically see used in charts for more eccentric shapes. With online presentations more and more common today, a quick way to spruce up your web slides and make them stand out is …
The post How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billion Dollar Whale Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6397</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/billion-dollar-whale-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=billion-dollar-whale-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T12:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Billion Dollar Whale tells the incredible story of Jho Low, a Malaysian man who committed one of the biggest heists of the century by defrauding a national investment fund. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Wharton Business School is one of America’s highest-ranked business schools, and prospective students can expect an […]
The post Billion Dollar Whale Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341511</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-the-outline-property-as-a-collapsable-border/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T20:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outline property in CSS draws a line around the outside of an element. This is quite similar to the border property, the main exception being that outline isn’t a part of the box model. It is often used for …
The post Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carter Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342326</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-typography-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I studied the fonts of the top 1000 websites. Here’s what I learned. — Michael Li brings the data. San-serif has total dominance. “[…] it is rare to go below 10px or above 24px.” And poor <h5> always being the 
…
The post Links on Typography appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Be A Leader Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6396</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-be-a-leader-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-be-a-leader-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T12:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Be A Leader is Greek philosopher Plutarch’s guide to leadership and uses practical ideas, historical narratives, political events, and more to outline the qualities of the best leaders, including serving for the right reasons, speaking persuasively, and following more experienced leaders. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Ancient Roman […]
The post How To Be A Leader Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341948</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/perfect-tooltips-with-css-clipping-and-masking/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clipping and masking have been around for a while now in CSS and even have pretty decent browser support. I recently worked on a project that needed to use a clipping technique for tooltips showing above links in text.
Those …
The post Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Hoebregts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342257</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/start-serving-optimized-images-in-vue/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have become extremely important to the effectiveness of websites. They speak a 1000 words, attract attention, and stimulate emotions.
However, web performance is also a growing problem for most websites. And images are at the heart of many web …
The post Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageEngine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Towers Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6395</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/dark-towers-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dark-towers-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Dark Towers dives into the dirty inner workings and the rise and fall of Deutsche Bank, which contributed to many notable but not always beneficial events of the past 150 years, including the American railroad system, the Nazi regime, funding Russian oligarchs, and even the election of Donald Trump. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite […]
The post Dark Towers Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Styles as Classes (lol)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342358</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inline-styles-as-classes-lol/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re abhorred by using inline styles, just move that style to the class attribute! And then make sure you have CSS in place that, ya know, does what it says on the box. 
I've revolutionized CSS. pic.twitter.com/1AWCldyCwP
— Sam 

…
The post Inline Styles as Classes (lol) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful and Useless Code Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342630</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2021/useful-and-usless-code-comments/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T19:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Nielsen: 
If somebody says a comment isn’t adding any value, I would ask: to whom?
Personally, I’ve never liked the advice that writing obvious comments is bad practice—probably because I write obvious comments all the time.
Jim showed …
The post Useful and Useless Code Comments appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Order Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6394</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/beyond-order-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=beyond-order-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Beyond Order is the follow-up to Jordan Peterson’s bestselling book 12 Rules for Life and identifies another 12 rules to live by that help us live with and even embrace the chaos that we struggle with every day, identifying that too much order can be a problem just as much as too much disorder. […]
The post Beyond Order Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Escape Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6393</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-great-escape-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-great-escape-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Great Escape challenges the idea that the world is on fire by declaring that things have never been better in many ways, although the advancements we’ve made and the ways they have improved many lives haven’t reached everyone equally. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: If you were born in […]
The post The Great Escape Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long should you work on a problem ?]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19336</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/14/how-long-should-you-work-on-a-problem/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T21:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lev Reyzin says that working too long on a problem might be unproductive: I, personally, have diminishing (or negative?) returns to my creative work as I explicitly work on a problem past some amount of time. I often have insights coming to me out of nowhere while I’m relaxing or enjoying hobbies on nights or … Continue reading How long should you work on a problem ?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperfocus Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6392</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/hyperfocus-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hyperfocus-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Hyperfocus teaches you how to become more efficient and improve your concentration by deciding on one thing to work on, focusing only on that task, learning to understand when your mind has wandered and redirecting your attention back to your work, and thinking creatively when you’re not working. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post Hyperfocus Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (June 12th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19326</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/12/science-and-technology-links-june-12th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T16:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We completed the sequencing of the human genome. AstraZeneca’s drug Lynparza cut combined risk of recurrence of breast cancer or death by 42% among women in study. Glycine and N-acetylcysteine supplementation improves muscle strength and cognition. We found Egypt’s ancient capital. It has been lost of 3,400 years. It is unclear why it was abandoned. … Continue reading Science and Technology links (June 12th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Nations Fail Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6391</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/why-nations-fail-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=why-nations-fail-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Why Nations Fail dives into the reasons why economic inequality is so common in the world today and identifies that poor decisions of those in political power are the main reason for unfairness rather than culture, geography, climate, or any other factor. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Why do some […]
The post Why Nations Fail Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19312</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/03/computing-the-number-of-digits-of-an-integer-even-faster/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I my previous blog post, I documented how one might proceed to compute the number of digits of an integer quickly. E.g., given the integer 999, you want 3 but given the integer 1000, you want 4. It is effectively the integer logarithm in base 10. On computers, you can quickly compute the integer logarithm … Continue reading Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing the number of digits of an integer quickly]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19288</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/28/computing-the-number-of-digits-of-an-integer-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T19:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose I give you an integer. How many decimal digits would you need to write it out? The number ‘100’ takes 3 digits whereas the number ’99’ requires only two. You are effectively trying to compute the integer logarithm in base 10 of the number. I say ‘integer logarithm’ because you need to round up … Continue reading Computing the number of digits of an integer quickly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Powerful Responsive Websites With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19274</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/26/all-models-are-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T19:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong, but some are useful is a common saying in statistics. It does not merely apply to statistics, however. It is general observation. Box (1976) wrote an  influential article on the topic. He says that you make progress by successively making models followed by experiments, followed by more models, and then more … Continue reading All models are wrong]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>