<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-23T00:50:48.550Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-23T00:50:48.550Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Vaccination Game (Canvas API)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/claudiobonfati/the-vaccination-game-canvas-api-5b9j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/claudiobonfati/the-vaccination-game-canvas-api-5b9j"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T23:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I've worked on a project where I had to develop a small game alongside other components. But recently I've decided to isolate this game as a single stand-alone project since it was a good way to share a bit about canvas development and possibly introduce someone that Canvas API.
This article is intended to detail the development process of the game and some fundamentals of how to deal with Canvas API for similar projects.
First things first, you can take a look at the GitHub Project ⭐ or just play the game 🎮.
Before jumping into coding, we must have some things clear in mind, such as the concept of the game, the goal, how to win, and how to lose. If you have played it already, you've probably got it, but here is a quick overview:
The game consists of a population of 54 people se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Claudio Bonfati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The History Of JavaScript ⌛]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mr_victor/the-history-of-javascript-1fp3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mr_victor/the-history-of-javascript-1fp3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T23:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays JavaScript is everywhere 🌍
Hello 👋, Beautiful Coders on the internet 😃. In this article, I would share with you a quick yet comprehensive overview of how the most popular and widely used programming language in the world evolved to be what it is today.
Over the years JavaScript has become the most popular and versatile programming language. Powering over 97% of the web. As a web developer knowing the history of the most popular and in-demand programming language is a plus that will help enhance your understanding of the language.
Back in May 1995, the internet was becoming popular. The web back then was just static pages that were often text-heavy and ugly 😌.
the best ones had images floated to the left or right. Not exciting when you compare it to the web today 🤔
The Web nee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Ikechukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Selection sort algorithm]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/selection-sort-algorithm-5ke</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayabouchiha/selection-sort-algorithm-5ke"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T23:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Definition of selection sort


Selection sort is one of the simplest sorting algorithms, it works by continually finding the minimum number in the array and inserting it at the beginning.
The time complexity of selection sort is O(n2) and it's space complexity is O(1)
itertate from 0 to len(arr) - 1 
seting to minimunIdx variable the first element index in the unsorted part 
loop trough the unsorted part
if arr[j] < arr[minimumIdx]  => minimumIdx = j
swaping arr[minimumIdx] with the first in the unsorted part (unsortedPart[0])
def selectionSortAlgorithm(arr: list) -> list:
    """
        [ name ] => Selecion sort
        [ type ] => Sorting algorithms
        [ time complexity ] => O(n^2)
        [ space complexity ] => O(1)
        [ params ] => ( arr {list} array to sort )
        [ ret…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Bouchiha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rival weightlifter speaks out on transgender Hubbard's Olympic place]]></title>
        <id>https://www.insidethegames.biz/articles/1108399/anna-vanbellinghen-hubbard</id>
        <link href="https://www.insidethegames.biz/articles/1108399/anna-vanbellinghen-hubbard"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T22:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effects of cat ownership on the gut microbiota of owners]]></title>
        <id>https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0253133</id>
        <link href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0253133"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T22:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Another Gradient Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shadowfaxrodeo/not-another-gradient-generator-2mhl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shadowfaxrodeo/not-another-gradient-generator-2mhl"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T22:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is full of gradient generators. So I thought I'd make another one: Not Another Gradient Generator
It has some novel features though:
Generates linear, radial, and conic gradients.
Allows you to layer gradients to make complex designs.
Automatically adds colors to prevent gradients looking washed out.
Exports gradients as CSS, SVG, PNG, and JPEG.
I started this project with the goal of being able to replicate the instagram logo gradient in CSS. The instagram logo isn't a simple linear or radial gradient. It's complex and made by clever graphic designers using expensive software.
But CSS allows us to layer gradients on top of each other, by combining radial and linear gradients you can approximate the same thing:

This almost looks like it, the main issue is that it's all washed out.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathaniel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racing Game in ClojureScript]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ertugrulcetin/racing-game-cljs</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ertugrulcetin/racing-game-cljs"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T22:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Todo List with React and Sanity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joeholmes/how-to-create-a-todo-list-with-react-and-sanity-4dpg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joeholmes/how-to-create-a-todo-list-with-react-and-sanity-4dpg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T22:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sanity is often described as a "headless CMS"—a content management system decoupled from its presentation, allowing a developer to create any kind of frontend they desire.
But most "headless CMS" platforms are rather limited in what they can accomplish. They're usually designed to be blogs, e-commerce stores, or marketing pages—try and do something more avant-garde and you may soon find yourself in the weeds.
Not so with Sanity! With its thoughtful developer experience and lightning-fast APIs, Sanity can also compare favorably to "managed databases" such as Firebase and Supabase. Systems like these are designed for more complex, technical applications that require user authentication and dynamically presented data. Sanity can hold its own here!
Don't believe me? Let's build an app.
We'll b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Holmes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is ranked-choice voting and why is New York using it?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/22/1008807504/ranked-choice-voting-new-york-city-mayors-race</id>
        <link href="https://www.npr.org/2021/06/22/1008807504/ranked-choice-voting-new-york-city-mayors-race"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 reasons developers should use social media]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thevik/top-3-reasons-developers-should-use-social-media-1col</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thevik/top-3-reasons-developers-should-use-social-media-1col"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media has some great benefits for developers, in their careers and in connecting with their communities. This post kicks off a blog series that will describe the value I’ve gotten from social media and what I’ve learned about specific social media platforms, including tips for using each platform effectively.
Whether you’re looking to just keep in touch with other developers or wanting to build up your personal brand, today we’ll focus on “why social media?” Read on for my top three reasons why some time on social media is worth it for developers.
Social media helps you connect with people online around common interests, especially favorite or emerging technologies. It’s given me a sense of being part of other tech communities, beyond the people I interact with in my day-to-day job …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aditya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips for someone who wants to be a Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/krowser/tips-for-someone-who-wants-to-be-a-developer-19bd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/krowser/tips-for-someone-who-wants-to-be-a-developer-19bd"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plenty of companies are on the hunt for software developers. So, what are the secrets to software developer success?
If you want to be a software developer, you won’t be stuck for company choices. Many of the biggest companies are looking for software developers.
So, how exactly can you map out a successful career as a software developer? What do you need to know when you’re just starting out?
We gleaned a number of tips for someone who wants to be a software developer from those who have walked the path before.
Ronan O’Dulaing is the vice-president of engineering at Globoforce. He said a passion for problem-solving is critical to a successful career in software development. “You could start by practising coding simple programs every day,” he said.
“Pick problems to solve, perhaps related …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krowser Web Services</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[inherit, initial, unset, revert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342930</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inherit-initial-unset-revert/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are four keywords that are valid values for any CSS property (see the title). Of those, day to day, I’d say I see the inherit used the most. Perhaps because it’s been around the longest (I think?) but also …
The post inherit, initial, unset, revert appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atajos de Teclado (shortcuts) en Visual Studio Code.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gdcodev/atajos-de-teclado-shortcuts-en-visual-studio-code-427l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gdcodev/atajos-de-teclado-shortcuts-en-visual-studio-code-427l"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code actualmente en uno de los editores de código más utilizado, sobre todo entre los desarrolladores Web, nos permite programar en casi cualquier lenguaje. Tiene muchas características que lo hacen el editor de código favorito de muchos, ya que es muy personalizable, esto quiere decir que podemos adaptarlo a los gustos personales de cada uno.
Algo que puede ayudarte a ser mas rápido y ahorrar mas tiempo a la hora de moverte o escribir código en VSCode sin duda son los atajos de teclado. Ahora veremos en detalle algunos de ellos.



Acción
Atajo




Abrir paleta de comandos
Ctrl + Shift + P


Abrir archivo
Ctrl + P


Nueva ventana
Ctrl + Shift + N


Cerrar ventana
Ctrl + Shift + W


Ajustes del perfil
Ctrl + ,






Acción
Atajo




Crear un nuevo archivo
Ctrl + N


Abrir archivo
Ctrl + O


Guardar archivo
Ctrl + S


Cerrar
Ctrl + F4


Abrir Terminal
Ctrl + '


Panel de problemas
Ctrl + Shift + M






Acción
Atajo




Cortar linea
Ctrl + X


Copiar linea
Ctrl + C


Borrar linea
Ctrl + Shift + K


Insertar linea abajo
Enter


Insertar linea arriba
Ctrl + Shift + Enter


Buscar en archivo abierto
Ctrl + F


Reemplazar
Ctrl + H


Linea de comentario
Ctrl + /


Bloque de comentario
Shift + Alt + A


Salto de linea
Alt + Z


Seleccionar lineas
Alt + Click Mouse


Tabular linea
Tab


Destabular linea
Shift + Tab






Acción
Atajo




Acercar Zoom
Ctrl + +


Alejar Zoom
Ctrl + -


Barra lateral
Ctrl + B


Abrir debug
Ctrl + Shift + D


Panel de salida
Ctrl + Shift + U


Control de source
Ctrl + Shift + G


Acceder a extensiones
Ctrl + Shift + X


Abrir terminal integrado
Ctrl + Shift + Ñ



Mas sobre Visual Studio Code: https://code.visualstudio.com/shortcuts/keyboard-shortcuts-windows.pdf
📌 Mis Redes: Facebook | LinkedIn | GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gastón Danielsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Components, comunicação entre componentes (parte 5)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gabrieljm/web-components-comunicacao-entre-componentes-parte-5-ido</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gabrieljm/web-components-comunicacao-entre-componentes-parte-5-ido"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Essa é a quinta parte da série de tutoriais sobre Web Components, não deixe de ver as outras partes. Neste tutorial vamos ver um pouco mais sobre algumas abordagens de como podemos fazer uma comunicação entre nossos componentes.
Sim, já que todo componente que criamos se trata de um elemento HTML customizado, nós podemos ouvir e disparar eventos como qualquer outro elemento faz, além de adicionar eventos customizados também. Eventos serão a forma mais comum que terá para fazer a comunicação entre os elementos.
Caso você não sabia nós podemos disparar os eventos do HTML de forma programática, sem a necessidade de interações do usuário.
const clickEvent = new Event('click')

document.querySelector('button').dispatchEvent(clickEvent)

Com esse simples código você verá que o evento atrelado ao…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel José</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping with PHP – How to Crawl Web Pages Using Open Source Tools]]></title>
        <id>60d2323d6e1a1407b6b0ac4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-with-php-crawl-web-pages/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping lets you collect data from web pages across the internet. It's also called web crawling or web data extraction.  PHP is a widely used back-end scripting language for creating dynamic websites and web applications. And you can implement a web scraper using plain PHP code.  But since we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Storing Files in the Database Is Considered Bad Practice]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maximization/why-storing-files-in-the-database-is-considered-bad-practice-4a49</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maximization/why-storing-files-in-the-database-is-considered-bad-practice-4a49"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally published a day earlier at https://maximorlov.com/why-storing-files-database-bad-practice/
You're already storing structured data in the database, it seems only logical to store files in there as well.
So you look up how to save files in MongoDB (or PostgreSQL, MySQL, etc.), only to find out that storing files in the database is considered bad practice.
Other web developers are saying that you shouldn't store files in the database, and they'll frown upon you if you ask them how to.
But nobody tells you why...
Is it because it looks bad to have a very long base64 string in the database?
There has to be more to it than that.
By the end of this article, you'll find out why saving files in the database is considered a bad practice.
You will discover common downsides…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxim Orlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SafeButler (YC S17) Is Hiring a Marketing Associate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.safebutler.com/careers</id>
        <link href="https://www.safebutler.com/careers"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 4 Types of Activity timeouts in Temporal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/temporalio/the-4-types-of-activity-timeouts-in-temporal-1p69</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/temporalio/the-4-types-of-activity-timeouts-in-temporal-1p69"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T20:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One benefit of moving business logic to Temporal is how Temporal implements retries and timeouts for Activities in a standardized way. This has the effect of adding a reliability layer atop unreliable Activities and Workers, in a durable and scalable fashion. However, understanding the terminology can be a bit intimidating at first glance. 
This post (together with the embedded talk) aims to give you a solid mental model on what each Activity timeout does and when to use it.
Note: You can also set Workflow timeouts and retry policies you can set. This post deals only with Activity timeouts.
You can watch this 18 minute talk where our CEO Maxim Fateev explains the 4 Types of Activity timeouts you see in Temporal.




The rest of this post summarizes the main points covered in this whiteboar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>swyx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Being a developer at a startup is actually pretty great]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koan/being-a-developer-at-a-startup-is-actually-pretty-great-3n5m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koan/being-a-developer-at-a-startup-is-actually-pretty-great-3n5m"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T20:31:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re a developer who is looking for their next role and you are thinking about what kind of companies to talk to. One of the first decisions you have to make is whether to join a startup or a bigger, more established company. Here’s a quick case for startups:
The earlier you are joining the company, the higher the financial benefits can be. If the startup does well, your share options can be worth a lot of money. The people you’re going to work with are often very entrepreneurial and innovative (and since you’re reading this article, you probably are too). You can learn a lot being around other creators, sharing ideas, and discussing things openly. It’s a stark contrast to more corporate processes and environments.
It’s not all paperwork and sitting in meetings. At a startup “agile” is a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kaczmarczyk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Dangerous Censorship]]></title>
        <id>https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/on-censorship-pt-1</id>
        <link href="https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/on-censorship-pt-1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T19:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reply of the Zaporozhian Cossacks]]></title>
        <id>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reply_of_the_Zaporozhian_Cossacks</id>
        <link href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reply_of_the_Zaporozhian_Cossacks"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T18:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regularization is all you need: simple neural nets can excel on tabular data]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2106.11189</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2106.11189"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T18:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curiosity Damned the Cat]]></title>
        <id>https://edwardfeser.blogspot.com/2021/06/curiosity-damned-cat.html</id>
        <link href="https://edwardfeser.blogspot.com/2021/06/curiosity-damned-cat.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T17:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A from-scratch tour of Bitcoin in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://karpathy.github.io/2021/06/21/blockchain/</id>
        <link href="https://karpathy.github.io/2021/06/21/blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Async/Await to Write Better JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>60cac8ff4dc1a607ed7b4592</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-async-await-write-better-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a special syntax you can use in JavaScript that makes working with promises easier. It's called “async/await", and it’s surprisingly straightforward to understand and use.  In this article, we'll discuss:  What are asynchronus functions? How promises work in JavaScript Async/Await basics How to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript and MongoDB to Build a 100 Days of Code Discord Bot]]></title>
        <id>60c13e71d3126007592d5be2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-100-days-of-code-bot-for-discord-using-typescript-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 100 Days of Code challenge is very popular among new coders and developers looking to level up their skills. It's so popular that our Discord server has an entire channel dedicated to it.  By popular demand, we recently built a Discord bot that helps people track their progress in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python to Create a Visual Novel Game in 10 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>60cfff5a4dc1a607ed7b5e58</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-python-to-create-a-visual-novel/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have a story idea that you'd like to turn into a novel? How about adding visual appeal and interactivity to that novel?  A Visual Novel might be the game genre you are looking for. And this tutorial is here to help set you up in 10 minutes, with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Feeling guilty for doing the bare minimum at work]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27593462</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27593462"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs) v1.0 (W3C draft)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.w3.org/TR/did-core/</id>
        <link href="https://www.w3.org/TR/did-core/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brave Search beta]]></title>
        <id>https://search.brave.com/</id>
        <link href="https://search.brave.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Then – Understand how you spend your time and what influences your mood]]></title>
        <id>https://pupishi.com/then</id>
        <link href="https://pupishi.com/then"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T15:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I wrote a book about Python]]></title>
        <id>https://pragprog.com/titles/dmpython/intuitive-python/</id>
        <link href="https://pragprog.com/titles/dmpython/intuitive-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T15:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I made a new kind of Bible app]]></title>
        <id>https://sparkbible.com</id>
        <link href="https://sparkbible.com"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Custom Elements in Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-custom-elements-in-svelte/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte fully supports custom elements (e.g. <my-component>) without any custom configuration or wrapper components and has a perfect score on Custom Elements Everywhere. However, there are still a few quirks you need to watch out for, especially around …
The post Using Custom Elements in Svelte appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Rich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SiFive P550 Core: High-Performance RISC-V Processor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sifive.com/press/sifive-performance-p550-core-sets-new-standard-as-highest</id>
        <link href="https://www.sifive.com/press/sifive-performance-p550-core-sets-new-standard-as-highest"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342925</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/if-were-gonna-criticize-utility-class-frameworks-lets-be-fair-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not here to raise a shield protecting CSS utility frameworks. I don’t even particularly like the approach, myself, and nothing is above fair criticism. But fair is a key word there. I can’t tell you how many times I’ve …
The post If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSP bypass: How one Chrome XSS bug took 2.5 years and an HTML spec change to fix]]></title>
        <id>https://portswigger.net/daily-swig/csp-bypass-how-one-chrome-xss-bug-took-2-5-years-and-an-html-spec-change-to-fix</id>
        <link href="https://portswigger.net/daily-swig/csp-bypass-how-one-chrome-xss-bug-took-2-5-years-and-an-html-spec-change-to-fix"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T13:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyper-learning Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6432</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/hyper-learning-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hyper-learning-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Hyper-learning shows how people and companies can adapt in the rapidly changing world we live in today, explaining how a growth mindset, collaboration, and losing your ego will build your confidence that you can stay relevant and competitive as the world around you accelerates. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: If […]
The post Hyper-learning Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fasm, a F# to Jitted ASM/IL disassembler as a dotnet tool]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/d-edge/fasm</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/d-edge/fasm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T11:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elfcat: Visualize ELF Binaries]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ruslashev/elfcat</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ruslashev/elfcat"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T11:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attack Surface Analyzer helps you analyze your OS's security configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Microsoft/AttackSurfaceAnalyzer</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Microsoft/AttackSurfaceAnalyzer"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T10:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Inside the EU Green Pass QR Code?]]></title>
        <id>https://gir.st/blog/greenpass.html</id>
        <link href="https://gir.st/blog/greenpass.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T10:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pocketlang]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ThakeeNathees/pocketlang</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ThakeeNathees/pocketlang"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T07:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Exit Vim – Vim Save and Quit Command Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>60c81f774dc1a607ed7b2f66</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-exit-vim/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using Vim since the first year I started coding. For all the IDEs/editors that I have used, the Vim plugin is always the very first plugin that I install. I know that Vim can be challenging to work in for people who are not familiar with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List Methods – append( ) vs extend( ) in Python Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>60bce157acb62507dd1d9f11</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-methods-append-vs-extend/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with Python lists, you often need to combine data from multiple lists. So how do you do that? In this tutorial, we'll see the different ways you can combine data from multiple lists. We'll also learn how the list methods append() and extend() work through simple examples.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342887</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/new-responsive/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una is calling it the new responsive. A nod to the era we were most certainly in, the era of responsive design. Where responsive design was fluid grids, flexible media, and media queries, the new responsive is those things …
The post Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Redux by Making a Counter Application]]></title>
        <id>60cccd6e4dc1a607ed7b4f81</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-redux-by-making-a-counter-application/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux is a state management library for front end applications. Developers commonly use it with React through the react-redux package, but it can also stand alone – so you can use it in any front end framework or library, including Vanilla JavaScript.  Redux can really be intimidating at first. It might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Portfolio Website with React]]></title>
        <id>60d0d0ff6e1a1407b6b0a506</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-portfolio-website-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T18:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today you're going to create one of the most important apps you can build for yourself: your developer portfolio. Every React developer or web developer in general needs to be able to show off what they can do to any potential client or employer. That's exactly what we're going to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Figma? A Design Crash Course [2021 Tutorial]]]></title>
        <id>60cda7104dc1a607ed7b5588</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/figma-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T17:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma is a powerful design tool that helps you to create anything: websites, applications, logos, and much more. By learning to use Figma, you'll take your first steps into User Interface Design and and User Experience Design. These skills are essential for building a great portfolio for yourself and potentially]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Technical Guide to IPFS – the Decentralized Storage of Web3]]></title>
        <id>60a55b37906c5207e3a7ea78</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/technical-guide-to-ipfs-decentralized-storage-of-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But where do you store your application's content? Storing the content on the blockchain would be expensive and inefficient. Your blockchain application needs decentralized storage!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342448</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-css-charts-with-interesting-shapes-glyphs-and-emoji/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s forego the usual circles and bars we typically see used in charts for more eccentric shapes. With online presentations more and more common today, a quick way to spruce up your web slides and make them stand out is …
The post How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billion Dollar Whale Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6397</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/billion-dollar-whale-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=billion-dollar-whale-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T12:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Billion Dollar Whale tells the incredible story of Jho Low, a Malaysian man who committed one of the biggest heists of the century by defrauding a national investment fund. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Wharton Business School is one of America’s highest-ranked business schools, and prospective students can expect an […]
The post Billion Dollar Whale Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digitising Rural Land Records, One Drone at a Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/digitising-rural-land-records-one-drone-at-a-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/digitising-rural-land-records-one-drone-at-a-time"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T11:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Silence Barrier [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>http://www.arvindguptatoys.com/arvindgupta/jppsilencebarrier.pdf</id>
        <link href="http://www.arvindguptatoys.com/arvindgupta/jppsilencebarrier.pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T10:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My favourite C++ footgun]]></title>
        <id>https://dustri.org/b/my-favourite-c-footgun.html</id>
        <link href="https://dustri.org/b/my-favourite-c-footgun.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T09:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ML Beyond Curve Fitting: An Intro to Causal Inference and Do-Calculus (2018)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.inference.vc/untitled/</id>
        <link href="https://www.inference.vc/untitled/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T09:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crosby, Stills, Nash and Young’s lost album, Human Highway]]></title>
        <id>https://longreads.com/2021/03/30/crosby-stills-nash-youngs-lost-album-human-highway/</id>
        <link href="https://longreads.com/2021/03/30/crosby-stills-nash-youngs-lost-album-human-highway/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T03:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Browsers Decode Images Differently]]></title>
        <id>https://bien.ee/image-decoding-differences-between-browsers/</id>
        <link href="https://bien.ee/image-decoding-differences-between-browsers/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T21:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Turing's biggest fan remains the real enigma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.westword.com/news/alan-turing-enigma-british-codebreaker-homeland-security-colorado-11996659</id>
        <link href="https://www.westword.com/news/alan-turing-enigma-british-codebreaker-homeland-security-colorado-11996659"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T18:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341511</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-the-outline-property-as-a-collapsable-border/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T20:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outline property in CSS draws a line around the outside of an element. This is quite similar to the border property, the main exception being that outline isn’t a part of the box model. It is often used for …
The post Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carter Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342326</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-typography-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I studied the fonts of the top 1000 websites. Here’s what I learned. — Michael Li brings the data. San-serif has total dominance. “[…] it is rare to go below 10px or above 24px.” And poor <h5> always being the 
…
The post Links on Typography appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Be A Leader Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6396</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-be-a-leader-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-be-a-leader-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T12:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Be A Leader is Greek philosopher Plutarch’s guide to leadership and uses practical ideas, historical narratives, political events, and more to outline the qualities of the best leaders, including serving for the right reasons, speaking persuasively, and following more experienced leaders. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Ancient Roman […]
The post How To Be A Leader Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341948</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/perfect-tooltips-with-css-clipping-and-masking/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clipping and masking have been around for a while now in CSS and even have pretty decent browser support. I recently worked on a project that needed to use a clipping technique for tooltips showing above links in text.
Those …
The post Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Hoebregts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342257</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/start-serving-optimized-images-in-vue/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have become extremely important to the effectiveness of websites. They speak a 1000 words, attract attention, and stimulate emotions.
However, web performance is also a growing problem for most websites. And images are at the heart of many web …
The post Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageEngine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Towers Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6395</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/dark-towers-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dark-towers-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Dark Towers dives into the dirty inner workings and the rise and fall of Deutsche Bank, which contributed to many notable but not always beneficial events of the past 150 years, including the American railroad system, the Nazi regime, funding Russian oligarchs, and even the election of Donald Trump. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite […]
The post Dark Towers Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Styles as Classes (lol)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342358</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inline-styles-as-classes-lol/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re abhorred by using inline styles, just move that style to the class attribute! And then make sure you have CSS in place that, ya know, does what it says on the box. 
I've revolutionized CSS. pic.twitter.com/1AWCldyCwP
— Sam 

…
The post Inline Styles as Classes (lol) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful and Useless Code Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342630</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2021/useful-and-usless-code-comments/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T19:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Nielsen: 
If somebody says a comment isn’t adding any value, I would ask: to whom?
Personally, I’ve never liked the advice that writing obvious comments is bad practice—probably because I write obvious comments all the time.
Jim showed …
The post Useful and Useless Code Comments appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Used the WAAPI to Build an Animation Library]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342353</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-used-the-waapi-to-build-an-animation-library/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T14:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web Animations API lets us construct animations and control their playback with JavaScript. The API opens the browser’s animation engine to developers and was designed to underlie implementations of both CSS animations and transitions, leaving the door open to …
The post How I Used the WAAPI to Build an Animation Library appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okiki Ojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Order Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6394</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/beyond-order-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=beyond-order-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Beyond Order is the follow-up to Jordan Peterson’s bestselling book 12 Rules for Life and identifies another 12 rules to live by that help us live with and even embrace the chaos that we struggle with every day, identifying that too much order can be a problem just as much as too much disorder. […]
The post Beyond Order Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect Unused Classes in… HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342198</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/detect-unused-classes-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T23:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually, when “unused” comes up in conversation regarding CSS, it’s about removing chunks of CSS that are not used in your site or, at least, the styles not currently in use on a specific page. The minimal amount of CSS …
The post Detect Unused Classes in… HTML appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media Queries in Times of @container]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342519</id>
        <link href="https://mxb.dev/blog/media-queries-in-times-of-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T19:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max Böck took me up on my challenge to look through a codebase and see how many of the @media queries could ultimately become @container queries.
I took the bait and had a look at some of my projects – 
…
The post Media Queries in Times of @container appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just How Niche is Headless WordPress?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342248</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/just-how-niche-is-headless-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T14:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wonder where headless WordPress will land. And by “headless” I mean only using the WordPress admin and building out the user-facing site through the WordPress REST API rather than the traditional WordPress theme structure.
Is it… big? The future …
The post Just How Niche is Headless WordPress? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Escape Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6393</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-great-escape-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-great-escape-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T12:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Great Escape challenges the idea that the world is on fire by declaring that things have never been better in many ways, although the advancements we’ve made and the ways they have improved many lives haven’t reached everyone equally. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: If you were born in […]
The post The Great Escape Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long should you work on a problem ?]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19336</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/14/how-long-should-you-work-on-a-problem/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T21:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lev Reyzin says that working too long on a problem might be unproductive: I, personally, have diminishing (or negative?) returns to my creative work as I explicitly work on a problem past some amount of time. I often have insights coming to me out of nowhere while I’m relaxing or enjoying hobbies on nights or … Continue reading How long should you work on a problem ?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperfocus Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6392</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/hyperfocus-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hyperfocus-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Hyperfocus teaches you how to become more efficient and improve your concentration by deciding on one thing to work on, focusing only on that task, learning to understand when your mind has wandered and redirecting your attention back to your work, and thinking creatively when you’re not working. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post Hyperfocus Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (June 12th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19326</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/12/science-and-technology-links-june-12th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T16:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We completed the sequencing of the human genome. AstraZeneca’s drug Lynparza cut combined risk of recurrence of breast cancer or death by 42% among women in study. Glycine and N-acetylcysteine supplementation improves muscle strength and cognition. We found Egypt’s ancient capital. It has been lost of 3,400 years. It is unclear why it was abandoned. … Continue reading Science and Technology links (June 12th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Nations Fail Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6391</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/why-nations-fail-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=why-nations-fail-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Why Nations Fail dives into the reasons why economic inequality is so common in the world today and identifies that poor decisions of those in political power are the main reason for unfairness rather than culture, geography, climate, or any other factor. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: Why do some […]
The post Why Nations Fail Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Logo Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6390</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/no-logo-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=no-logo-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T12:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: No Logo uses four parts, including “No Space,” “No Choice,” “No Jobs,” and “No Logo,” to explain the growth of brand power since the 1980s, how the focus of companies on image rather than products has affected employees, and to identify those who fight against large corporations and their brands. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post No Logo Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Myth Of The Strong Leader Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6389</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-myth-of-the-strong-leader-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-myth-of-the-strong-leader-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T12:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Myth Of The Strong Leader reveals why being a bold, charismatic leader might not be all it’s cracked up to be even though people tend to think of good leaders in this light and explains how these individuals rise to power and some of the consequences of it happening on an international scale. […]
The post The Myth Of The Strong Leader Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19312</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/03/computing-the-number-of-digits-of-an-integer-even-faster/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I my previous blog post, I documented how one might proceed to compute the number of digits of an integer quickly. E.g., given the integer 999, you want 3 but given the integer 1000, you want 4. It is effectively the integer logarithm in base 10. On computers, you can quickly compute the integer logarithm … Continue reading Computing the number of digits of an integer even faster]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing the number of digits of an integer quickly]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19288</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/28/computing-the-number-of-digits-of-an-integer-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T19:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose I give you an integer. How many decimal digits would you need to write it out? The number ‘100’ takes 3 digits whereas the number ’99’ requires only two. You are effectively trying to compute the integer logarithm in base 10 of the number. I say ‘integer logarithm’ because you need to round up … Continue reading Computing the number of digits of an integer quickly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Powerful Responsive Websites With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19274</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/05/26/all-models-are-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T19:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All models are wrong, but some are useful is a common saying in statistics. It does not merely apply to statistics, however. It is general observation. Box (1976) wrote an  influential article on the topic. He says that you make progress by successively making models followed by experiments, followed by more models, and then more … Continue reading All models are wrong]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>