<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-07-22T01:00:21.957Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-07-22T01:00:21.957Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[setting up browser notification]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dev_hills/setting-up-browser-notification-4dib</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dev_hills/setting-up-browser-notification-4dib"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T23:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up browser notifications are in every way crucial in web application development....

most times we do need to pass valuable informations to application users in order to decide our next step.
The process of implementing web notifications is made so easy with the browser notification api...
//first of all we check if the browser supports notification
if(!window.Notification){
console.log("browser notification not supported")
// now we try to display a notification
const showNotification = () =>{
const title =" hey there man, how's it going ";
const options = {
    body:" would you like to recieve weekly updates from us",
    icon:"./assets/logo.png"
}
const notify = new Notification(title,options)

//optionally you could decide to clear the notification dialog after some time

setTimeout(()=>{
//now we check the permission status
if (Notification.permission === "granted")
//this basically runs if the user neither accepted nor denied the request
else if (Notification.permission !== "denied"){
console.log('permission denied');
and thats all you need to start implementing browser notifications in your web application...
note: web notifications only works on a secure https, something of this sort "file:///C:/Users/HILLARY/Notify.html" would not work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Chibuko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emmet: Writing code can be Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jdc1492/emmet-writing-code-can-be-easier-5ece</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jdc1492/emmet-writing-code-can-be-easier-5ece"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T23:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing code, it's easy to make mistakes. A misspelled word on occasion, forgetting a closing tag in an HTML file, The smallest of mistakes can be hidden once the application becomes large enough. Recently, I found out about a plug-in called emmet that seems like it could possibly cut down on lines of code that I would've normally typed out manually, resulting in less mistakes. So far it seems like a plug-in that I will be making great use of in the future. 
One cool thing emmet allows you to do is seen when writing out tags. If you wanted a simple pair of div brackets normally you'd type them out.
<div></div>

Using emmet you simply type out the word div, press enter and the result would be the same. 

Another great thing about emmet is that if you wanted to give the element or a class you can do that as well.
div#blach

would give us
<div id='blah'>
<div> 

Once again, less typing less chance of an error on your part. You can even to the same with a class as well.
div.blach

would give us
<div class='blah'>
<div> 

If you're familiar with CSS you may notice similarities in how one would tell emmet we want an id or class vs a CSS declaration of an id or a class as well. As stated before, I'm in the early stages of purposefully using emmet, so I'm learning it all as I go. I wanted to share what I've learned and maybe point other beginners in the right direction. Finding cool things like this keeps me at my computer and excited for what I may find next. Happy Coding!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FTC Votes Unanimously to Enforce Right to Repair]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wired.com/story/ftc-votes-to-enforce-right-to-repair/</id>
        <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/ftc-votes-to-enforce-right-to-repair/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T23:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 CSS Tricks to Improve Your Next Coding Project (Cheatsheet)]]></title>
        <id>60f55f3e66c61b07d458ee8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/10-css-tricks-for-your-next-coding-project/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T22:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cascading nature of CSS sometimes makes it tough to understand and use. Developers at all levels often struggle while trying to figure out how to use certain features, and you'll often find yourself googling or asking a colleague for help.  So when you're having issues dealing with CSS, don’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 HTML and CSS Projects For Your Portfolio]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codewell/6-html-and-css-projects-for-your-portfolio-3kbh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codewell/6-html-and-css-projects-for-your-portfolio-3kbh"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T22:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After speaking to seasoned developers, you will quickly realize that the best way to improve your portfolio is by building projects. It is probably the best way to get better, because along the way, you'll be facing challenges that will require research to solve, and that ultimately improves your skills. 
We've made a list of 6 HTML and CSS Projects you can practice on and include in your portfolio!
1- Waitlist Page
2- Multi-step Form
3- Fiber Landing Page
4- Spense Landing Page
5- Nested Comments
6- Remix Landing Page with Dark/Light Mode
1- Waitlist Page



You will learn:
CSS Transforms
Flex or Grid
Responsive design
2- Multi-step Form



You will learn:
Creating multi-step forms
Creating custom components 
Responsive design
3- Fiber Landing Page



You will learn:
Absolute positioning
Flex/Grid
Creating cards
4- Spense Landing Page



You will learn:
Absolute positioning
Flex/Grid
Creating cards
5- Nested Comments



You will learn:
Positioning
Created nested comments
6- Remix Landing Page with Dark/Light Mode



You will learn:
Creating dark and light mode pages
Work on a full sign up and onboarding process
Creating blog cards
Using variables and mixins to make your life easier
You can also see a walkthrough of Codewell's challenges on Youtube.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moemin Mamdouh 👨‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using VS Code Teams Toolkit Extension for Teams App Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/azure/using-vs-code-toolkit-for-teams-app-development-2o0g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/azure/using-vs-code-toolkit-for-teams-app-development-2o0g"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T22:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous posts related to the Microsoft Teams developer platform, I introduced a few of Teams app types and how to build your first tabs, bots, and message extensions. These tutorials instructed you to use App Studio for manual configurations and minimal local setup, to focus on familiarizing you with the cencept of Teams app features.
However, in this tutorial, I am showing another way to develop, using a newly introduced developer tool, called Teams Toolkit (Preview) for VS Code, which was created to help you build and deploy Teams apps with integrated identity, access to cloud storage, data from Microsoft Graph, and other services in Azure and M365. 
Before you begin, let's check if you have set up your working environment to develop on Teams. 
First, make sure if your Teams clien…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomomi Imura 🐱</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I just learned I only have months to live. This is what I want to say]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/07/21/magazine/i-just-learned-i-only-have-months-live-this-is-what-i-want-say/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/07/21/magazine/i-just-learned-i-only-have-months-live-this-is-what-i-want-say/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webdev & Research Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aidenybai/javascript-libraries-research-projects-4b0l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aidenybai/javascript-libraries-research-projects-4b0l"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plug: I work on Million.js: <1kb virtual DOM - it's fast!
This is a bit of a short post for me to share my thoughts about JavaScript libraries in research.
I've been working on various research projects for the past few years in high school, ranging from inventing practical methods of reducing microplastic pollution to creating fully fledged JavaScript libraries and presenting at ISEF.
From this experience, I've found that many web/JavaScript related research projects are subpar -- in fact, the entire web development field is downright untapped. Most research projects are unfinished, outdated, and so unpractical it has no use in real life.
Web development needs a lot of improvement in the research space. This allows other researchers to gain insight into new technologies -- in my case, JavaScript libraries. We need more representation to explore more interesting topics, like WASM, compiler-based frameworks, and worker-based libraries.
So... what should you take away from this? Well, if you have a substantial, practical, and useful library in the web development space, develop a research project in parallel to contribute to the great world of science.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aiden Bai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How are salaries for senior devs in Berlin at the moment?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27912487</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27912487"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:33:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Use EditorConfig to Standardize Code Styles]]></title>
        <id>60f5ecb966c61b07d458f479</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-editorconfig-to-standardize-code-styles/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You use EditorConfig to define formatting conventions for textual files in a project. It's great because it's widely supported, and it's not tied to any particular language, framework, or code editor. EditorConfig on its own is just a vendor-agnostic configuration file. It relies on third-party tools or integrations to implement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AugLy On Image, Video, Audio, and Text?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aarora4/how-to-use-augly-on-image-video-audio-and-text-3m57</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aarora4/how-to-use-augly-on-image-video-audio-and-text-3m57"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read the full article here: https://analyticsarora.com/how-to-use-augly-on-image-video-audio-and-text/
Introduction to Data Augmentation
Facebook just recently released the AugLy package to the public domain. In this article, we will take a dive into the package. Just before data however, let's take some time to understand what data augmentation is about. 
Many coding examples are shown below. You can view the complete notebook on Github. 
Article Overview
What is data augmentation?
About AugLy
How AugLy Works
Why AugLy
Image Data Augmentation
Textual Data Augmentation
Audio Data Augmentation
Video Data Augmentation
About AugLy
AugLy is a recently released open source project in python that can be used for data augmentation. The aim is to help AI models have an improved robustness during t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avi Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airbnb raises violent crime rates in cities as residents are pushed out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.euronews.com/next/2021/07/15/airbnb-raises-violent-crime-rates-in-cities-as-long-term-residents-are-pushed-out-says-us-</id>
        <link href="https://www.euronews.com/next/2021/07/15/airbnb-raises-violent-crime-rates-in-cities-as-long-term-residents-are-pushed-out-says-us-"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEV Community: Ableist Language & Maintaining an Inclusive Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devteam/dev-community-ableist-language-maintaining-an-inclusive-environment-37g3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devteam/dev-community-ableist-language-maintaining-an-inclusive-environment-37g3"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello DEV Community! 👋
In recent months, you have probably seen a few posts from the DEV Community Success team — posts like this one on avoiding plagiarism from @itscasey
 and this one by yours truly from a few months back about the various community moderation roles and duties within our community as well as an overall framing of our Code of Conduct.  
The goal of these posts is to equip you with more context about the decisions we make collectively as moderators/community managers. We hope that showing you all a bit of our thought process and talking about the specific ways that we strive to create a positive environment will be enlightening and encouraging, giving you folks a clear window to better understand how we go about building a kind and inclusive community.
This post is no exc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Tharrington (he/him)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yet Another Mobile Context Menu With No Indication it Can Scroll]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344950</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/yet-another-mobile-context-menu-with-no-indication-it-can-scroll/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember Tyler Hall’s personal story of a UX moment where the popup sharing context menu on iOS had no visible indication that the content inside was scrollable? The thing his mom wanted to do seemed impossible iOS isn’t alone here …
The post Yet Another Mobile Context Menu With No Indication it Can Scroll appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECMAScript proposal: JSON modules]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344948</id>
        <link href="https://2ality.com/2021/06/json-modules.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Axel Rauschmayer looks at JSON modules, which is already live in Chrome 91 (but nothing else). It looks just like an ES Modules-style import, only you asset the type at the end. 
import configData from './config-data.json' assert {type: 
…
The post ECMAScript proposal: JSON modules appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the IBM PC Won, Then Lost, the Personal Computer Market]]></title>
        <id>https://spectrum.ieee.org/tech-history/silicon-revolution/how-the-ibm-pc-won-then-lost-the-personal-computer-market</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/tech-history/silicon-revolution/how-the-ibm-pc-won-then-lost-the-personal-computer-market"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is about:blank? Chrome Blank Homepage Guide]]></title>
        <id>60f81c021d2b080797b80d44</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-about-blank-chrome-blank-homepage-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might have heard of about:blank but don't understand what it is. Or you've seen it appear when you first load up a fresh new session in the Chrome browser – just an empty white page with about:blank showing in your address bar.  You might even see it when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dover (YC S19) just raised $20m and is hiring our first Engineering Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.dover.com/open-roles/engineering-manager</id>
        <link href="https://www.dover.com/open-roles/engineering-manager"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T21:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time and Date with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lukecp5/time-and-date-with-javascript-224f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lukecp5/time-and-date-with-javascript-224f"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T20:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This section is all about the best JavaScript libraries for handling date and time. These libraries are used to simplify and handle the complexity of dates and times in JavaScript. There are many advantages to using these JavaScript libraries which include the fact that they can help you with parsing, formatting, and setting a wide variety of date/time formats.
The most popular JavaScript library for handling date and time is Moment.js. Other libraries for handling date/time include:
-date-fns - this library provides you with a large amount of functions for working with dates
-moment - this library has been deprecated but it still remains one of the most popular
-datejs - this library provides you with a simple interface to work with dates
—
Dates and times are essential in a variety of fields. JavaScript has a lot of libraries to help programmers handle these two concepts better.
The JSS date library is the most popular one used for date handling. It is open-source and provides a lot of options for developers who need it. The library provides methods for parsing, formatting, manipulating, and generating dates, as well as handling time zones and calendars.
This JSS library can be used with other JavaScript frameworks like Angular, React or Vue just by including the library with the respective framework package manager (NPM or Yarn).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lukecp5</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Electron.js architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/logrocket/advanced-electron-js-architecture-cj6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/logrocket/advanced-electron-js-architecture-cj6"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T20:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Written by Alain Perkaz ✏️
A while back, I began working on a side project called taggr, a completely offline, interactive photo exploration app. Developing taggr required me to navigate up from the lowest level of app complexity, trying out multiple architectural approaches and exploring the limitations of each.
In this article, we’ll discuss the trade-offs of different architectural approaches for building desktop applications with Electron. We’ll analyze the shortcomings of each and introduce an architecture that aims to tackle them.
The blueprint presented in this article is the outcome of an ongoing effort to find an approach that enables me, a solo developer, to manage the complexity of the app and meet performance requirements by leveraging standard web tooling. Let’s dive in!
Note:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Angelosanto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Vs React – The Right Pick For Your Next Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gravelsoft/angular-vs-react-the-right-pick-for-your-next-project-25he</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gravelsoft/angular-vs-react-the-right-pick-for-your-next-project-25he"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T20:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript structures are very common in the advancement commercial center. Such systems are stages which give constructions of utilization plan to creating web applications dependent on JavaScript. 
Then again, the JavaScript libraries are an assortment of capacities and segments that a designer can use to insert in the code. 
A Framework can be an assortment of JavaScript Libraries which give a predefined code to be utilized while creating projects.Since JavaScript is the most every now and again utilized programming language for fostering a site, with not a single other tough substitution to be seen, the structures worked to help these web applications are likewise a significant number. 
A large portion of the significant endeavors managing web administrations have fostered their own al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GravelSoft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add content recommendations to website]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fischerbach/how-to-add-content-recommendations-to-website-365</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fischerbach/how-to-add-content-recommendations-to-website-365"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T20:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to add content recommendations to website



  
  
  Show users what they want (even though they don’t even know what they want)



Personalized content proposals are now an established element of the Web. Most social media serve content to their users based on multiple touchpoints of the user’s interaction with the platform. (Some of them also track the user outside their pages, which has caused a whole discussion about privacy and blocking cross-domain tracking.) Usually, the aim is to increase some interaction rate (i.e. measured by the number of visits, purchases or other actions per user).

Online shops increase their revenue with clever recommendations of products that appear at every stage of the sales funnel. But non-retail sites can also benefit from the advantages of recommender systems. If you run a website that provides content, you can use content recommendations to maintain user attention and increase visits.
In this article, using an example of a movie database web site, I’ll show you how to add content recommendations to your website. We’ll discuss basic approaches to this and then use a SaaS called Pipeless, which allows you to create a database with built-in recommendation algorithms.
Read More:
https://levelup.gitconnected.com/how-to-add-content-recommendations-to-a-website-be107c336117]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fischerbach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What redesigning our product taught us about optimizing video call performance in React]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/trydaily/what-redesigning-our-product-taught-us-about-optimizing-video-call-performance-in-react-4hl1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/trydaily/what-redesigning-our-product-taught-us-about-optimizing-video-call-performance-in-react-4hl1"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T20:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, one of Daily’s front-end engineers, Christian Stuff, internally shared several performance improvement tips he discovered while working on Daily Prebuilt. The following discussion is based on that list.
One of our primary goals at Daily is to help our customers embed reliable and easy-to-use video calls into their apps in the shortest developer time possible. One way we’ve found to do this is by offering Daily Prebuilt. 
Daily Prebuilt is Daily's ready-to-use, embeddable video chat that can be added to any app with just a few lines of code. This is in comparison to our call object option, which enables customers to build their own custom video calls with our core APIs. 
Basically, if Daily Prebuilt is your favourite meal served at a restaurant, Daily's customizable call object is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Mitchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man Arrested in Connection with Alleged Role in Twitter Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/man-arrested-connection-alleged-role-twitter-hack</id>
        <link href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/man-arrested-connection-alleged-role-twitter-hack"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T18:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why aren't there more programming-language startups?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.akitasoftware.com/blog-posts/why-arent-there-more-programming-languages-startups</id>
        <link href="https://www.akitasoftware.com/blog-posts/why-arent-there-more-programming-languages-startups"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T18:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost world revealed by human, Neanderthal relics washed up on North Sea beaches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/01/relics-washed-beaches-reveal-lost-world-beneath-north-sea</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/01/relics-washed-beaches-reveal-lost-world-beneath-north-sea"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T17:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Low-Code Tutorial – Build 3 Financial Apps]]></title>
        <id>60f83b421d2b080797b80f10</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/low-code-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T15:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low-Code can allow you to spin up apps fast and with out-of-the-box UI components. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about Low-Code solutions by building 3 financial apps.  Ania Kubów developed this course. She is a ex-financial Broker turned software developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Context for Beginners – The Complete Guide (2021)]]></title>
        <id>60f7eeda1d2b080797b80b31</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-context-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T15:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React context is an essential tool for every React developer to know. I lets you easily share state in your applications. In this comprehensive guide, we will cover what React context is, how to use it, when and when not to use context, and lots more. Even if you've never]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Twitter thread sparked a lawsuit against Nieman Lab’s founder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cjr.org/opinion/nieman-lab-lawsuit-joshua-benton-francesca-viola.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.cjr.org/opinion/nieman-lab-lawsuit-joshua-benton-francesca-viola.php"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T15:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bezos donates $100M each to CNN contributor Van Jones and chef Jose Andres]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/20/media/van-jones-bezos-100-million/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/20/media/van-jones-bezos-100-million/index.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T15:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Freelance Developer Portfolios to Inspire You]]></title>
        <id>60f5c9b866c61b07d458f2af</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/13-awesome-freelance-developer-portfolios/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T15:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article by @study_web_dev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Background Image – With HTML Example Code]]></title>
        <id>60f66b6f66c61b07d458f93c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-background-image-with-html-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T15:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a user sees on a website will impact how good their user experience is. It will also affect how easily they can use the whole site in general.  Adding images to the background of certain parts of a website is often more visually appealing and interesting than just changing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planning and estimating large-scale software projects]]></title>
        <id>https://tomrussell.co.uk/writing/2021/07/19/estimating-large-scale-software-projects.html</id>
        <link href="https://tomrussell.co.uk/writing/2021/07/19/estimating-large-scale-software-projects.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T14:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Step-By-Step Process for Turning Designs Into Code]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344337</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-step-by-step-process-for-turning-designs-into-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T14:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turning website design files into a combination of HTML, CSS and JavaScript is the bread and butter of many front-end web development jobs, but there’s a part of this work that doesn’t neatly fit in to tutorials on any specific …
The post A Step-By-Step Process for Turning Designs Into Code appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Noonan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Epsilon3 (YC S21) – Software for spacecraft and complex operations]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27906787</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27906787"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T14:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I built my first serverless robot and won $1000]]></title>
        <id>https://towardsdev.com/how-i-built-my-first-serverless-robot-and-won-200-87127a0b108c</id>
        <link href="https://towardsdev.com/how-i-built-my-first-serverless-robot-and-won-200-87127a0b108c"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T14:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Digger.dev – A PaaS that generates Terraform, in your AWS account]]></title>
        <id>https://diggerdev.com</id>
        <link href="https://diggerdev.com"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caffeine and theanine exert opposite effects on attention (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28044450/</id>
        <link href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28044450/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBEdit 14]]></title>
        <id>https://www.barebones.com/products/bbedit/bbedit14.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.barebones.com/products/bbedit/bbedit14.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/color-tools-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? We’ve collected some useful color tools and resources that we’ve discovered lately — to help you get the most out of your creativity. We’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [accessible front-end components](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/complete-guide-accessible-front-end-components/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using WebAssembly threads from C, C++ and Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://web.dev/webassembly-threads/</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/webassembly-threads/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T12:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do Chrome extensions impact browser performance?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.debugbear.com/blog/chrome-extension-performance-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.debugbear.com/blog/chrome-extension-performance-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T12:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fail Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6656</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-fail-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-fail-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T12:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Fail shows the surprising benefits of going through a difficult time through the experiences of the author, Elizabeth Day, including the failures in her life that she’s grateful for and how they’ve helped her grow, uncovering why we shouldn’t be so afraid of failure but instead embrace it. Read in: 4 minutes […]
The post How To Fail Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS now allows customers to pay for their usage in advance]]></title>
        <id>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2021/07/aws-allows-customers-pay-their-usage-in-advance/</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2021/07/aws-allows-customers-pay-their-usage-in-advance/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T10:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish police seize large drone used to carry drugs from Morocco]]></title>
        <id>https://english.elpais.com/spain/2021-07-15/spanish-police-seize-large-drone-used-to-carry-drugs-from-morocco.html</id>
        <link href="https://english.elpais.com/spain/2021-07-15/spanish-police-seize-large-drone-used-to-carry-drugs-from-morocco.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T10:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is our generation's Multics]]></title>
        <id>http://www.oilshell.org/blog/2021/07/blog-backlog-2.html</id>
        <link href="http://www.oilshell.org/blog/2021/07/blog-backlog-2.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T08:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary Trees are optimal except when they’re not]]></title>
        <id>https://hbfs.wordpress.com/2021/07/20/binary-trees-are-optimal-except-when-theyre-not/</id>
        <link href="https://hbfs.wordpress.com/2021/07/20/binary-trees-are-optimal-except-when-theyre-not/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T07:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Distribution for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://software.intel.com/content/www/us/en/develop/tools/oneapi/components/distribution-for-python.html</id>
        <link href="https://software.intel.com/content/www/us/en/develop/tools/oneapi/components/distribution-for-python.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T06:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Change Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6655</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/how-to-change-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-to-change-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T06:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: How To Change by Katy Milkman identifies the stumbling blocks that are in your way of reaching your goals and improving yourself and the research-backed ways to get over them, including how to beat some of the worst productivity and life problems like procrastination, laziness, and much more. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote […]
The post How To Change Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programmatic Video Editing with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Zulko/moviepy</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Zulko/moviepy"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T05:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching Tech Together]]></title>
        <id>https://teachtogether.tech/en/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://teachtogether.tech/en/index.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T04:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Information Sovereignty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lrb.co.uk/blog/2021/july/information-sovereignty</id>
        <link href="https://www.lrb.co.uk/blog/2021/july/information-sovereignty"/>
        <updated>2021-07-21T01:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting 'Steinached' was all the rage in Roaring ’20s (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mcgill.ca/oss/article/health-history-science-science-everywhere/getting-steinached-was-all-rage-roaring-20s</id>
        <link href="https://www.mcgill.ca/oss/article/health-history-science-science-everywhere/getting-steinached-was-all-rage-roaring-20s"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T23:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Nine States of Design]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=345062</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/swlh/the-nine-states-of-design-5bfe9b3d6d85"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T23:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a really good ol’ post from way back in 2015 all about the nine states of design and how we should think all the edge cases whenever we’re building interfaces. Vince Speelman writes:
Modern UI teams are designing components 
…
The post The Nine States of Design appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Underline Text – How to Use the &lt;u&gt; Tag with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>605301d528094f59be257c67</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-underline-text-how-to-use-the-u-tag-with-example-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T22:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to learn about the <u> tag and when it is appropriate to use it in HTML 5.  In older versions of HTML, you'd use this tag as a way to underline text. We are going to learn about the new HTML 5]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The undiscovered country: Can suicide be predicted?]]></title>
        <id>https://harpers.org/archive/2021/08/the-undiscovered-country-death-by-suicide-prediction-suicidology/</id>
        <link href="https://harpers.org/archive/2021/08/the-undiscovered-country-death-by-suicide-prediction-suicidology/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T22:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming VS Coding VS Development – What&#x27;s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>60f2dbac66c61b07d458e5c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-coding-developement-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T20:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my very early days as a budding web developer, I made a fairly common mistake. On Facebook, I sent a friend request to a senior software engineer (I wasn't aware of his position at the time) and started a chat with him thereafter. Done with greetings and pleasantries, I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344944</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T20:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric doesn’t mince words, especially in the title, but also in the conclusion:
In modern web design and development, displaying an image is a highly intentional act. Alternate descriptions allow us to explain the content of the image, and in 
…
The post Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Scale a System With Process Splitting and Redis]]></title>
        <id>60ed44c866c61b07d458d023</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scale-system-split-processes/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T19:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever gotten into trouble trying to handle a single process that's really huge or heavy? If so, I can help you figure out how to better manage it. In this article I will be sharing how I'm currently managing a single message that is too big to be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typewriter Animation That Handles Anything You Throw at It]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344497</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/typewriter-animation-that-handles-anything-you-throw-at-it/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T15:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I watched Kevin Powell’s video where he was able to recreate a nice typewriter-like animation using CSS. It’s neat and you should definitely check it out because there are bonafide CSS tricks in there. I’m sure you’ve seen other CSS …
The post Typewriter Animation That Handles Anything You Throw at It appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuzaali Surti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From WordPress To A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/wordpress-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-20T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will look at when it makes sense to migrate from a monolithic project to a headless setup and the benefits that come with it. In addition to a step-by-step guide on how to migrate WordPress to Storyblok Headless CMS, the problems that will arise during the process and how to deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A collection of outlandish human-computer interaction papers]]></title>
        <id>https://floe.butterbrot.org/matrix/rants/weird/</id>
        <link href="https://floe.butterbrot.org/matrix/rants/weird/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T21:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Images are hard.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344404</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/images-are-hard/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T20:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Putting images on websites is incredibly simple, yes? Actually, yes, it is. You use <img and link it to a valid source in the src attribute and you’re done. Except that there are (counts fingers) 927 things you could (and …
The post Images are hard. appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Use Cases for Scroll-Linked Animations in CSS with Scroll Timelines]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343893</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/practical-use-cases-for-scroll-linked-animations-in-css-with-scroll-timelines/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T14:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Scroll-Linked Animations specification is an upcoming and experimental addition to CSS. Thanks to the @scroll-timeline at-rule and animation-timeline property this specification provides, you can control the time position of regular CSS Animations by scrolling.
In this post, we’ll take …
The post Practical Use Cases for Scroll-Linked Animations in CSS with Scroll Timelines appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bramus Van Damme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Stopping Time Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6638</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-art-of-stopping-time-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-art-of-stopping-time-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T12:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Art of Stopping Time teaches a framework of mindfulness, philosophy, and time-management you can use to achieve Time Prosperity, which is having plenty of time to reach your dreams without overwhelm, tumult, or constriction. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: What would you say if I asked you what the […]
The post The Art Of Stopping Time Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining End-To-End Quality With Visual Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/maintaining-end-to-end-quality-visual-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding visual elements to your tests, you can gain more options to add meaningful ways in maintaining a high level of quality for your app. Colby Fayock explains how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Colby Fayock)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Admin Warnings in the Block Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344217</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wordpress-admin-warnings-in-the-block-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T20:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We sent out an email the other week that ultimately had a <video> in the HTML markup. We send the newsletter by creating it here in the WordPress block editor, which is fetched through RSS-to-Mailchimp. Mailchimp dutifully sent it out, …
The post WordPress Admin Warnings in the Block Editor appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Of Course We Can Make a CSS-Only Clock That Tells the Current Time!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344147</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/of-course-we-can-make-a-css-only-clock-that-tells-the-current-time/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T14:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a fully functioning and settable “analog” clock with CSS custom properties and the calc() function. Then we’ll convert it into a “digital” clock as well. All this with no JavaScript!
Here’s a quick look at the clocks …
The post Of Course We Can Make a CSS-Only Clock That Tells the Current Time! appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mate Marschalko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Typography Links]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344411</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-typography-links-3/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T14:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glitter text — whO (I learned a name for people who go by a one-word moniker like that: Mononymous) created a builder for fancy SVG-based type. It’s a custom font with <text>, and the fancy comes in with a 
…
The post Some Typography Links appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Insights I Gained While Researching Vue.js Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/three-insights-vuejs-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web app accessibility appears difficult because it seems that there is little information on the subject available online. Let’s take a closer look at the accessible use of framework features, concrete Vue.js traits, as well as community initiatives and vetted patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are You Doing With Your Life Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6595</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/what-are-you-doing-with-your-life-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=what-are-you-doing-with-your-life-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-16T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: What Are You Doing With Your Life is a book by the great philosopher and teacher Jiddu Krishnamurti, who turns traditional ideas about happiness and the purpose of life on its head by diving into the details of life’s most important questions so you can live with intention and joy more consistently. Read in: […]
The post What Are You Doing With Your Life Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get a Pixel-Perfect, Linearly Scaled UI]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344273</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-get-a-pixel-perfect-linearly-scaled-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamically scaling CSS values based on the viewport width is hardly a new topic. You can find plenty of in-depth coverage right here on CSS-Tricks in articles like this one or this one.
Most of those examples, though, use …
The post How to Get a Pixel-Perfect, Linearly Scaled UI appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgi Nikoloff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISR vs DPR: Big Words, Quick Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/isr-dpr-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two strategies for incrementally building websites that are growing in popularity: Incremental Static Regeneration and Distributed Persistent Rendering. What’s the difference? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cassidy Williams)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Do That With A JavaScript Data Grid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/javascript-data-grid-kendo-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll get to see some pretty groundbreaking things you can achieve with modern JavaScript grids and discover new ways to augment a data grid to make it engaging, responsive, and accessible. All this will be illustrated using Kendo UI Data Grids and their features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Way Of Integrity Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6594</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-way-of-integrity-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-way-of-integrity-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T12:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Way Of Integrity uses science, spirituality, humor, and Dante’s Divine Comedy to teach you how to find well-being, healing, a sense of purpose, and much more by rediscovering integrity, or the recently lost art of living true to yourself by what you do, think and say. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from […]
The post The Way Of Integrity Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19380</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/14/faster-sorted-array-unions-by-reducing-branches/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing an index, a database or a search engine, you frequently need to compute the union of two sorted sets. When I am not using fancy low-level instructions, I have most commonly computed the union of two sorted sets using the following approach: v1 = first value in input 1 v2 = first value … Continue reading Faster sorted array unions by reducing branches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Complex CSS Transitions using Custom Properties and cubic-bezier()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344249</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/build-complex-css-transitions-using-custom-properties-and-cubic-bezier/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T14:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently illustrated how we can achieve complex CSS animations using cubic-bezier() and how to do the same when it comes to CSS transitions. I was able to create complex hover effect without resorting to keyframes. In this article, I …
The post Build Complex CSS Transitions using Custom Properties and cubic-bezier() appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bashful Button Worth $8 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344407</id>
        <link href="https://cloudfour.com/thinks/a-bashful-button-worth-8-million/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T14:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us grumble when running across a frustrating UX experience online (like not being able to complete a transaction because of a misplaced button). We might pen a whiny tweet. Jason Grigsby is like I’m going to write 2,000 …
The post A Bashful Button Worth $8 Million appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Broken Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frustrating-design-patterns-broken-frozen-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Too often dealing with filters can be frustrating. Let’s get them right. That means never freeze the UI on a single input, provide text input fallback and never auto-scroll users on a single input. Here’s why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Money Trading Options Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6593</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/make-money-trading-options-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=make-money-trading-options-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T12:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Make Money Trading Options teaches the art of trading stock options, including the pitfalls to watch out for and how to use simple tools like the Test Trading Strategy and virtual trading tools to find stocks that are most likely to be profitable, so you don’t have to just guess where to invest. Read […]
The post Make Money Trading Options Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on React and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344316</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-react-and-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T19:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a day-job, React-using person, I like to stay abreast of interesting React news. As such, I save a healthy amount of links. Allow me to dump out my latest pile. Most of this is about React but not all …
The post Links on React and JavaScript appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journey Of Awakening Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6592</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/journey-of-awakening-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=journey-of-awakening-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Journey Of Awakening explains the basics of meditation using ideas from multiple spiritual sources, including how to avoid the mental traps that make it difficult so you can practice frequently and make mindfulness, and the many benefits that come with it, part of your daily life. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the […]
The post Journey Of Awakening Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Dynamic Header With Intersection Observer]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/dynamic-header-intersection-observer/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, attaching an event listener to constantly fire a callback on scroll can be performance-intensive. But there is a better way with Intersection Observer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Migrate From jQuery To Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/migrate-jquery-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’re taking a closer look at different approaches and strategies on how we can migrate a web application that uses jQuery framework, and start using one of the coolest React frameworks in the market: Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Introduction (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/refactoring-css-introduction-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS refactoring is not an easy task — it needs to be done in a way that doesn't create problems. First we need to analyze the existing codebase, audit CSS codebase health, discover weaknesses, agree on the approach, and convince management to invest time and resources into the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feel Great Lose Weight Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6571</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/feel-great-lose-weight-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=feel-great-lose-weight-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Feel Great Lose Weight by Dr. Rangan Chatterjee is a book that goes beyond fad diets and quick fixes for weight problems and instead dives into the science of how your body really works when you put food into it and how you can use this information to be fitter and feel better. Read […]
The post Feel Great Lose Weight Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19369</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/07/10/science-and-technology-links-july-10th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use CRISPR, a state-of-the-art gene editing technique, to edit the genes of live human patients in a clinical trials. A clinical trial has begun regarding an HIV vaccine. If you choose to forgo meat to fight climate change, you may lower your individual’s lifetime warming contribution by 2 to 4%. Age-related testosterone loss may … Continue reading Science and Technology links (July 10th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Born To Win Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6553</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/born-to-win-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=born-to-win-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T12:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: Born To Win is a book by Zig Ziglar and his son Tom Ziglar in which they explore how planning and preparation is the only way to win in life and shows you how to use these tools in combination with a vision for your life, goals, and thinking positively to become a winner […]
The post Born To Win Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making A Strong Case For Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/strong-case-for-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility is often overlooked or bolted on to the end of a project. Let’s figure out how to implement and advocate for accessibility from the inception of a project to the release or handoff and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Todd Libby)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hero Code Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://fourminutebooks.com/?p=6552</id>
        <link href="https://fourminutebooks.com/the-hero-code-summary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-hero-code-summary"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T12:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Sentence-Summary: The Hero Code is Admiral William H. McRaven’s guide to becoming a hero, identifying the traits of real-life heroes through inspiring stories of bravery and determination, including many of McRaven’s own experiences as a four-star admiral and in his personal life. Read in: 4 minutes Favorite quote from the author: What is a hero? […]
The post The Hero Code Summary appeared first on Four Minute Books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Rowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools And Practices To Speed Up The Vue.js Development Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though Vue.js claims to have an approachable minimalist framework that can be incrementally adaptable, it can be a little bit overwhelming when starting as a Vue.js newbie. In this article, we’re looking at ways to make writing Vue.js a breeze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Uma Victor)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Figma Interactive Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Components in Figma allows designers to create a component with states (hover, active, clicked, focus) and make it interactive so that every copy of the component will inherit those same interactions by default. Let’s explore how it can reduce the time and effort needed to create interactions for your mock-ups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emiliano Cicero)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an array of Headless CMSes out there. In this article, we delve into headless CMS features to satisfy your content editors, marketers and yourself as a developer. For the experience headless practitioner, this could be a checklist to see what’s new out there. For those starting out on their headless journey, this could be a guide on what to look for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emmanuel Tissera)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HSL Colors In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ahmad Shadeed explains what HSL is, how to use it, and shares some of the useful use-cases and examples that you can use right away in your current projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Testing Flow As It Should Be]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many tools and approaches, email still has quite a few pain points, both for developers and email marketers. Email is difficult because it has too many aspects to set and a few instances with no common rules to follow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andriy Zapisotskyi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s A (Front-End Testing) Trap! Six Common Testing Pitfalls And How To Solve Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When writing front-end tests, you’ll find a lot of pitfalls along the way. Let’s explore common mistakes developers make, and how to avoid them. Testing doesn’t need to be painful, after all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compressing JSON: gzip vs zstd]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19354</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/30/compressing-json-gzip-vs-zstd/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T20:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON is the de facto standard for exchanging data on the Internet. It is relatively simple text format inspired by JavaScript. I say “relatively simple” because you can read and understand the entire JSON specification in minutes. Though JSON is a concise format, it is also better used over a slow network in compressed mode. … Continue reading Compressing JSON: gzip vs zstd]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web Workers In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is single-threaded. This makes it increasingly hard to write smooth and responsive apps. Workers have a bad rep, but can be an important and useful tool in any web developer's toolbelt for these kinds of problems. Let’s get up to speed on Workers on the Web!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Surma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Shades Of July (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome July with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from around the world, they are available with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down Bulky Builds With Netlify And Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static Generation is great for performance — until the app gets too big and build-times go through the roof. Today, we’ll have a look at how Netlify’s fresh On-Demand Builders can fix that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 40 With Mike Cavaliere: What Is Chakra UI For React?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Chakra UI. What is it and how can it help with your React projects? Drew McLellan talks to expert Mike Cavaliere to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Custom Emmet Snippets In VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Manuel explains why Emmet is one of his favorite productivity tools for writing HTML and CSS, and how you can create custom Emmet snippets in Visual Studio Code to help you improve your front-end workflows even more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science and Technology links (June 26th 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://lemire.me/blog/?p=19349</id>
        <link href="https://lemire.me/blog/2021/06/26/science-and-technology-links-june-26th-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T16:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reportedly, half of us own a smartphone. It is often reported that women or visible minority earn less money. However, ugly people are doing comparatively even more poorly. We have highly efficient and cheap solar panels. However, we must also quickly dispose of them after a few years which leads to trash. Handling an increasing … Continue reading Science and Technology links (June 26th 2021)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lemire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Multi-Author Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how we can connect different types of content in a Next.js application. With this technique, we can add any kind of one-to-one, one-to-many, or even many-to-many relationship to our projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dom Habersack)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run A UX Audit For A Major EdTech Platform (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a case study of how a UX audit affects a UI. It explains how a famous educational platform can be analyzed edX against Jakob Nielsen’s usability guidelines. To get started, Mark Lankmiller shares all of the criteria and metrics he used for his UX audit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mark Lankmilier)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: support an experimental template for YouTube feed 📺 Demo | Source

Aggregate content from any YouTube channel rss url https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=<replace_with_channel_id>
Videos are embedded via iframe and loading accelerated by youtube-lite-embed
Ads are reduced thanks to YouTube's policy for embedded videos 🙃
Works on mobile devices with butter smooth horizontal scroll.
Caveat: the template works only with YouTube content. You cannot mix textual RSS feed or other video sources such as Vimeo.
Changed: Default HTML template meta tag adjusted to match convention
Changed: sources in template data is now ordered by last update timestamp (as opposed to alphabetical)
Thank you @PiyushLosalka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>